You're cool with me, Lukas.
Thanks, Jesse.
Me too.
Thanks...
If you're all right with them, then I guess I can live with it.
Okay. I'll take that.
All right, then. Let's head out.
Look at that thing.
What is it?
Some kind of building. I think.
Let's get a closer look.
What are we waiting for? Let's go!
What is this place?
That's what we're trying to figure out.
It's the Temple of the Order of the Stone.
Lukas, are you sure?
He's right! Look.
Do you think they're in there?
Let's go in and find out.
Let's just all be careful.
Okay.
If you spot anything, call it out. We don't have a lot of time.
Isn't it weird how dispenser are carved to look like spooky little faces?
What do you dispense, little guy?
Iiii get the feeling that we don't really wanna find out.
Get behind me.
What was that?
That's probably not a good thing.
Aw, come on, dispenser faces!
I thought we were friends!
Run!
We're trapped!
We activated the dispensers with that pressure plate.
If we can figure out a way to trigger it again, I'll bet that'll shut'em off.
There's a crafting table. Maybe we can make something useful.
What do you mean? We don't have anything.
All of our tools and materials are back home.
All right everyone. Empty your pockets.
Let's see what we've got to work with.
I hav