just keep your distance Jesse come on he was here all night
no it's okay I'll
take that all right then let's head out
look at that thing
what is it let's get a closer look
Oh
what are we waiting for let's go
what is this place that's what we're trying to figure out
it's the temple of
the order of the stone Lucas are you sure
he's right look do you think they're in there let's go in
and find out
let's just all be careful okay if you spot anything call it
out we don't have
a lot of time isn't it weird how dispensers are carved to
look like spooky
little faces what do you dispense little guy I get the
feeling that we don't
really want to find that's probably not a good thing
we're trapped we activated the dispensers with that
pressure plate if
we can figure out a way to trigger it again I bet that'll
shut them off
there's a crafting table maybe we can make something useful
how do what we
don't have anything all of our tools and materials are back
home all right
everyone empty your pockets let's see what we've got to
work with I have a few
sticks left over from building the shelter last night I've
got some flint
and a piece of string all I have are some chicken feathers
I picked up after
that chicken machine exploded
sword oh and some string
string sticks lint and feathers
Océ