Magnus no this armor belongs to you
You earned it Jesse
Hey at least I finally got to be a real hero, right
All those people they're alive the wither storm didn't kill
them Jesse you gotta help him
all of them
Course, I'll save them every one of them
We're the good guys, right that's what we do
Come on Ruben we've got a job to do
You guys help the survivors I need to make sure we find the
people who might be trapped
I
Don't know what to do
I'm not sure what to do
We find the people who might be trapped
Don't worry, it's all over now my friends are gonna help
you. Thank you. Thank you
You're gonna be okay, I promise I thank you
No the command block that's impossible
I don't understand soren said the permitted bomb would
destroy it, but it looks fine
What the guys over here
Yeah
But I thought you were dead I saw you
What's happened here? I'll explain everything just not
right now
Oh
So