Hey, whoa it is.
Not bad. Not bad. Guess it'll have to do.
Axel, what are you doing over there on his side?
Yeah, thought you might bring that up.
It's just that Ruben wanted to take your corner and I
didn't want to crowd him or anything, so I thought I'd
watch from over here.
Take your best shot!
And that's how you shouldn't throw an egg.
Ha! You grieve with me, you grieve with the best!
So, amulet holder, taking an amulet isn't enough. You need
to take my crown as well.
I do not discriminate in my accessory taking. Your crown
shall be mine.
You are but a student. Prepare yourself, for I am here to
give you your final lesson.
That was just a warning!
What? A warning that you need glasses?
It seems the student has become the master and the amulet
holder will win the day.
I don't know what that means, but I love it! I want to put
it on a t-shirt!
But what happened to getting hit by my TNT?
Nobody messes with the boom master!
Jesse! Jesse, you okay?
You had enough yet?
Alrighty, I think noob time is over.
We've had some nice laughs, but now they must come to a
close.
And you should run home!