Stone it is.
Not bad. Not bad. Guess it'll have to do.
So what are you doing over there on his side?
Yeah, I thought you might bring that up.
It's just that Reuben wanted to take your corner,
and I didn't want to crowd him or anything,
so I thought I'd watch from over here.
Take your best shot!
And that's how you shouldn't throw an egg.
Ha! You grief with me, you grief with the best!
So, amulet holder, taking an amulet isn't enough.
You need to take my crown as well.
I do not discriminate in my accessory taking.
Your crown shall be mine.
You are but a student.
Prepare yourself, for I am here to give you your final
blessing.
That was just a warning!
What? A warning that you need glasses?
It seems the student has become the master,
and the amulet holder will win the day.
I don't know what that means, but I love it!
I want to put it on a T-shirt!
But what happened to eating hit by my team teeth?
Nobody messes with the boom master!
Jesse! Jesse, you okay?
Had enough yet?
Alrighty, I think nuke time is over.
I'm going to go get the amulet holder.
I'll be right back.
We've had some nice laughs, but now they must come to a
close.
And you should run home!