We've all made mistakes, including Ivor, right?
Well, nothing's quite that simple.
But I appreciate you saying that.
It was dark and foul, and I was sure I was a goner.
Well, you aren't.
You made it back alive.
Which is more than I can say for some of us.
Oh, man. Ellie. For a second, I almost managed to forget.
Are you guys talking about Eligard?
I just can't believe she's gone. Doesn't feel real.
Guys, it was my fault.
I'm the one who took Eligard's armor.
But you couldn't have known what was going to happen.
She's right. Don't blame yourself, kid.
I, uh, never blame myself for anything.
Being emotional is getting us nowhere!
What I want to know is, what happened out there today?
Why is that thing still alive?
The Formidabomb just wasn't strong enough.
I mean, it ripped the Witherstorm apart, but it didn't make
a dent in the command block.
So the command block is still out there?
Oh, great.
Look, our plan didn't work, so we obviously need a new one.
The question is, what do we do?
Why are you asking me?
Am I expected to know every last thing in the universe?
I need a moment to think.
Is he always like this?
You have no idea.
That jacket. It looks... familiar.
Lucas always wears that jacket.
No, I saw other people wearing it when I was being thrown
from that... that monster.
Even thinking about it hurts.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
Jesse, if what Petra said is true...
I mean, do you think?
I thought for sure they were gone, but if they were just
trapped in the Witherstorm...