Don't touch my pig.
Oh, maybe he's his own pig, Jesse.
You ever thought of that?
You heard what I said.
Jesse?
What?
The amulet.
Soren must be close.
Uh, huh, where'd he go?
You have got to be kidding me.
Sounds like the grinder is backed up.
With loot?
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go!
Whoa!
Keep moving!
Axel, look out!
Ah!
Take that, ugly!
Oh, you want some too?
I'm coming, buddy!
I have had enough of this!
Take that!
Your face, spider!
There's two things I hate.
It's running and monsters.
Any portal?
That's the way out.
Wait!
What?
Look!
Oh no!
Gabriel!
Get away from them!
In your face, monsters!
I think I'm starting to get the hang of this.
Here we go!
Jump!
Whoa!
Oh, great!
Just keeps getting better.
Where's Axel?
He was right behind me.
You!
I swear, I'm not trying to do that.
Get off!
Oh, geez.
Are you hurt?
What?
No, I'm not crying.
Just look!
Hurry!
I hate this.
So, uh, what do we call that?
A herd of Endermen?
A flock of Endermen?
A swarm?