Why did you leave us?
Leave? We're right here!
You ditched us!
Uh, we've been fighting this entire time!
Uh, what's going on?
Uh...
You don't have to worry about the monsters.
They're running away!
Worry about what they're running away from.
I feel like that got bigger.
It did.
It's for minibomb time.
Soren?
It's him! It's you!
Hello, old friends.
You're mine!
It's time to go.
We only get one shot at this.
Remember, once the for minibomb is crafted,
it'll explode in a matter of seconds.
It means whoever's doing the crafting will be in great
danger.
The Forminibomb.
I was hoping...
Well, perhaps we could draw straws.
I'm going to set off the for minibomb.
That's what I was hoping for.
The rest of us will build distractions in its path.
Hopefully it will buy you some time.
Jesse, take my armor.
It will help.
Eh, you can take mine.
It's gotten me out of a lot of jams.
I insist.
I double insist.
I triple insist.
I... insist four times.
Quadruple!
Know it all.
I've never found that insult before.
I bet you don't know what the fifth one is, though.
Quintuple.
Alternatively, pentuple.
Up to you, Jesse.
Wheel armor or nerd armor.