Everyone, this could be a really nasty fight.
The rest of you, go!
Hold them off!
What? I've worn no...
There's no time to argue.
Just head for the corner of the glitch wall!
The what wall?
Hey, you witch! You're not the only one who can draw a
potion!
Come on!
Guys, I think we lost them for...
Wow!
You lost them for wow?
What is that?
Oh...
Wow...
It's like we're at the edge of the world.
Actually, we seem to be at the corner of it.
Welcome to the Far Lands, my friend.
You're welcome.
I'd feel a lot better about going into this crazy wall
thingy if I wasn't still hungry.
I'd rather be hungry than killed by a witch.
I'd rather be eating dinner.
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Swerne, have you been here before?
Not here specifically, but I have visited the Far Lands.
The Order traveled far and wide during our heyday.
How can Ivor live here?
I mean, it's one thing to build a wall world inside the End
with this.
Oh, I doubt he lives here.
He most likely comes here only for his most secretive
research.
Whenever Ivor is hiding in here, it will be extremely well
guarded.
This way, I suspect.
I'd feel better about this if the rest of our group was
with us.
Come on!
Is this... a maze?
It would appear so.
A massive one from the looks of it.
If Ivor used the command block to build this, it could hold
a spiny pearl.
Why do I sense that entering this so-called maze would be a
grave mistake?
Because some part of you still knows Ivor is here.
I've been here before.
It would be a grave mistake.
Because some part of you still knows Ivor.
Unfortunately, this seems to be the only way forward.
There has to be another way.
A secret door, or... I don't know.
Some way around.