Are you that paranoid? Do you really not trust anyone?
That's how I've survived this long.
Please just trust us, just for a minute, okay?
Okay, okay, you sold me!
I'm in.
Oh, but we might have a little bit of a problem getting out
of here.
Huh? You're Magnus. You can just walk out of here.
Hello. I don't know if you've looked around this place, but
it's kind of full of griefers.
But that's kind of awesome, right?
No. You've heard about the whole challenging the king for
his crown thing, right? It's like their thing.
So long as I'm king, I can't leave this tower.
But you're Magnus. No one can beat you.
And that's the problem. Simply put, that's life as king of
Boomtown.
Just choose a new king and then come with us.
Look, I've beaten them dozens of times, and none are
worthy. They'll see right through it.
But you, huh, you're the newcomer with the gold amulet.
By now there'll probably be all sorts of rumors about how
awesome you are.
If you beat me, then I'll be able to leave.
Can't believe I didn't think of it before!
They're gonna call this the fight of the century!