The "Redstone Rap!"
Aaaand just like that, I’m nervous again.
Don’t talk like that! We can do this! Just stick to the plan and everything will be fine.
This year, we can't lose!
Let's do it.
Building... starts... now!
Oh, no! A fireworks dispenser?! I’m soooo scared!
You worry about your build and we’ll worry about ours.
And now, the moment of truth.
Here goes nothing…
Aw man, that looks so cool. We’ll win this for sure.
The Creeper was definitely the right way to go.
Guys, people are looking at us.
Good build, man!
What?
No way...
It's just a bunch of dyed wool!?
Oh, no! Reuben's on fire!
Reuben, no! Come back!
The lava's getting closer!
It's gonna ruin the build!
Reuben's going to get lost!
You guys stay and save the build.
On it!
We've got it covered, Jesse. Be careful.
We’ll meet up with you at Endercon!
Reuben?! Where are you?
Just give me an oink if you can hear me.