The only way off this bridge is through them.
I don't wanna die!
Too many herk from prince, I don't want to die!
No, my red.
No, no.
Stop it!
Shut up.
I said, shut up!
So, when we're making the deal, I need you to let me do the
talking, okay?
Should I be nervous about this?
Given your personality, your life experience, and
everything else you've done to make it
to this moment, yes.
Jesse!
And Petra?
Hey, you all know Petra, my new super close friend.
We're super close now.
We ran into each other while I was looking for Ruben.
What were you doing in the woods, Petra?
Nothing, just drawn by the sound of Jesse's high-pitched
screams.
I would have been spider-bait if she hadn't found me.
Sorry we didn't come with you, Jesse.
But hey, we won!
We did okay, didn't we?
I still wish I'd gotten that part in the back to look
better.
There could have been more fireworks in there, somewhere.