The only way off this bridge is through them.
I don't wanna die!
Don't you know you dive into the water you don't land on
top of it pull yourself together and follow me
Oh
Just let me know if you see Reuben anywhere, he's got to be
here somewhere. I hope you're right
So when we're making the deal I need you to let me do the
talking, okay
Should I be nervous about this?
Given your personality your life experience and everything
else you've done to make it to this moment
Yes
Jesse and
Petra hey you all know Petra my new super close friend.
We're super close now
We ran into each other while I was looking for Reuben
couldn't find him, huh?
He'll turn up sooner or later. I just know it I saw him but
before I knew what was happening
We were under attack by a zombie horde. I told him to run
it was for his own good
Sorry, we didn't come with you Jesse, but hey we won
We
Did okay didn't we I still wish I'd gotten that part in the
back to look better I
Could have fit more fireworks in there somewhere