Alright, let's jump!
Don't you know you dive into the water you don't land on
top of it
Pull yourself together and follow me
So when we're making the deal I need you to let me do the
talking, okay
Should I be nervous about this?
Given your personality your life experience and everything
else you've done to make it to this moment
Yes
Jesse and
Petra hey you all know Petra my new super close friend.
We're super close now
We ran into each other while I was looking for Ruben. What
were you doing in the woods Petra? Nothing just
Drawn by the sound of Jesse's high-pitched screams. I would
have been spider-bate if she hadn't found me
Sorry, we didn't come with you Jesse, but hey we won
We did okay, didn't we I still wish I'd gotten that part in
the back to look better
There could have been more fireworks in there somewhere