Alright, let's jump!
AHHHHH!
Don't you know, you dive into the water, you don't land on
top of it.
Pull yourself together and follow me.
Just let me know if you see Ruben anywhere.
He's gotta be here somewhere.
I hope you're right.
So, when we're making the deal, I need you to let me do the
talking, okay?
Should I be nervous about this?
Given your personality, your life experience, and
everything else you've done to make it to this moment...
Yes.
Jesse!
And Petra?
Hey, you all know Petra, my new super close friend.
We're super close now.
We ran into each other while I was looking for Ruben.
Couldn't find him, huh?
He'll turn up sooner or later, I just know it.
I saw him, but before I knew what was happening, we were
under attack by a zombie horde.
I told him to run, it was for his own good.
Sorry we didn't come with you, Jesse.
But hey, we won!
We did okay, didn't we?
I still wish I'd gotten that part in the back to look
better.
I could have fit more fireworks in there, somewhere.