All right, let’s jump!
Aaaaah!
Burns, it burns!
Don’t you know? You dive INTO the water… you don’t land on top of it.
Pull yourself together, and follow me.
So, when we’re making the deal, I need you to let me do the talking, okay?
Should I be nervous about this?
Given your personality, your life experience, and everything else you've done to make it to this moment?
..Yes.
Jesse!
… and… Petra?
Hey, you all know Petra... my new super-close friend.
We're super-close now.
We ran into each other while I was looking for Reuben.
What were you doing in the woods, Petra?
Nothing. Just… drawn by the sound of Jesse’s high-pitched screams.
I would’ve been spider-bait if she hadn’t found me.
Sorry we didn’t come with you, Jesse.
But hey, we won!
We did okay, didn’t we?
I still wish I’d gotten that part in the back to look better