We're the Dead Enders.
Whoa! It sounds like a name for pirates.
It's cool.
Okay, Dead Enders. You guys are in Booth 5.
Is that a freakin' beacon?
They have a freakin' beacon?!
Freakin' Beacon!?
That's stained glass.
They aren't just building a beacon.
They're building a rainbow beacon.
Our design is way cooler.
Our design is better. A creeper that shoots fireworks is cooler than a fancy light.
Their difficulty score is going to be higher than our total score.
But we’ve got something they don’t... fireworks.
We should probably stop staring at them.
Hahaha! Look, it's the Order of the Losers. Again.
Good one, Gill!
We're just looking.
There’ll be plenty of time for you all to look at it after it wins and gets shown at Endercon.
You're being unpleasant.
Maybe not all of you…
Endercon doesn't allow outside food or drink.
Shut up.
What's that?
Jesse said “shut up.“
Do you need to hear it again?
I don't know, maybe?
Stop wasting your time, Aiden.
We've got work to do.
You're lucky I'm busy.
Hey Jesse. Guys.
Hey Petra.
How's the build going?
Only time will tell. But we’re optimistic.
Hey Petra, I forgot to thank you for that nether star.
Hey Lukas.
Not a problem.
You helped these tools?
For the right price, I’ll help anyone.
If you need anything, you know where to find me.
None of us know where to find you.
Exactly.
No hard feelings guys.
If you're cool with Petra, you're cool with us.