Ellegaardd, we've actually got much bigger problems to deal
with.
We're actually here to get your help.
There's a giant wither storm that's attacking the entire
world.
A wither what? What are you talking about? Who sent you?
Gabriel sent me.
Look, you both seem like very pleasant people who are prone
to fainting,
but I simply don't have the brain power for this.
I'm in the middle of my greatest project to date.
A powerful block capable of altering reality itself.
I've seen one of those before. It's a command block.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. How do you know what a command
block is?
We've seen one up close before. It was Ivor's.
He's done something terrible with it.
The world needs the Order of the Stone. That's why we're
here.
Sorry to bust your circuits, but the Order isn't really
together anymore.
We, uh, sort of disassembled.
That's actually kind of why we're here.
Gabriel's amulet.
Yes, he gave it to me so that I could find the Order.
Your wither storm problem was created by a command block,
yes?
That means a command block could be the perfect way of
beating it.
And maybe...
Will you help me make one?
It's going to work this time.
I can feel it.
Right here. In my brain.
I could help too.