I've got Petra!
They don't take Gabriel!
Hold on, this might be a bumpy ride.
Come on, horses!
Whatever you do, don't look back!
Ah! I look!
Watch out!
It's gaining on us!
It's coming after us!
Keep longer!
We can stop, please!
Please!
I'm doing the best I can.
Jesse, look out!
I'm going to get you!
Have I seen Enderman attack a weather storm?
Enderman move blocks. It's what they do.
There! We can hide over there.
Guys, come on!
We've got to build a new one, like right now.
Come on, faster!
Yee-haw!
Yee-haw! Yee-haw!
I saw you screaming in my ear!
Sorry.
We made it!
We actually freaking made it!
Hey, how are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I don't really feel like myself.
I still can't believe you're even alive.
Do you not recognize us?
I'm Axel. This is Olivia.
We've been friends for a really long time.