Wow.
It's absolutely incredible.
How did they build this?
This looks like some sort of tracking system.
It's the Order. It's showing where they are right now.
Look, we don't know enough about how this thing works.
Maybe the amulet only tracks them when they're on the
surface.
Or maybe it doesn't work when they're in the Nether.
We have to go off what we do know.
Petra is relying on us.
That Witherstorm is still out there.
We know that Gabriel was trying to tell us something.
We've got to find the Order of the Stone.
But there are only two lights.
There are only two members of the Order left.
He said Sorin was missing.
That leaves Magnus.
Or Eligard.
Let's head out.
I'm not going with you guys. I have to stay here.
If I know Petra, she's probably doing everything she can to
find this place.
Just stay safe, okay?
If there's even a small chance she's alive, I have to stay.
Go. Get help.
I'm going to focus on making this place safe before
nightfall.
This temple is pretty big though.
If we're going to have a chance at fortifying it, I'm going
to need some help.
If maybe one of you guys can hang back with me.
Sounds like Olivia will have you totally covered while me
and Jessie are out finding Magnus.
Finding Magnus? You really think that's how it's going to
go?
We need Eligard. She's the world's greatest engineer.
She'll figure out a way to stop that thing.
We're trying to destroy it.
And when it comes to destruction, Magnus is the master.
You're a smart person, Jessie.
Obviously, the smart thing to do is to go get Magnus.
I... think Axel meant Eligard there, Jessie.
Uh, no. I don't think I did. Pretty sure Axel meant Magnus.
Jessie, the point is you should be going to Eligard's. It's
the clear choice to make.
You've got to come with me.
You're my best friend, Jessie.
It's you and me. Like always.
Think about it, Jessie.
This is more of a gut call.
We need to make sure we get this right. We're not going to
get a second shot at this.
Whatever decision you make, I'll be cool with it.
Really?
As long as it's me.
Come on, Jessie. This is an easy call.