You're the genius, Eligar. Let's get started.
Fantastic.
Okay, excellent. Good. This is so exciting. Terribly
exciting.
Has it gotten this far before?
No, never!
Is it... destabilizing?
Oh, no!
Eligar, come on!
We need to go! We need to get to the portal!
Over here!
This way!
Captain!
Okay, just a little farther.
Wow, that's certainly impressive.
Wow.
Who goes there?
Oh, Jesse? Is that you?
Lucas, did you build all of this?
Well, yeah.
I figured I would try and fortify the portal.
Yeah! I figured I would try and fortify the place, you know?
Nice!
Quick, come on! You guys are never gonna believe who showed
up while you were gone.
Petra!
Hey, guys. How's it going?
I'm so glad you're okay, Petra.
Yeah, I'm pretty stoked about it myself.
And it's really good to see you, Jesse.
Back there in Gabriel's bunker, it got pretty dicey.