Soren come back here dude, what a chicken
Jesse you can handle things out here, right? What I can't let him get himself killed
Just get to the command block and destroy it
Sorry, so much for the mighty order of the stone
Doesn't matter. We have work to do
We need to get those Enderman to attack it
Tractor beam Jesse that's it
Make them chase you into the tractor beam
Yes, they're falling for it
Jesse look, it's working
Now we just need to find you a way up
Everyone empty your pockets. Let's see
I've got redstone and cobblestone from I Wars army. I have some TNT from boomtown
I've got pistons repeaters some wool some leftover slime
Oh, and I still have that minecart. That's gotta be enough to make something
I'm gonna go get some more of that
And I still have that minecart that's gotta be enough to make something right?
I mean if we use the TNT on say the minecart or those pistons and we do have all that cobblestone
Maybe we could build a ramp or even go straight up vertically or find a way to use redstone
We're close to an answer. I can feel it