Soren, you coward, I can't believe you!
I can. Jesse, you can handle things out here, right?
What?
I can't let him get himself killed! Just get to the command block and destroy it! Soren!
So much for the mighty Order of the Stone.
Doesn't matter. We have work to do.
We need to get those Endermen to attack it!
The Tractor Beam! Jesse, that's it!
Make them chase you into the Tractor Beam!
How do you like the bag? Or what? Free?
Yes, they're falling for it!
Jesse, look! It's working!
That hole's big enough to get inside of.
Now we just need to find you a way up.
Or build you a way up.
That's it! Everyone, empty your pockets!
Let's see...
I've got Redstone and Cobblestone from Iowars Armory.
I've got some TNT from Boomtown.
I've got Pistons, Repeaters, and...
I've got Pistons, Repeaters, some wool, some leftover slime...
Oh, and I still have that Minecart.
That's gotta be enough to make something, right?
I mean, if we use the TNT on, say...
The Minecart?
Or those Pistons...
And we do have all that Cobblestone.
Maybe we could build a ramp?
Or even go straight up vertically.
Or find a way to use Redstone.
We're close to an answer. I can feel it!