There's no way we're going into some crazy maze that I were
built to keep people away.
We'll find some other way through.
Best decision you've made all day.
Huh. We can probably climb these.
Everyone, on guard!
There's too many! We can't fight them all!
Who needs to climb when you have a potion of leaping?
Guys, climb the vines!
Well, that worked, I suppose.
Yeah, I guess.
But now what do we do? We're all separated.
Let's just head that way and find a place where the paths
connect.
Sure hope they don't get lost in there.
I hope I don't get lost in there.
Hey, that must be Ivor's lab.
Wish it was a little closer.
What's that?
Looks like Ivor kept some redstone dust handy.
And a slime ball.
Redstone blocks, some pistons.
I wonder what this thing's supposed to be.
Hello? Anyone?
Olivia, is that you?
Jesse, there you are.
This maze? We don't have time for this.
Who even knows where the others are by now?
I mean, the clock's ticking here, Jesse.
Yet we're lost in some elaborate puzzle.