We followed Ivor to the Far Lands. We might as well keep going.
Here we go. Into another dungeon of doom.
Whoa. A stone waterfall?
That's the craziest thing I've ever seen.
The Far Lands may be perilous, but they are indisputably fascinating.
We should probably keep moving.
Guys, looks like this is a...
There's too many! We can't light them all!
Everyone, back!
Ugh!
Who needs to climb when you have a potion of leaping?
Guys, carve the vines!
Well, that worked, I suppose.
Yeah, I guess.
But now what do we do? We're all separated.
Let's just head that way and find a place where the pads connect.
Sure hope they don't get lost in there.
I hope I don't get lost in there.
Sigh.
Hey, that must be Ivor's lab.
Wish it was a little closer.
Huh. What's that?
Looks like Ivor kept some redstone dust handy.
And a slime ball.
Huh. Redstone blocks. Some pistons.
I wonder what this thing's supposed to be.
Hello? Anyone?
Olivia! Is that you?
Jesse! There you are.
This maze? We don't have time for this.
Who even knows where the others are by now?
I mean, the clock's ticking here, Jesse.
Yet we're lost in some elaborate puzzle.
Thanks for watching!