Be careful out there.
Totally am!
Add up all the times he was a jerk to us, and this doesn't compare.
You're being ridiculous. And if anything happens to him, I'm blaming you.
I didn't know it would rain.
You feeling good about yourself?
He'll be fine.
Hey, guys. I, um... I picked some apples.
You're more than welcome to some if you want.
Thanks, Lukas.
You got up early and did all this?
I figure we have to eat.
I thought you left.
Yeah. Me too. I got a tower up as fast as I could.
I tried to do some thinking... but it was too cold…
And then it started raining.
No, it's all right. It's just...
It's been a long night.
I'm resourceful, y'know? People always say that.
And I'm a good friend.
Most of the time. I'm a good friend.
Yesterday I wasn't at my best for one second and it's like... none of that matters.
Except for one thing...
Petra still needs us.
I let her down once.
It won't happen again.