And these are supposed to be the Ender crystals?
Scale models of them. They were the secret to the dragon's
demise.
The secret, huh?
Ha, if only you'd been there. It was a fight for the ages.
We'd spent weeks preparing for our greatest battle ever.
But even so, the Ender Dragon was stronger than even I had
imagined.
I realized that it was drawing strength from the Ender
crystals,
and that the crystals had to be destroyed.
I hit the first with a perfectly placed arrow,
the second I destroyed by launching myself on the shockwave
of Magnus' TNT.
Using only my strength and my wiles,
I steered the foul beast toward the third crystal.
I flew the dragon directly toward the final crystal.
Only then did Gabriel deliver his famous final blow.
We became heroes, and eventually, legends.
The greatest the world has ever known.