The order failed. Part of me was still holding out hope
that they could fix things, but...
I guess I should have known better.
You're really not making me feel better, Reuben.
Oh, you want help, do you?
That's what I said, isn't it? Just as you once helped us
before.
This isn't about the past, it's about the future.
There are three of those things now.
You say that like it's my fault!
It is your fault!
I'll take responsibility for once, Soren.
Soren, you need to listen to me.
Hush, Ivor, for once!
I told you, I wouldn't have followed you here without good
reason.
What you don't understand is, you are all in very grave
danger.
Obviously!
No, I mean specifically this group.
The Witherstorm isn't acting randomly. It's following
Gabriel.
You see, I may have programmed it to follow his amulet.
I have the amulet, Ivor. I have all along.
What? Ivor, you fool! You've created a monster that's
following Jesse!
I... I didn't know.
And it's only getting stronger.
You don't think I realize that? Nothing can stop those
things!
Nothing even hurts them!
Well, except Enderman.
We actually just saw a bunch of Enderman pull blocks off a
Witherstorm.
So, enough of them working together might be able to
destroy a Witherstorm entirely.
The question is, how to bring the storms and the Enderman
together?
Enderman aren't pets. They don't follow orders.
At least, not from mere mortals.
Thanks for watching!