Are you gonna help us take on the winter storm?
Ha! Help you? You're gonna help me!
Uh, we've been fighting this entire time!
Ah!
Uh, what's going on?
You don't have to worry about the monsters!
They're running away!
Worry about what they're running away from.
I feel like that got bigger.
It did.
It's verminabomb time.
Zoran?
It's him! It's you!
Hello, old friends.
It's time to go.
We only get one shot at this.
Remember, once the verminabomb is crafted,
it'll explode in a matter of seconds.
It means whoever is doing the crafting will be in great
danger.
I'm going to go get Zoran.
Whoever is doing the crafting will be in great danger.
I was hoping, well, perhaps we could draw straws.
I'm going to set off the verminabomb.
That's what I was hoping for.
The rest of us will build distractions in its path.
Hopefully it will buy you some time.
Jesse, take my armor. It will help.
Nah, you can take mine.
It's gotten me out of a lot of jams.
I insist.
I double insist.
I triple insist.
I insist four times.
Quadruple!
Know it all.
I've never found that insulting.
I bet you don't know what the fifth one is though.
Quintuple.
Alternatively, pentuple.
Up to you, Jesse.
Real armor or nerd armor.