Let's keep this between us for now.
I was thinking the same thing.
They might get upset or... I don't know.
Exactly. We don't know.
When the time comes, I'll share it with those that wish to
know.
Until then, I hope you can be discreet.
Hey guys, I have an idea.
Okay.
Magnus, help!
Well, alright. But I have another idea.
Is it yelling for Eligard?
Well, not anymore.
They aren't coming back.
They couldn't abandon us if they wanted to.
As long as we have...
This!
Flint and Steel? I don't get it.
It's not... That's not what I meant to pull out.
Hold on.
This!
Here, let me see it.
Do you mind?
I just want to see it.
You can see it without touching.
Not if you can't get it to work.
It's working fine.
Soar it!
This is the spot that has to be.
Maybe.
This is definitely it.
Get ready to dig, people.
Who knows how far down that goes?
Anyone else have a better plan?
Jesse's talking to you, Lucas.
I know. I just...
I know!
Let's get to it, then.
Are we cool?
It's a hole!
Does that mean we're cool?
I'll find out!
I guess that makes sense. You dig, you get a hole.
I'm not sure why I expected anything else.
That was my point.
No, it wasn't.
Jesse's got this, you guys.