It is said that within every loss, every challenge...
...and every failure, there is a gift.
And when our band of unlikely adventurers are tasked with
saving the world from the
coming storm, they will bring together the bravest and the
brightest to stop it.
But finding the last and most elusive member of the Order
of the Stone and his legendary
Formidi-bomb would prove their most perilous mission yet.
For some would rather our heroes' story end here, shutting
the door on their adventure forever.
But like all doors, when one closes, another is bound to
open.
Stop him!
You won't get away.
Watch it!
Get out of the way!
Everyone okay?
I felt all of that.
That was one heck of a landing, Axel.
He mostly used his face.
We need to find Soren.
Yeah.
I still can't figure out how Ivor made the door close.
Maybe we should focus more on how it opens.
That's basically what I said.
Are you okay?
Of course. Why would you feel the need to ask?
Just checking in.
I am a-oh...
a-oh...
My goodness...
Just give it a second..
Do not be frightened or alarmed.
But it's getting worse.
I'm in a lot of pain.