you're just as good as them Olivia just be confident maybe
but thanks for the
vote of confidence
each and every one of you your hard work inspires me every
day I am about to
enter my dome of concentration where I will be unreachable
for the foreseeable
future I will emerge when I complete my latest and greatest
creation the
command block
continue working continue building and whatever person most
impresses me they
shall be my protege ready to help usher in a new era of
innovation and creativity
Calvin throw the switch
Jesse we need to get there before she totally locks herself
in
so elegant trying to make a command block in there I don't
know Jesse that
sounds pretty risky you saw what happened when I were tried
to control a
command block excuse me mr. Calvin was it we need to speak
to elegant it's
oh I'm afraid that's quite impossible did you hear the
speech she's on lockdown
until she completes her next great invention I have a
message from Gabriel
okay elegant old friend
I'm afraid I have many more things to attend to than
answering all of your
questions I must go better just take this repeater disable
the stair
controls we don't want any troublemakers disturbing elegant
guess
we'll need to get another repeater we need three stone two
redstone torches
and one pile of redstone dust to make one right