I don't understand. How did you escape?
If you hadn't pulled me out of the Witherstorm's clutches...
Well, let's just not think about that.
I came here to the temple, hoping against hope to find
other survivors.
Wow, did Petra get away too? Did you see?
All that creature left in its wake was bedrock.
All those people...
Your friend Petra...
No one could get away.
We are alive.
That means there's still hope.
Come along. Everyone else is still inside.
Boy, can't remember the last time I saw this place.
Would someone care to explain what he is doing here?
Oh, this isn't going to go well.
Right, I forgot to mention. Axel went on a little...
...adventure of his own while you were gone.
An adventure to get him?
Did you know about this?
Look, just wait here a second while I figure out what's
going on.
Much appreciated.
So, who are you then?
And why'd you bring the Queen of the Nerds with you?
That's Jesse, my best friend.
Trust me, Jesse's totally cool.
I'll be the judge of that, huh?