Yeah, he's kind of a jerk sometimes, but he's our jerk, you
know? Can't help but like him.
Interesting. Very interesting. Then why didn't you listen
to his plan to come get me?
I figured that we needed Brains to fight the Witherstorm.
And Brains means Eligard.
Yeah, I've definitely heard that a lot. I'll try not to let
it hurt my feelings too much.
Well, just keep on your toes.
Uh, guys?
I told you he was going to catch up with us.
You really weren't kidding.
No. How could he find me again?
We can hatch all that out later. Come on, we've got to get
out of here!
This creature never stops.
The Sorens isn't much farther. We can make it.
I'm getting very tired of this Witherstorm.
Agreed.
The Sorens' place has got to be just ahead of us.
Yeah, it's a good idea.
I think we should go and check it out.
Yeah, I think we should go and check it out.
I'm getting very tired of this Witherstorm.
Agreed.
The Sorens' place has got to be just ahead. Come on!
Soren really lived down here? It's so far from... anyone.
Enchanting, isn't it?
Yeah, and I'm really not feeling those columns.
Aw, come on! It's fine! Look! Woo!
Just don't fall, okay?
Oh, that is deep. That is very, very deep.
Hang on! I'm coming!
Oh, man, we've got Enderman.
It was more of a drop than I was expecting.
Enderman.
There were so many, I didn't think they ever came in groups
that big.
No kidding. It's like an Enderman party.
I heard your voice and thought I would come down to help.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.