Axel's one of my best friends. He makes me laugh and he
always sticks up for his friends
Interesting very interesting
Then why didn't you listen to his plan to come get me?
I figured that we needed brains to fight the wither storm
and brains means elegant. Yeah, I've definitely heard that
a lot
I'll try not to let it hurt my feelings too much. Well,
just keep on your toes
I
Guys
I told you we're gonna catch up with this
Really weren't kidding
How can it find me again
I
Can't all that out later, come on, we got to get out of
here this creature never stop
Soren's isn't much farther. We can make it
I
Am getting very tired of this wither storm agreed place has
gotta be just ahead. Come on
I
Soren really live down here. It's so far from anyone
Enchanting isn't it?
Yeah, and I'm really not feeling those columns
Oh
Just don't fall, okay. Oh
That is deep that is very very deep
Oh
It was more of a drop than I was
Enderman there were so many I didn't think they ever came
in groups that big
No kidding. It's like an enderman party. I heard your voice
and thought I would come down to hell