Magnus no this armor belongs to you you earned it Jesse
Hey at least I finally got to be a real hero, right
All those people they're alive the wither storm didn't kill
them Jesse you gotta help him
all of them
Of course, I'll save them every one of them
We're the good guys, right that's what we do
I
Come on Reuben, we've got a job to do
You
Guys help the survivors. I need to make sure we find the
people who might be trapped
It's all over now my friends are gonna help you thank you.
Thank you
You're gonna be okay, I promise I
I thank you
That's impossible, I don't understand soren said to from it
about this trip it looks fine
What the guys over here
No
But I thought you were dead I saw you
Oh
You