What part of throwing the fight was that what say you noob
I am king and those who challenge me will be
Annihilated Jesse. I think he just lost it Magnus crowds a
cannon
Yeah, finish it with a cannon if it's a cannon you want
It's a cannon you'll get
Yep, he's completely lost it dudes going to the kill Jesse
even a crap that I don't know greatest thing in your life
Like right now. Well, there's still some material in the
chest
Supposed to throw the fight
Oh
Yeah, but the TNT inside the cannon
I got you
Flying pink jokes are totally played out
Oh
I
Say something that champ it's just the winner sometimes I
don't know gives us speech
Quantificates or eights say something