Luck sometimes visits the most unskilled of us, but it
never lingers.
Skill, mastery, these are the things that will see you
defeated!
Magnus, craft a cannon!
Yeah! Finish it with a cannon!
If it's a cannon you want, it's a cannon you'll get!
Yep, he's completely lost it.
Dude's going for the kill.
Jesse, you'd better craft the, I don't know, greatest thing
in your life, like right now!
Well, there's still some material in the chest.
That's it, Jesse, go!
Actually, check it out.
That should hold him.
Yeah, it's, yeah, um, yeah, it might do, but Jesse, look!
Whoa!
Supposed to throw the fight.
No!
Jesse, you down!
Get him!
No, leave it out!
Stop! I got this little stuff!
Coming your way!
I got you a bow and some arrows!
A bow? In a cannon fight?
Actually, there are all sorts of cliched lines about this.
Yeah, but the TNT, inside the cannon!
TNT plus arrow.
Oh yeah!
Let me see how well you slide!
How bad!
I got you, I got you!
Man, there's no foolishness right now.
Hey Magnus!
Yeah, short stub?
Flying pig jokes are totally played out.
No!
We have a winner!
The Amulet Holder!
Can I say something there, champ?
It's just the winner sometimes, I don't know, gives a
speech.
Pontificates, orates, say something.