My hero, Reuben the Pig.
He may have seemed like just a pig to most people,
but he was so much more.
And at the end of the day, he saved us all.
For Reuben!
Jesse, this Nether Star is all that remained
when the Wither Storm was destroyed.
Would you please do the honors?
Oh, man, this stage is so cool.
I'm so excited.
Man, this stage is so cool.
My friends, I am now pleased to introduce to you
a new Order of the Stone.
A new Order of the Stone!
And so it was that a new Order of the Stone was born,
one whose adventures were only just beginning.
For though the world had been saved
and the command block destroyed,
there are many more worlds than just this one.
Thank you for watching.