Ella guard no time for specifics. I'm afraid
Hey you goddle girl switch on that T-flop circuit to
activate the delivery shoots and you grab me a blaze rod
and an iron block
She wants me to do something for her. What if I screw it
up? What if I oh I feel light-headed
Now I need an assistant to help with my assistant think you
can handle it on your own
Olivia Olivia, can you hear me? I don't think that I've
ever fainted before
So embarrassing everything working over
Uh
Trial number six thousand four hundred fifty one another
bust
Now about you three
Your friend here. Does she fall over frequently? Is this
gonna be a regular occurrence? I know I'm sorry
I was just so excited to end with me always pacing around
lost in my own brilliant thoughts
I could have tripped over you and conked my brain
Brilliant thoughts
I could see that