Ella guard no time for specifics. I'm afraid
Hey you goggle girl switch on that T-flop circuit to
activate the delivery shoots and you grab me a blaze rod
and an iron block
She wants me to do something for her. What if I screw it
up? What if I oh I feel light-headed
Now I need an assistant to help with my assistant think you
can handle it on your own
Olivia Olivia, can you hear me? I don't think that I've
ever fainted before
So embarrassing everything working over
I'll just do it myself then
Loser oh
Trial number six thousand four hundred fifty one another
bust
Now about you three
Your friend here does she fall over frequently is this
gonna be a regular occurrence I
Know I'm sorry. I was just so excited to and with me always
pacing around lost in my own brilliant thoughts
I could have tripped over you and conked my brain
Brilliant thoughts go on
I could see that