Huh?
What?
Where's Petra?
We did everything we could.
What are you saying?
It was chaos.
There wasn't much I could do.
Jesse's right.
Petra is still up there.
I got scared.
Just for a second.
You got scared?
It wasn't my fault.
You got scared and it's not your fault?
Back off, Axel.
We gotta go back.
She just needs more time.
Petra needs our help.
We're going.
There she is.
Come on, come on.
You again.
Ivor.
You ruined everything.
You can't blame us.
Your plan, your monster, your fault.
Maybe.
But if you hadn't stolen from me, I would have destroyed it.
And all of those people would have been saved.
There's nothing left up there.
Nothing but that weather storm.
Why are we wasting time talking to this jerk?
We have to go and get Petra.
The girl.
I saw her.
What?
While I was running toward the portal, I passed her.
She was running in the opposite direction.
Such bravery.
Of course.
There's a fine line between bravery and stupidity.
And your friend has crossed it.
I'm sorry.
I'm saying she's stupid.