Hello boomtown, how we all doing, huh?
Hey, that's awesome
So proud standing in front of you all today. Well you guys
ready then
Wait, what's going on? Oh, well, that's not good
Help me! What are we?
Go, red messing boomtown, go!
Okay, just a little farther
Wow, someone really went bonkers with the defenses, huh?
Who goes there? Oh, Jesse?
Oh, Jesse?
Who goes there? Oh, Jesse? Is that you? Lucas, did you
build all of this?
Well, yeah, I figured I would try and fortify the place,
you know?
Nice!
Quick, come on. You guys are never gonna believe who showed
up while you were gone
Gabriel
Hello everyone, it is good to see you
He showed up not too long before you guys
You always were a tough cookie to keep down
It's good to see you too, you meathead
And it's especially good to see you, Jesse. I fear that you
might be the last face I ever saw
Getting here was hard
But it was worth it
Thank you for watching