Oh no, my machine! Oh my cow!
Oh no, your amazing invention.
You! You did this!
Hey, I am not taking credit for any of this.
That machine's been a cow death trap since block one.
Okay, that's a step in the right direction.
Good.
Bam, more open.
Switch is on.
Okay, good, good.
Wow, here it is.
Ellegard's Redstone Laboratory.
Seems more like an entrance or a foyer or something.
Don't worry pal, we'll find her.
I just hope she can actually help us.
Okay, let's go.
It's not going to actually help us.
That might be the last Redstone stuff I've ever seen in my
life.
You can say that again.
She's moving a lot of different ingredients around here.
Man, look at all this, huh?
Whatever she's working on, if it requires all of these
ingredients, it must be something
really, really big.