He could be anywhere, stay on your guard!
Invisible or not, he isn't going to get by me.
Please, I would. Just stand down.
There's no time for this.
Jesse! Gabriel!
Even more of you?
Will this parade of useless babblers never cease?
What's going on?
We found Ivor. We stopped him.
False. You have stopped nothing.
A query.
I'm not sure what's going on.
I'm sure he's not going to make it.
False. You have stopped nothing.
A query.
Have you ever seen the effects of a splash potion of
slowness?
What?
I'm falling around.
You big jug.
Magnus and the other guard may think they can stop me,
that they can destroy the Wither Storm,
but they are mistaken, and it will cost them their lives.