It's one of his invisibility potions, he could be anywhere!
Invisible or not, he isn't going to get by me.
Please, Ivor, just stand down!
This one's on you, you puffed up fool!
There's no time for this!
Jesse! Gabriel!
Even more of you?
Will this parade of useless babblers never cease?
What's going on?
You found Ivor, we stopped him.
False!
You have stopped nothing.
A query.
Have you ever seen the effects of a splash potion of
slowness?
What?
I'm coming around.
You big jerk!
Get me out!
Magnus and Ellegaard may think that Ivor is a monster,
Ellegaard may think they can stop me, that they can destroy
the wither storm,
but they are mistaken, and it will cost them their lives.
you