Let's do this.
All right.
Good job, Jesse.
See?
This must be their enchantment room.
Doesn't this look like Ivor's creepy basement?
Find anything useful?
Not sure about useful, but definitely interesting.
There is a lot of history in this room.
The battle was fierce, but the Order of the Stone emerged
triumphant, saving the land and ensuring that peace and
prosperity would reign forever.
Well, not exactly forever.
These five members, five friends, together would give so
much to gain their rightful place as five years.
They would author their own end.
They would slay a dragon.
Ivor was a member of the Order of the Stone?
The story's never mentioned him.
This is so crazy.