Sure.
That's the best thing I've heard in years.
Admittedly, it's not a very high bar.
Don't worry. I'm going to help you, because that's what
friends do.
Before we leave, I'm going to give my old friends a gift.
A gift of song.
What's happening?
Oh.
Gary may seem scary, but he's a swell guy.
Sally Dilly Dally's, give her credit she tries
They might look the same to the untrained eye
But that's a lie, so I say
Wait, is that... Are you...
Soren'.
Whoa.
Hey.
You look terrible.
Terribly handsome.
Hello, old friend.
We've been looking for you.
Look away.
You upset them.
You altered their behavior.
Okay, let's go.
And the heads just keep on coming.
I wasn't expecting so many house guests.
There's no way I have enough seashell subs for all of them.
How are we supposed to get out of here?
We need to come up with a plan.
And not our usual we'll come up with a plan when we have
to...
Oh, wait, now we have to kind of plan.