We have to tell the others.
Your friends? No! That's a bad idea.
You have to.
It's just gonna cause panic,
and we can't afford that right now.
When the time comes,
I'll share it with those that wish to know.
Until then, I hope you can be discreet.
Hey, guys, I have an idea!
Okay.
Magnus! Help!
Well, all right... but I have another idea.
Is it yelling for Ellegaard?
Not... anymore.
Look, they aren't coming back.
They couldn't abandon us if they wanted to.
As long as we have...
This!
Flint and Steel? I don't get it.
It's not... that's not what I meant to pull out.
Hold on.
Uh... This!
Here, let me see it.
Do you mind?
I just want to see it.
You can see it without touching.
Not! If you can't get it to work, it's working fine.
Soren!
This is the spot. It has to be.
Maybe...
This is definitely it.
Get ready to dig, people.
Who knows how far down that goes?
Anyone else have a better plan?
Jesse's talking to you, Lukas.
I know. I just... need a...
PAI-GOW!
Let's get to it then.
Are we cool?
It's a hole!
Does that mean we're cool?
I'll find out!
I guess that makes sense.
You dig, you get a hole.
I'm not sure why I expected anything else.
That was my point.
No, it wasn't.
Jesse's got this, you guys.