even if you're intimidated maybe you could talk to them
they could teach you
some cool stuff about what they know yeah maybe
I want you to know your hard work inspires me every day I
am about to
enter my dome of concentration where I will be unreachable
for the foreseeable
future but I will emerge when I complete my latest and
greatest creation the
command block continue working continue building and
whichever person most
impresses me they shall be my protege
era of innovation and creativity Calvin throw the switch
Jesse we need to get there before she totally locks herself
in
so elegant trying to make a command block in there I don't
know Jesse that
sounds pretty risky you saw what happened when I were tried
to control a
command block excuse me mr. Calvin was it we need to speak
to elegant it's
I'm afraid that's quite impossible did you hear the speech
she's on lockdown
until she completes her next great invention I have a
message from Gabriel
okay elegant old friend I'm afraid I have many more things
to attend to than
answering all of your questions I must go better just take
this repeater disable
the stair controls we don't want any trouble makers
disturbing elegant guess
we'll need to get another repeater we need three stone two
redstone torches
and one pile of redstone dust to make one right