Not really.
Uh, I get it. A joke. Between friends.
That is so classic. You.
Don't worry. I'm going to help you because that's what
friends do.
Before we leave, I'm going to give my old friends a gift.
A gift of song.
What's happening?
Gary may seem scary, but he's a swell guy. Sally dilly
dallys.
Give her credit she tries. They might look the same to the
untrained eye.
But that's a lie. So I say...
Wait, is that...are you...
Soren.
Whoa.
You look...terrible.
Terribly handsome.
Hello, old friend.
We've been looking for you.
Look away.
You upset them. You altered their behavior.
Okay, let's go.
And their heads just keep on coming...
Huh. I wasn't expecting so many house guests.
There's no way I have enough seashells to take from them.
Wait till they have this one.
What are they doing with all those other house guests?
Your friends have been footprinted, not own.
All right, okay...
I have enough seashell subs for all of them.
How are we supposed to get out of here?
We need to come up with a plan.
And not our usual we'll come up with a plan when we have to-
Oh wait, now we have to kind of plan!