Are we there yet? No, no, no, we are not there yet.
Ooh, my rear end is profoundly sore.
It feels like we've been riding forever.
I am telling you, we cannot go to the Far Lands.
They're not just the edge of our world, but the limits of
our comprehension.
Oh, please, the Far Lands are a happy accident.
Nature's way of keeping life interesting.
No, no, no, they are perilous and unpredictable.
Hold on, back up. What exactly are the Far Lands?
Are you being serious?
The Far Lands lie at the very edge of all things, where
logic gives way to chaos.
They're a dangerous place to visit, and a ridiculous place
to construct a laboratory.
Just wait until you see it.
Do those two never stop arguing?
I don't know. I'm too hungry to care.
No kidding. I'm starving.
Maybe we should turn back?
This isn't the time. Swamps are too dangerous.
Guys, we can't turn back now, not after coming so far.
Fine, but I'm taking a break.
So am I.
We mustn't linger long. The Far Lands are just beyond this
swamp.
So this could be our last chance to find food?
I'll be back.
A witch's eye!
Ah!
We should steer clear of it.
Nothing good ever happens when witches are involved.
Look, a cake! That's enough to feed everyone.
It isn't worth it, Jesse.
Witches hate trespassers.
Is that a witch?
Jesse, we shouldn't be here. Witches are very strong.
And they know these swamps far better than I.
Probably in time.