Who likes explosions?
That's right, yeah you do.
That's why I'm standing up here today.
Well, you guys ready then?
Oh, yeah! This'll be a way easier target than Magnus.
Wait, what's going on?
Oh, well, that's not good.
Is that your wither storm?
How are we? What do we?
Okay, just a little farther.
Wow, someone really went bonkers with the defenses, huh?
Who goes there?
Oh, Jesse? Is that you?
No, it's not Jesse.
Jesse, you're not going to get away with this.
I'm going to get you.
Who goes there?
Oh, Jesse? Is that you?
Lukas, did you build all of this?
Well, yeah. I figured I would try and fortify the place,
you know?
Nice!
Quick, come on. You guys are never going to believe who
showed up while you were gone.
Gabriel!
Hello, everyone. It is good to see you.
He showed up not too long before you guys.
Magnus, my old friend.
You always were a tough cookie to keep down.
It's good to see you.
It's good to see you too, your meathead.
And it's especially good to see you, Jesse.
I fear that you might be the last face I ever saw.
Getting here was hard.