We need to find a way for me to use this.
Whoa, that is, without question, the coolest thing I have ever, ever seen.
Oh, and I brought you some armor, Axel.
Here.
Nice! I was feeling a little left out.
Guys, let's go kick some command block butt.
Does anyone see the command block?
We don't think it's exposed!
We need to get out of here!
Command block?
We don't think it's exposed!
We need to get more Endermen focused on the Winter Store!
How do you make Endermen focus? I can't even make myself focus.
We shouldn't be here. Not if this is going according to plan.
Soren? What are you doing?
I, uh, you know, I really enjoy meeting you all, but...
Soren!
Did Soren just run away?