I bet we can find him. I'm very curious to see it. I've
never actually seen it work before
All right, there's your light my light
That's new
There he is
Sorin had his fortress deep inside the mountains after the
order broke up. That's where he went to keep doing his
experiments
Look, he invited me there a couple times, but it always
seemed a little weird, right? It always seemed a little
weird
Then let's stop hanging around here and go get us some
super TNT
I
Bore is going to soren's we need to move
It's not too far we could probably make it on foot
Perfect. We can wait till tomorrow morning and travel with
a full day's sunlight
And is that thing catching up with us? I think I've had
enough with her store for one day
Thank you very much because getting caught out there in the
dark is so much better
Yeah, I don't want the with the storm catching up with us.
We should go now
Okay, everyone let's get moving
Jesse right? Oh, hello. We haven't had the chance to
acquaint ourselves properly
I hear that you saved your friend Petra from this wither
storm
Sounds like you're a pretty impressive individual. I'm just
doing my best to keep everyone safe. I can always
appreciate humility
I like you a slight tangent. What's the deal with your
friend Olivia?
I appreciate her enthusiasm, but she can be a little
Much sometimes
She's always very eager to jump in and help
Which is sweet, of course, though. Sometimes I wish she
would think a bit more before jumping in
Especially when she keeps getting in over her head