Yeah, but assuming I won, wouldn't I be stuck here then?
Nah, you're not as legendary as me.
Should be easy enough to throw another fighter.
Just give up the crown with way lower level grievers.
The trick is, don't become a legend.
But looking at you, I don't think...
Well, anyway.
Oh, this is gonna be good.
I'm actually excited about this.
But we gotta make sure it looks legit.
The Death Bowl has never seen the carnage that we're about
to create.
Uh, what's the Death Bowl?
This is the Death Bowl!
I love playing in the pool!
Welcome, ladies and gentle grievers, to the Death Bowl!
In one corner we have Magnus, your king of boob-tell!
Prepare to defend this title and crown!
Some tiny welcome to the Death Bowl.
The Grief Off to end all Grief Offs.
How do you want to fake this?
We'll start off small, then I'll throw some TNT at you.
Just let it graze you, then we'll call it a finish, alright?
Okay, something about TNT. Awesome!
And you! What name do you go by?
They call me...
The Amulet Holder!
You heard the name, folks.
Give a big Death Bowl welcome to the...
Amulet Holder!
Then let's begin!
Opponents will craft their own griefing towers,
which they will then use to grief each other.
The only rule is...
There are no rules!
No eye poking!
Other than that, go crazy!
Seriously.
Amulet Holder, pick your building material, and Magnus,
you...
Nah, I'm good. Brought my own supply.
Let the griefing begin!
Some stone...
Some...
Pink wall?
Eww!