He wasn't on the map.
Jesse, do you still have the amulet I gave you?
Of course.
Alright, there's your light, my light.
That's new.
There he is.
Sorin had his fortress deep inside the mountains.
After the order broke up, that's where he went to keep
doing his experiments.
Look, he invited me there a couple times, but it always
seemed a little...
Weird, right? It always seemed a little weird.
Then let's stop hanging around here and go get us some
super TNT.
Whoa.
Blue?
That's Ivor!
Ivor is going to Sorin's. We need to move.
It's not too far. We could probably make it on foot.
Perfect. We can wait till tomorrow morning and travel with
a full day's sunlight.
And is that thing catching up with us?
I think I've had enough witherstorm for one day. Thank you
very much.
Great, because getting caught out there in the dark is so
much better.
Hey, I don't want the witherstorm catching up with us. We
should go now.
Okay.
Okay, everyone, let's get moving.
Jesse, right?
Oh, hello.
We haven't had the chance to acquaint ourselves properly.
According to Gabriel, you saved him from this witherstorm.
Sounds like you're a pretty impressive individual.
I'm just doing my best to keep everyone safe.
I can always appreciate humility. I like you.
A slight tangent. What's the deal with your friend Olivia?
I appreciate her enthusiasm, but she can be a little...much
sometimes.
She's always very eager to jump in and help.
Which is sweet, of course, though sometimes I wish she
would think a bit more before jumping in.
Especially when she keeps getting in over her head.