Sure.
That's the best thing I've heard in years.
Admittedly, it's not a very high bar.
Don't worry. I'm going to help you, because that's what
friends do.
Before we leave, I'm going to give my old friends a gift.
A gift of song.
What's happening?
Gary may seem scary, but he's a swell guy.
Sally Dilly Dallys, give her credit she tries.
They might look the same to the untrained eye.
But that's a lie, so I say...
Wait, is that... are you...?
Soren.
Whoa.
Nice to meet you, Soren.
You look... terrible.
Look away!
You've upset them!
You've altered their behavior!
Okay, let's go.
And the hits just keep on coming.
Huh?
I wasn't expecting so many house guests.
There's no way I have enough seashell subs for all of them.
How are we supposed to get out of here?
We need to come up with a plan.
And not our usual
will-come-up-with-a-plan-when-we-have-to-oh-wait-now-we-have-to
kind of plan.
We need to come up with a plan.
And not our usual
will-come-up-with-a-plan-when-we-have-to-oh-wait-now-we-have-to
kind of plan.
Oh, wait, now we have to kind of plan!