Not really.
Uh, I get it. A joke. Between friends.
That is so classic. You.
Don't worry. I'm going to help you because that's what
friends do.
Before we leave, I'm going to give my old friends a gift.
A gift of song.
What's happening?
Gary may seem scary, but he's a swell guy. Sally dilly
dallys.
Give her credit she tries. They might look the same to the
untrained eye.
But that's a lie. So I say...
Wait, is that...are you...
Soren.
Whoa.
Nice to meet you, Soren.
You look...terrible.
Look away!
You upset them. You altered their behavior.
Okay, let's go.
And the hits just keep on coming.
Huh? I wasn't expecting so many house gases.
There's no way I have enough seashell subs for all of them.
How are we supposed to get out of here?
We need to come up with a plan.
And not our usual will come up with a plan when we have
to...
Oh, wait, now we have to kind of plan.