I need six blocks to finish that shape in Soren's
instructions.
This guy's got the only block around.
Let's take a little look at the instructions.
Nothing I can't handle.
False evidence of Enderman intelligence accomplished.
Nothing to see here guys. Just walk away.
I am sorry about this but it has to look real.
I don't think it'll bruise.
These suits were built with durability in mind.
You must be Soren.
I am, but must I be?
Why did you hit me?
There were strategic reasons and a personal one.
You are trespassing after all.
You hit me hard in the face.
You upset the Enderman and I got you to safety.
By the way, as far as introductions are concerned,
this is not going very well.
We're in danger.
What else is new?
Whatever your issue is, whatever your problem,
it has occurred before and has been solved before.
Even so, what do you need me for?
I've gone out of my way to avoid these types of problems.
I don't even remember what it looks like up there.