Olivia's one of my best friends. She's smart. She always
has a plan. Oh wow interesting
So why didn't you listen to her plan to come and recruit me
I?
Figured that we needed firepower and no one knows
destruction better than Magnus
The man does know how to blow things up with reckless
abandon. That's for sure
I'll do my best to not let it hurt my feelings
Joke that was a joke
Guys
I told you who's gonna catch up with us
Really weren't kidding
Not again
And hash all that out later come on we got to get out of
here not again
Sores isn't much farther we can make it
I
Am getting very tired of this weather storm agreed place
has gotta be just ahead come on
I
Soaring really live down here so far from anyone
Enchanting isn't it?
Oh
Yeah, and I'm really not feeling those columns
Just don't fall okay
That is very very deep
I
Was more of a drop than I was expecting
There are so many I didn't think they ever came in groups
that big
No kidding it's like an Enderman party I heard your voice
and thought I would come down to hell
You