I don't know if you caught this but she's like your biggest
fan. You probably just make her nervous
That's an excellent point hadn't thought about that
Seems like you respect her a lot
Why didn't you listen to her plan to come and recruit me?
I figure that we needed firepower and no one knows
destruction better than Magnus
The man does know how to blow things up with reckless
abandon. That's for sure
I'll do my best to not let it hurt my feelings
Ha joke that was a joke
Guys
I told you we're gonna catch up with this
Really weren't kidding
Again
I saw that out later. Come on. We got to get out of here
Not again, so it isn't much farther. We can make it
I
Am getting very tired of this weather storm agreed
Soren really live down here so far from anyone enchanting
isn't it?
Yeah, and I'm really not feeling those columns
Oh
That is deep that is very very deep
It was more of a drop than I was expecting
Enderman there are so many I didn't think they ever came in
groups that big
No kidding it's like an enderman party I heard your voice
and thought I would come down to hell