Eligard, come on. I know this isn't how the plan was
supposed to go, but it's going to be fine. Ha!
Fine.
Uh, people, can we please focus on the bigger picture? We
have a very hungry wither storm in the process of turning
the whole world into its dinner.
It was terrifying. It came out of nowhere and just
destroyed... everything.
Little too scary for you, Ellie? Couldn't just think it
away?
You weren't there, Magnus. I'm telling you, this thing was
like nothing I've ever seen.
Why? Because it's never come inside one of your little
workshops?
Would you two stop fighting?
Whoa! Yikes.
Jesse speaks the truth. We must find a way to defeat that
monstrosity.
Well, I don't know if you've had the chance to poke around
this old dump yet, but it's pretty much stripped bare.
It would take a mountain of TNT to kill that thing.
I hate to say it, but you have a point.
Can we start crafting some, then?
I don't think we got that kind of time.
If only Sorin were here, he might have something we could
use.
Oh, Ellie. Not this again.
There's something stronger than TNT?
Sorin had a kind of super TNT.
Stronger and more explosive than anything else in the world.
The Formidabomb.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I've heard all about the F-bomb before.
Well, the Formidabomb sounds perfect. We should go get it
now.
Well, there's a little problem there.
We don't know where Sorin is.
But you found us. Do you know where he is?
Our map could locate him.
Unless he's in the nether or the end.
But it's worth a shot.