Elegant, I'm sorry, but no, I can't let you do this. Please
we have to go go
This seems terribly short-sighted. I had thought you were
the brains of your little trio
This could be the greatest invention the world has ever
seen it could change everything
You'll understand when you see it. I promise there's no time
While I'm very glad you want my assistance and trust me I
won't faint I'm still not sure
Oh my surface
So so sorry we should get to the portal now as soon as
possible
Oh
Okay, just a little farther, wow, that's certainly
impressive Wow
There oh Jesse is that you Lukas did you build all of this
Quick come on. You guys are never gonna believe who showed
up while you were gone
Petra hey guys, how's it going?
I'm so glad you're okay Petra. Yeah, I'm pretty stoked
about it myself
It's really good to see you Jesse back there in Gabriel's
bunker. I got pretty dicey
You