Hey, come on Magnus is awesome. He's gonna help us stop
this weather storm. You really believe that?
Wow
It was kind of crazy. Actually, I went to redstonia and
there were all these incredible engineers and inventors
It was a little intimidating actually, but Ellegaard's made me
her protege. Well assistant for now
She might have well
Embarrassed herself a tiny bit
Yeah, but after I pled my case she agreed to take me on as
her assistant and come back to help
Not bad, right? Well, I'm the king of boon town
Very impressive
Ray it's Ellie and here I was just starting to enjoy myself
Hello, Magnus your voice is exactly as pleasant as I
remember which is to say not at all
My feelings is that the same way you're gonna use to save
the world
Why you're here to tell me how to do it better? Oh, I would
never dream of doing that
Unlike you I actually do things instead of just talking
about them. Hey, that's Ellegaard. You're talking to show her
some respect
Wow, you finally found yourself a live one. Hey
Your little devotees are usually a little more on the
brookish side leave her out of this magnus
This is between the two of us
Oh, I started ignoring her ages ago