Yeah, and you two are going to have to get along, okay?
We didn't even know you were gonna be here.
If he's nice, I'll be nice too.
It was kind of crazy, actually.
I went to Redstonia,
and there were all these incredible engineers and inventors.
It was a little intimidating, actually.
But Ellegaard's made me her protege.
Well, assistant for now.
She might have, well, embarrassed herself a tiny bit.
Yeah.
But after I pled my case,
she agreed to take me on as her assistant and come back to
help.
Not bad, right?
Well, I'm the king of Boon Town.
Very impressive.
Hooray! It's Ellie.
And here I was just starting to enjoy myself.
Hello, Magnus.
Your voice is exactly as pleasant as I remember.
Which is to say, not at all.
Oh, my feelings.
Is that the same way you're gonna use to save the world?
Why? You here to tell me how to do it better?
I would never dream of doing that.
Unlike you, I actually do things instead of just talking
about them.
Hey, that's Ellegaardd you're talking to.
Show her some respect.
Wow, you finally found yourself a live one.
Hey.
Your little devotees are usually a little more on the
bookish side.
Leave her out of this, Magnus.
This is between the two of us.
Oh, I started ignoring her ages ago.