Soren come back here dude, what a chicken
Jesse you can handle things out here, right? What I can't let him get himself killed
Just get to the command block and destroy it. Sorry
So much for the mighty order of the stone
It doesn't matter. We have work to do
We need to get those Enderman to attack it
Be Jesse that's it
epoxy
Yes, they're falling for it.
Jesse, look!
It's working!
That hose big enough to get inside of.
Now we just need to find you a way up.
Or build you a way up.
That's it!
Everyone, empty your pockets!
Let's see...
I've got redstone and cobblestone from Iowars Armory.
I've got some TNT from Boomtown.
I've got pistons, repeaters, some wool, and some
Oh, and I still have that minecart.
That's got to be enough to make something, right?
I mean, if we use the TNT on, say...
The minecart?
Or those pistons.
And we do have all that cobblestone.
Maybe we could build a ramp?
Or even go straight up vertically.
Or find a way to use redstone.
We're close to an answer.
I can feel it!