Soren, you coward, I can't believe you!
I can.
Jesse, you can handle things out here, right?
What?
I can't let him get himself killed!
Just get to the command block and destroy it!
Soren!
So much for the mighty Order of the Stone.
Doesn't matter. We have work to do.
We need to get those Endermen to attack it!
Jesse, that's it!
Make them chase you into the tractor beam!
How do you like that? Purple-eyed freak?
Yes, they're falling for it!
Jesse, look! It's working!
That hole's big enough to get inside of.
Now we just need to find you a way up.
Or build you a way up.
That's it!
Everyone, empty your pockets!
Let's see...
I've got redstone and cobblestone from Iowar's army.
I've got some TNT from Boomtown.
I've got pistons, repeaters, some wool,
some leftover wood, and some wood for the fire.
I've got some TNT from Boomtown.
I've got some TNT from Boomtown,
someías, somecribers, somewooll, someleftoverslime.
some