We know for a fact the wither storm will follow the ambulance. So if we take the amulet back to your fortress where the endermen are
We'll lead them straight into a massive trap. Just one problem. You're forgetting about the command block
Yes
It's clear now that no weapon can destroy it
Not even a formidable. Yes. Well, I created a fail safe. What kind of fail safe exactly?
an enchanting book
One that contains the power of the command block itself
Use it to enchant a weapon and you'll be able to smash the command block to bits
forever
Yes
Yes, that's it
Ivor?
Ivor? Well, I'll be
It is you
The pleasure as always, Eligard
It just keeps coming for us
Guys, there's a reason it's been following us. Ivor says it's because of the amulet that Gabriel the point is we need to get moving
We aren't safe. Not as long as we have that amulet. I'll take it
I'll keep the wither storms busy. You guys do what you got to do. Axel. Thank you. You just go make that super weapon
I'll meet you back at soren's fortress. Well, axel shouldn't have to do this alone
I'm going with him. I appreciate that
Well, i'm going with jesse. I pledge to help and that's what I must do
Everyone take good care of yourselves
Hey jesse, let's try our handshake again just once for the road