Let's break that fountain.
Back in the maze, when we fell into the water, the Enderman
didn't follow us.
Well, naturally. Enderman hate water.
Oh, if we could force the fountain to overflow somehow...
Jesse, you still have the Enderman suit.
Put that on, and you'll be able to safely reach the
fountain.
Ugh. Just when I thought I'd never have to smell this thing
again.
Good luck, dude.
We'll, uh, all watch from here, then.
Where it's safe.
Phew.
Try not to die.
Okay, everybody, let's go!
What's the holdup?
Ugh.
They're everywhere.
How are we supposed to get through this?
I mean, physically and psychologically.
Say we somehow make it.
You can't see how this won't become a reoccurring nightmare.
I mean, we're not going to make it.