They can't hurt us if we don't look at them, right?
So we just keep our eyes closed.
Forever.
One constant about endermen is that they hate water.
If we can force that fountain to overflow somehow.
Jesse, you still have the endermen suit.
Put that on and you'll be able to safely reach the fountain.
Yuck.
Just when I thought I'd never have to smell this thing
again.
Good luck, dude.
We'll, uh, all watch from here then.
Where it's safe.
Phew.
Try not to die.
Hey.
Ah!
Okay, everybody, let's go.
What's the holdup?
They're everywhere.
How are we supposed to get through this?
I mean, physically and psychologically.
Say we somehow make it.
I can't see how this won't become a reoccurring nightmare.