Guys, check it out. We use the pistons and some redstone to
build a flying machine.
Then when I'm high enough, I ignite the TNT and blast
myself into the wither storm.
Haha, heck yeah! I love that idea.
So what are we waiting for? Let's hurry up and...
Oh, look out!
Petra!
Axel!
Gah!
I can't hold on!
I got you!
Lukas! You're here!
Ocelots, distract that wither storm!
Hey you! Get a load of this!
Lukas, thank you. Anything for a friend.
Now let's hurry up and build this thing.
Okay, it's finished.
Quick, climb on!
Jesse, you can do this. I know you can.
We all do.
Thanks guys. It means a lot.
Now go to the walls that command block.
Reuben, this is no place for a...
Wow...
Gah!
There it is.
We meet again, command block.
Now it's time to destroy you.
Reuben, I think we made it angry.
It's doing everything it can to protect the command block.
I'm going to get you, Reuben.
Awesome weapon, don't fail me now.
Holy moly!
This thing will die!
Gah!
Reuben, whatever happens, we have to destroy that command
block.
Wait a second, I know exactly how to get up there.
The tractor beam!
Hey, you!
I'm going to get you, Reuben.