I need you to be a hero.
Hmm, I see.
And what do you think a hero would do in this situation?
A hero would give me his vermitabom.
There's a wither storm on the loose and it's eating the
world.
Ah, I see. You misspoke.
You don't need me. You need my stuff.
I've found that when you give people what they want,
they turn on you.
Who turned on you?
All of them.
It's why I prefer Endermen.
They always do what you expect, almost to a fault.
I have the amulet.
What?
Gabriel gave it to me.
Gabriel?
Gabriel asked me to reassemble the Order of the Stone.
The Order of the Stone?
They asked for me?
Gabriel is your friend.
Hmm, I don't know.
Does he ever talk about me?
Uh, sure.
What kinds of things do they say?
That you were missed.
Really?
Maybe it was more missing.
You have to read between the lines.
Yes, yes you do.
But what about you?
Are you my friend?
As long as we're on the subject?
Not to put you on the spot.
Hey.