Got to help them.
What about the ambulance?
You get it.
I'm coming, Ruben!
Get away from my pig!
Got it!
Jesse's behind you.
Get out!
No!
Ah!
Is everyone okay? We all good?
Well, I am definitely not thirsty anymore.
We're fine.
No, no, don't worry. I'm totally fine.
Why?
Oh, I'm sorry.
No!
I knew you'd come for us. I just knew it.
Ruben has dows.
I owe you.
I'm just glad you're okay.
Both of you.
Thanks, Jesse.
There's something different about you, Jesse.
You're...
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
This is where all the loot gets sorted, right?
That's exactly what it is.
See that? Things are starting to turn around.
It looks like it's still working.
I'll just be real careful with it.
Keep it safe.
You