And how is that any better? You reveal their lies at the
expense of the world itself?
Look, my wither plan obviously backfired.
You think?
I didn't know we'd end up with three of those things
tearing the world apart!
Which brings us back to why we're here. We need to destroy
that command block. Like now!
Jesse's right. Destroying the command block is all that
matters anymore.
How ironic that the best thing the command block gave us
was the very means to destroy it.
So the enchanting book, what do we do with it?
You craft a weapon, then put it on an anvil. Follow me,
I'll show you.
Ivor? I'm sorry. About everything.
Yes, well, it doesn't matter now.
Grab some ingredients and craft a weapon. I'll show you how
to enchant it.
Sweet.
Let's see, there's a bunch of crafting stuff and...
Diamond score!