You’re gonna have to make a run for it, okay?
I’ll meet up with you back in town, I promise!
Get outta here! Now!
Get off of me!
Come on, let’s get out of the open.
I wanna show you something.
Not this isn’t a cool, dimly lit tunnel, but… how far away is this thing you want to show me?
Careful, Jesse. You don’t want to get a reputation as a wimp.
This isn’t my first time in a cave, Petra.
Yeah, but have you ever seen… A witherskull?
Woah!
Fresh from the Nether.
That’s insane, Petra. You could’ve gotten yourself killed.
Don’t worry so much. I can handle myself.
There’s this guy I’m meeting up with at Endercon… he’s gonna trade me a diamond for it.
Why didn’t he just go get the skull himself?
He’s not the kind of guy who has time to do something like that!
What kind of guy is he, then?
The kind who understands the value of hard work.
Wow.
Wow… what?
In a single day, you went to the Nether, you killed a Wither skeleton…
I mean, I DID build a super cool statue, but still. It’s pretty sweet being you, huh?
You know… you could come with me.
I mean, if you’re too nervous, I totally get it.