Too many of them, buddy!
Don't leave that spot no matter what.
You hear me?
I got you!
Get away from him!
No, he got you!
Jesus!
Come on, let's get out of the open.
Hello!
I wanna show you something.
Not that this isn't a really cool dimly lit tunnel, but...
How far away is this thing you wanna show me?
Careful, Jesse. You don't wanna get a reputation as a wimp.
This isn't my first time in a cave, Petra.
Yeah, but have you ever seen...
...a wither skull?
Whoa!
Fresh from the nether.
That's insane, Petra! You could've gotten yourself killed.
Don't worry so much. I can handle myself.
There's this guy I'm meeting up with at Endercon.
He's gonna trade me a diamond for it.
Why didn't he just go get the skull himself?
He's not the kind of guy who has time to do something like
that.
What kind of guy is he, then?
The kind who understands the value of hard work.
Wow.
Wow what?
In a single day, you went to the nether, you killed a
wither skeleton.
I mean, I did build a super cool statue, but still...
...it's pretty sweet being you, huh?
You know, you could come with me.
I mean, if you're too nervous, I totally get it.
But I wouldn't mind a little backup.