All I've got is this sword.
Oh, that's very nice.
With this, I could cut my butchering time in half.
Nice doing business with you.
Come on, Ruben.
I'm sorry, Ruben. I was so busy trying to find that creepy
dude, I didn't notice.
Remember that thing I had to go do with Petra? Long story
short, we met up with this guy. He cheated me and Petra on
a deal, and now we're trying to track him down. You in?
Oh, I'm in. Alright.
Any sign of him?
I thought I saw him earlier, but it was just a false alarm.
Wait, there he is! Looks like he's heading towards the hall.
We're gonna have to get past that usher to follow him.
Let's go!
So, yeah, hey.
What would it take to get us inside tonight?
Uh, tickets?
This might sound crazy, but we're actually on an important
mission.
I hope your mission came with tickets to the show, cause I
mean, otherwise...
Chicken! Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!
It's gone. You're totally fine. You were totally cool doing
it.
We have to do something. Like what? This show has been sold
out for ages.
We need a distraction.
A lot of chickens running around might be a distraction.
Shoo! Shoo! Get out of here!
Usher is afraid of chickens.
What would you say if I told you I want to break this guy's
chicken machine to create the mother of all distractions?
But you have to break that pane of glass. How are you gonna
reach it?
Let's look around. There has to be something we can do.
I'm not sure what to do.