Now, I don't want to alarm you, Olivia, but...
I have no idea what I'm looking at here.
I don't know what it is yet either.
That's why I'm studying it.
Come on, let's keep moving.
Seems like this place has really blown you away.
You're not kidding.
This is like everything I've ever dreamed of.
Entering Eligard's laboratory, seeing her right there...
She'll ask me to be her apprentice, and the next thing you
know we'll be changing the world together.
Let's just try to save the world first.
Whoa! Hi! Hey! Didn't see you sneaking up on me. Guess
that's the point.
Don't touch anything in here, okay? It's all supremely
fragile and genius.
Did Calvin send you? You my new assistants?
New assistants with a stupidly adorable pig, that is!
Jessie! She thinks we're her new assistants!
This is so exciting!