I'll take Gabriel.
Then I've got Petra.
Hold on, this might be a bumpy ride.
Come on, horses!
Whatever you do, don't look back.
Ah!
I look.
Watch out!
It's gaining on us!
Pick up the pace or we're all done for!
First time on a horse here!
I can't find the horsemanship, Jesse.
Is that what this is called?
Jesse, look out!
I'm going to get you!
Am I seeing Enderman attack the weatherstorm?
Enderman move locks, it's what they do!
There! We can get him!
Ah!
We can be rich.
Guys, come on!
We've got to build a new one, like right now.
Come on, faster!
Yee-haw!
Woo!
I saw you screaming in my ear.
Sorry.
We made it!
We actually freaking made it!
Hey, how are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I don't really feel like myself.
I still can't believe you're even alive.
Do you not recognize us?
I'm Axel.
This is Olivia.
We've been friends for a really long time.