Cool mask!
It IS, isn’t it?
Yeah! Very convincing!
Hahaha!
The look on your faces!
Did you bring the fireworks?
Of course I did!
I even brought something for the little guy!
Nice!
You brought Reuben a disguise?
Umm… We’re going to a convention!
SOMEBODY’s gotta wear a costume!
He looks AWESOME!
It only took me like a million hours to build it.
Alright. Alright.
You definitely brought the fireworks, right?
Yeeesss! I’m ready! Waiting on you guys!
If he was REALLY your best friend, you wouldn’t let him go outside dressed like that…
The only thing more dangerous than putting a costume ON a pig, is trying to take OFF.
Hurry up and grab your stuff!
We’ll meet you downstairs, okay?
Okay!
Hmmm… flint and steel, not too shabby…
One of these days, we’re gonna WIN, the Endercon building competition.
And WHEN do, people will look up at us and say...
“Hey, there goes Jesse and Reuben, winners of the Endercon building competition!”
They really should change the name…
Give me a dragon roar, Reuben!
That’ll do, Reuben! That’ll do!
That’s everything.
Let’s roll!
Yeah, dude! “Roll”!
I heard a pretty juicy rumor about the building competition, but you guys have to PROMISE not say anything.
Okay.
ALSO it’s in two parts! Each part more exciting than the last!
Spit it out, Axel!
Part one. The special guest of this year’s Endercon is none other than Gabriel The Warrior him-freaking-self.
WOAH! What’s part two?!
Part TWO. According to my sources, the winner of the building competition is gonna get to meet him.