That wasn't funny, Axel.
I brought you good times and now I'm being punished for it?
You scared us half to death.
Did you bring the fireworks?
Of course I did.
I even brought something for the little guy.
Nice.
You brought Reuben a disguise?
Um, we're going to a convention.
Somebody's gotta wear a costume.
He looks awesome.
It only took me like a million hours to build it.
Alright, alright.
You definitely brought the fireworks, right?
Yes, I'm ready.
Waiting on you guys.
If he was really your best friend, you wouldn't let him go
outside dressed like that.
The only thing more dangerous than putting a costume on a
pig is trying to take it off.
Hurry up and grab your stuff.
We'll meet you downstairs, okay?
Okay.
Hmm, flint and steel, not too shabby.
One of these days, we're going to win the Endercon Building
Competition.
And when we do, people will look at us and say,
hey, there goes Jesse and Reuben, winners of the Endercon
Building Competition.
They really should change the name.
Give me a dragon roar, Reuben.
That'll do, Reuben.
That'll do.
That's everything.
Let's roll.
Yeah, dude.
Roll.
Let's go.
I heard a pretty juicy rumor about the building competition,
but you guys have to promise not to say anything.
Okay.
Also, it's in two parts, each part more exciting than the
last.
Spit it out, Axel.
Part one, the special guest at this year's Endercon
is none other than Gabriel the Warrior, him freaking self.
Whoa, what's part two?
Part two, according to my sources,
the winner of the building competition is going to get to
meet him.
It doesn't mean anything if we lose.
But if we win, oh, man, this would make up for all the
losing.