We politely ask for what's our.
Short, sweet and to the point. Not bad.
You ready?
Ready.
You see anything?
He must have gone out another way.
What is all this?
Looks like it used to be the basement. Weird place to have a hideout.
I bet you anything I'll find my Wither skull here.
And if we find anything else cool to steal along the way, so be it, right?
Axel -- that's not what we're here to do.
I said we should ask politely, Axel.
Yeah, but if the guy's not here, we can't ask. So I say, we take!
Let's focus on finding the skull -- not stealing.
Nobody ever lets me have any fun.
We let you hang out with us.
The faster we find what we're looking for, the faster we can get the heck out of here.
Oh, hello.
Too heavy. And too soft.
But super flashy.
You're keeping it? But I thought that it was too soft, too heavy.
Eh, it still might come in handy.
And it IS super flashy.
Hey, you still have that one stone sword, right?
Yep!
Find anything?
I wanna steal that. And that. I just wanna touch that.
Oooooh, take a look a this!
You're not gonna believe me, but I swear I had a dream about this.