Why would you do that? You lied, even to your closest
friends!
All I can say is...
I was a fool.
So you finally admit it.
Soren, how could you?
Ivor, how long have you guys been standing there?
Long enough that they heard the whole thing.
So we're liars. All of us.
You didn't think you could keep it secret forever, did you,
Soren?
Is this why you left the Order? Because Soren lied?
Because they all did.
Soren, Gabriel, Magnus, Eligard, they agreed to keep this a
secret.
And you? You agreed to stay quiet too, in exchange for all
of our treasures.
I've technically never told anybody.
So this whole thing, the wither you unleashed, it's all
been to teach the Order a lesson?
To teach the world a lesson! To show you who the Order
really are!
Liars, cowards! And now, they know!
Yes. I suppose they do.