Let's see what this sucker does.
A secret passageway.
Why would you build a secret passage in a house that nobody
ever visits?
More like why wouldn't you?
Secret passageways are cool.
Good point.
Are you guys okay?
We're fine, but the lever isn't working anymore. Stay
there. We'll head down and see what we can find
What is all this?
Incredible. He's gathered them all in one place.
Gathered what exactly?
The treasures of the Order of the Stone.
The stories I could tell about these dusty old things.
You know, I often give up on my family.
You know, I often give Ivor a hard time, but for all his
complaining, his time with the Order clearly meant a great
deal to him.
Yeah, I guess so. Anyway, let's go get that enchanting book.
By the stars, the Ender Dragon. With replica ender crystals
in all.
Wow, I always wondered what it looked like.
Hmm, no way out.
It's obviously some kind of puzzle.
Sorin, what's this thing supposed to be?
It appears to be an homage to our battle with the Ender
Dragon.
Despite its name, it's still a treasure.
It appears to be an homage to our battle with the Ender
Dragon.
Despite its anger, Ivor never stopped being fond of us.
He was a big part of our team after all.
He knows his days in the Order were his finest.