We deserve a victory party. Who's in?
I like all kinds of parties, but especially ones where I
get to celebrate winning.
About time we'll be the Guest of Honor at something.
Hey, Jesse, it's time to go see about that... thing.
Oh, right, the thing.
Subtle.
Yeah?
It has a punch to the face. Axel and I are gonna head into
Endercon anyway. See you in there?
I heard somebody saying there's free cake by the map booth.
Hurry. We're supposed to meet in the alley over there.
Dark, dark, very dark in here.
That's weird. He said the dark, creepy alley close to the
gates, but he's not here. Maybe he's late.
Are you sure this is the dark, creepy alley he meant?
Hmm. I was.
Is? Okay, new plan. You stay here, just in case this is the
spot he meant, and I'll look around.
Okay, I'll hold down the fort.
Thanks, Jesse. I'll be back before you know it. If he shows
up while I'm gone, just stall for me.
And just who are you?
I'm waiting.
Answer me.