I'm proud of you guys. Oh shucks. Don't make me blush
Seriously, don't hey Jesse. It's time to go see about that
thing
Oh, right the thing subtle. Yeah as a punch to the face
Axel and I were gonna head into Ender Khan anyway, see you
in there. I heard somebody saying there's free cake by the
map booth
Hurry we're supposed to meet in the alley over there
Dark dark very dark in here
That's weird. He said the dark creepy alley close to the
gates, but he's not here
Maybe he's late. Are you sure this is the dark creepy alley
he meant?
Hmm. I was
Okay, new plan you stay here just in case this is this body
meant and I'll look around
Okay, I'll hold down the fort thanks Jesse, I'll be back
before you know it if he shows up while I'm gone just stall
for me
And just who are you
I'm waiting
I
Answer me