The Witherstorms are already chasing us. If we just get
them to chase us to your fortress again...
They'll be caught between a rock and a hard place!
Just one problem. You're forgetting about the command block!
Ugh... yes. It's clear now that no weapon can destroy it.
Not even a Formita Bomb.
Yes, well, I created a failsafe.
What kind of failsafe, exactly?
An enchanting book! One that contains the power of the
command block itself.
Use it to enchant a weapon, and you'll be able to smash the
command block to bits. Forever!
Yes. Yes, that's it!
Ivor? Well, I'll be. It is you.
A pleasure, as always, Ellegaardd. It just keeps coming for us.
Guys, there's a reason it's been following us. Ivor says
it's because of the amulet that Gabriel...
The point is, we need to get moving. We aren't safe. Not as
long as we have that amulet.
I'll take it. I'll keep the Witherstorms busy. You guys do
what you gotta do.
Axel, thank you.
You just go make that super weapon. I'll meet you back at
Soren's fortress.
Well, Axel shouldn't have to do this alone. I'm going with
him.
I appreciate that.
Well, I wanna go with Jesse. That feels like where I belong.
Everyone, take good care of yourselves.
Hey, Jesse, let's try our handshake again, just once for
the road.