We know for a fact that Witherstorm will follow the Amulet.
So if we take the Amulet back to your fortress where the Endermen are...
We'll lead them straight into a massive trap!
Just one problem. You're forgetting about the Command Block.
Ugh, yes. It's clear now that no weapon can destroy it. Not even a Formita Bomb.
Yes, well, I created a failsafe.
What kind of failsafe, exactly?
An enchanting book. One that contains the power of the Command Block itself.
Use it to enchant a weapon, and you'll be able to smash the Command Block to bits. Forever!
Yes. Yes, that's it!
Ivar? Well, I'll be. It is you.
A pleasure, as always, Elagard. It just keeps coming for us.
Guys, there's a reason it's been following us. Ivar says it's because of the Amulet that Gabriel...
The point is, we need to get moving.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ivar says it's because of the Amulet that Gabriel...
The point is, we need to get moving. We aren't safe. Not as long as we have that Amulet.
I'll take it. I'll keep the Witherstorms busy. You guys do what you gotta do.
Axel, thank you.
You just go make that super weapon. I'll meet you back at Soren's Fortress.
Well, Axel shouldn't have to do this alone. I'm going with him.
I appreciate that.
Well, I want to go with Jesse. That feels like where I belong.
Everyone, take good care of yourselves.
Hey, Jesse. Let's try our handshake again, just once for the road.
You