Okay, we're all set to go again.
Time to move, buddy.
Let's go.
Hitting the path of trust.
Now.
I never doubted you for a second, but that was incredible.
Maybe we have a chance of getting to Ellegaardd after all.
Look, there's the sign.
Redstonia.
Redstonia, here we come.
They're about to meet the greatest redstone builders in the
world.
Wow.
Who would have thought that someday I'd really get to visit
Redstonia, Ellegaardd's capital city of engineering.
Incredible.
Do you think Ellegaardd will be willing, you know, to help us?
Have you seen all these inventions?
These inventors are all incredible.
I might know Redstone where we come from, but these people
are the real deal, Jesse.
I mean, I don't even know how they're making some of these
things.
That's rare for me.