Olivia's one of my best friends. She's smart and she always
has a plan. Oh wow interesting
So why didn't you listen to her plan to come and recruit me
I?
Figured that we needed firepower and no one knows
destruction better than Magnus
The man does know how to blow things up with reckless
abandon. That's for sure
I'll do my best to not let it hurt my feelings
Joke that was a joke
Guys
I told you
Really weren't kidding
How can it find me again
Come on we got to get out of here this creature never stop
so it isn't much farther we can make it
I
Am getting very tired of this weather storm agreed
Soren really live down here, it's so far from anyone
enchanting isn't it
Oh
Yeah, and I'm really not feeling those columns
Just don't fall okay
Oh that is deep that is very very deep
We've got
Oh
It was more of a drop than I was expecting
Enderman there were so many I didn't think they ever came
in groups that big
No kidding it's like an Enderman party. I heard your voice
and thought I would come down to hell
You