I don't know if you caught this but she's like your biggest
fan. You probably just make her nervous
That's an excellent point hadn't thought about that
Seems like you respect her a lot
Why didn't you listen to her plan to come and recruit me?
I figure that we needed firepower and no one knows
destruction better than Magnus
The man does know how to blow things up with reckless
abandon. That's for sure
I'll do my best to not let it hurt my feelings
Ha joke that was a joke
Guys
I told you I was gonna catch up with this
You really weren't kidding
How could it find me again
I can hash all that out later. Come on. We got to get out
of here. This creature never stopped
Soren's isn't much farther. We can make it
I
Am getting very tired of this weather storm agreed place
Soren really lived down here it's so far from anyone
Enchanting isn't it?
Yeah, and I'm really not feeling those columns
Columns
Don't fall okay. Oh that is deep that is very very deep
Hang on
It was more of a drop than I was expecting
So many I didn't think they ever came in groups that big
No kidding it's like an enderman party. I heard your voice
and thought I would come down to hell