The thief is mine, you take the one with the fishing pole.
Got it.
Sorry guys, but I've been trying to find Magnus for way too
long, so he'll just stop me now.
Oh, later dingus!
Only one way out of a pit.
Axel!
Jess, there you are. So I totally courted that fisher dude
and they were all scared and scared.
Where is the amulet?
Stop right there!
How about no?
This bridge will take forever to punch through.
Luckily I think I found us a punch-free entrance.
Okay, little amulet. Show me the way.
Of course not sure what I'll do when I get there, but
that's future Nohr's problem.
I bet future Nohr is very successful.
Uh-oh!
Oh my god!
Ha! Nice! What did I tell you about teamwork?
What? But I'm the one who said we should work together.
No you didn't! Give me that!
Give it back!
Got it! I actually got it!
Quick! Flush him out!
Oh my god!
Axel Magnus is somewhere in that building above us. He's
gotta be close!
Then quick! Toss me the amulet!
You're surrounded by creepers and they're gonna tear you
apart!
Well...
Jesse, we need to move now!