I’m proud of you guys.
Aw, shucks.
Don’t make me blush. Seriously. Don’t.
Hey, Jesse. It’s time to go see about that -- thing.
Oh, right, The “thing”.
Subtle.
Yeah?
As a punch to the face. Axel and I were gonna head into Endercon anyway -- see you in there?
I heard somebody saying there’s free cake by the map booth.
Hurry -- we’re supposed to meet in the alley over there.
Dark. Dark. Very dark in here.
That's weird -- he said the dark, creepy alleyway close to the gates, but he's not here. Maybe he's late.
Are you sure THIS is the dark, creepy alleyway he was talking about?
Hmm. I WAS.
Okay, new plan. You stay here just in case this IS the spot he meant, and I'll look around.
Okay, I'll hold down the fort.
Thanks, Jesse. I'll be back before you know it. If he shows up while I'm gone, just stall for me.
And just who are YOU?