I'm sorry.
I don't mean to worry you.
I've just got something I want to discuss with you in
private.
But let's split up.
I feel bad about ditching everyone else, but I just wanted
to talk to you about this alone.
Hey, whatever it is, I trust you.
You can tell me.
Thanks for being so understanding.
You got me away from the wither storm, but I'm worried that
I didn't get away soon enough.
What?
What is that?
What's wrong with your arm?
Do you know what wither is?
The wither?
Of course, we've been...
No, Jesse.
Just wither, or wither sickness, I guess.
And I feel like it's just gonna keep getting worse.
Well, we're gonna go back and tell the others we can get
help.
You can't tell anyone about this.
Grab my hand.
I'll pull you up.
Jesse, I just couldn't...
I'm sorry.
Jesse?
Are you okay?