It could work.
We're gonna die.
Got it!
Hit it, hit it, hit it!
Yes!
Time to move, buddy. Let's go.
You were awesome, Jesse. With that gasp and chasing the
mine cart.
That is like the perfect warm-up for when we get to
Boomtown.
Boomtown? Yeah! Boomtown!
This is it.
I think I'm gonna hold off on the whole going first thing
for a while, Jesse.
How about you take this one?
Just be careful, okay?
On the step.
Let's go!
Whoa! You see that? Utter chaos, man.
You'll lose his mind, friggin'.
You'll have to catch me first, Bandlefoot.
Whoa! I hope they're okay.
And if they're not, at least they died doing what they
loved.
Well, here you have it, Jesse. Boomtown in all its glory.
What do you think?
Wow, Boomtown sure does keep you on your toes. Exciting
stuff, huh?
Yeah, yeah, now you're getting it.
Dude, it's freaking glowing.
Dude, I think you're on to something there.