Heroes can come from unlikely beginnings.
And broken friendships can lead to dark rivalry.
When the world is in danger, fate calls on the ordinary to
do extraordinary deeds.
But the question remains, will it be enough to save the
world?
Woohoo!
Aw, come on, Jesse. You're not even having a little fun?
I mean, I am!
Just don't lose track of why we're here, okay?
If we don't get the order back together, the Witherstorm is
going to eat everything.
That means we need to get to Magnus as soon as freaking
possible.
You know what? You're right.
We're gonna find Magnus, bring him back, and he'll totally
know how to blow that thing sky high.
Uh, dude!
Whoa!
Ow, ow, ow!
The minecart!
Why does it hate us so much?
Hurry! Use something on that ghast!
Okay, think fast, Jesse. What to choose?