Time to move, buddy.
Let's go.
You were awesome, Jesse.
With that gasp and chase in the mine cart, that is like the
perfect warm up for when
we get to Boomtown.
Boomtown?
Yeah, Boomtown!
This is it.
I think I'm going to hold off on the whole going first
thing for a while, Jesse.
How about you take this one?
Don't be careful, okay?
Wrong step.
Bam, bam, bam...
Stella.
Are you all here?
Step.
I'm gonna go get some food.
Whoa, you see that?
Utter chaos, man.
Your loot is mine, friggin'.
You'll have to catch me first, Mammoth.
Whoa, I hope they're okay.
And if they're not, at least they died doing what they
loved.
Well, here you have it, Jesse.
Boomtown in all its glory.
What do you think?
Wow, Boomtown sure does keep you on your toes.
Exciting stuff, huh?
Yeah, yeah, now you're getting it.
Dude, it's freaking glowing.
Dude, I think you're on to something there.