We're here to ask for your help.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, sure.
So you're not a couple of Grievers here to catch me
unawares?
Because, haha, let me tell ya.
I mean, that guy?
He's got Griever written all over it.
Yeah, well that's because he's your biggest fan. Look at
him!
I mean, not like, biggest fan.
Right. So tell me something not Grievers.
How'd you find me?
Gabriel sent us on this mission.
Gabriel? Hahaha.
You're seriously telling me you're buddy-buddy with Gabriel?
You know how often people try to tell me that one.
This is all sounding pretty weird, dudes.
Who are you really? Why are you here?
The world is being destroyed.
You have me intrigued. Go on.
There's a huge monster eating up the entire world, and
nothing can stop it.
That's why Gabriel told us to reunite the Order.
Magnus, you've gotta come with us. You might be the only
chance we have.
Give me one reason why, for even a second, I should come
with you.
You're supposed to be a hero, Magnus, and right now, the
world needs a hero.
You can come with us and help stop this disaster.
All this stuff you've told me. You expect me to just take
your word for it?
Two strangers with wild stories.
And nothing to show for it.
Except an amulet that's not theirs.