Jesse, a lever's not gonna do you much good in a fight, is
it?
See? Isn't it better when you make it yourself?
Check it out. Endercons all lit up.
I can't believe it. We won!
Good for you, Jesse.
It's about time we beat Lucas and his gang of jerks. What
kind of stupid name is the Ocelots, anyway?
You know, Lucas may be kind of arrogant, but he has come
through for me in tricky situations.
You might want to get to know him. Just in case.
Yeah, you might be right.
I'm just saying, if you run into him at Endercon, try
talking to him.
I don't need a lecture on the power of collaboration, Petra.
How about a lecture on the power of my fists? It's short,
but deadly.
Come on, let's hurry.
Remember what Endercon was like before it was cool?
Remember what we were like before we were cool?
Some of us will never be cool.
Ha ha.
Creepers!
This doesn't look good.
Well, there's only one way off this bridge.
Whatever we do, we do it together.
Hurry up, Jesse!