Jesse, a lever's not gonna do you much in a fight, is it?
See, isn’t it better when you make it yourself?
Check it out… Endercon’s all it up.
I can’t believe it… we won!
Good for you, Jesse.
It’s about time we beat Lukas and his gang of jerks!
What kind of stupid name is the Ocelots, anyway?
You know, Lukas may be kind of arrogant, but he has come through for me in tricky situations.
You might wanna get to know him… just in case.
Yeah, you might be right
I’m just saying, if you run into him at Endercon… try to talk to him.
I don’t need a lecture on the power of collaboration, Petra.
How 'bout a lecture on the power of my fist?
It’s short. But deadly.
C’mon… let’s hurry.
Remember what Endercon was like BEFORE it was cool?
Remember what WE were like before WE were cool?
…some of us will never be cool.
Ha-ha.
Creepers!
This… doesn’t look good.
Well… there’s only one way off this bridge.