I don't know, he disappeared outside the witch's hut!
Curse that fool of a man.
Come on!
Guys, I think we lost them for...
Wow!
You lost them for wow?
What is that?
Oh... wow.
It's like we're at the edge of the world.
Actually, we seem to be at the corner of it.
Welcome to the Far Lands, my friend.
I'm glad Jesse snagged this cake.
Makes the whole wall of insanity thing a lot easier to face.
Hmm... I think I like cake.
Who doesn't like cake?
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Saren, have you been here before?
Not here specifically, but I have visited the Far Lands.
The Order traveled far and wide during our heyday.
How can Ivor live here?
I mean, it's one thing to build a war world inside the End,
but this...
Oh, I doubt he lives here.
He most likely comes here only for his most secretive
research.
Whatever Ivor is hiding in here, it will be extremely well
guarded.
This way, I suspect.
I'd feel better about this if Axel and Lucas were here.
Come on!
Is this... a maze?
It would appear so.
A massive one from the looks of it.
If Ivor used the command block to build this, it would hold
a speakable peril.
Why do I have a bad feeling about this?
Because some part of you still knows Ivor lives here.
I'm sure he's been here before.
Fortunately, this seems to be the only way forward.
There has to be another way.
A secret door, or... I don't know.
Some way around.