I think I must be seeing things
It's like another world up here a brand new totally
unspoiled world
That's my body axle my broken battered body
second
What it's made of wool this tree the grass it's it's all
wool
You're telling me that we've been resting all our hopes on
this guy and the whole time
He's been building some totally artificial happy land.
Could it be that he just
Missed home if you miss home you go and visit you don't
build an exact replica. We came here for nothing
We came here for Sorin and for his for mita bomb. That's
still the plan
Just look around Jesse if the greatest builder of all time
has spent years working on this
What are the chances he's even gonna have that bomb? Huh?
I've had enough crazy for one day
What's his problem just give him some space he'll be okay
So I'm probably looking for
Well to open a secret door you need a secret mechanism
You