it's yours if you want it that bad I've never wanted
anything badder there's no
way he won't notice his fancy potion is missing a good
thief always covers his
tracks fixed it oh he had the perfect crime
hey Ruben find any clues what is it buddy you smell
something
something over there good work Ruben
there's all this stuff soul sand it was everywhere in the
nether what about that
block in the middle I've never seen one of these before I
wonder if I just take
a closer look don't touch that Olivia I was just curious
don't forget what we're
here for find that skull
so good news weird news I found the skull but why'd I risk
my neck for that skull
if he's got two of them already maybe I've or some kind of
collector a trophy
hunter or he could be collecting them to make a bunch of
banners I think I know
what's going on here soul sand plus three wither skulls
that's the recipe
for a wither but oh wither that's one of the worst monsters
there is it came down
here to find the skull well we found it maybe we should
just grab it and get out
of here while we still can
guys scanner
don't you recognize me wait to see me that's not good
that you were rid of me didn't you that's better
you
with that