C'mon Axel -- make yourself useful and go find that skull.
I am…
Uh, nope. You're literally doing the exact opposite of what I just asked you to do.
There's no way he won't notice his fancy potion is missing.
A good thief always covers his tracks.
Fixed it!
Oh yeah, the perfect crime.
Hey, Reuben. Find any clues?
What it is, buddy? You smell something?
Something over there? Good work, Reuben!
What the hell is all this stuff?
Soul Sand. It was everywhere in the Nether.
What about that block in the middle?
I've never seen one of these before…
I wonder if I just -- take a closer look…
Don't touch it, Olivia!
I was just curious.
Don't forget what we're for -- find that skull.
Sooooooo.... Good news, weird news.
I found the skull, but...
Why'd I risk my neck for that skull if he's got two of them already?
Maybe Ivor's some kind of collector, a trophy hunter.
Or he could be collecting them to make a bunch of banners.
I think I know what's going on here.
Soul Sand, plus three Wither skulls…
That's the recipe for a Wither.
But... A Wither... That's --
One of the worst monsters there is.
We came down here to find the skull. Well, we found it.
Maybe we should just grab it, and get out of here -- while we still can.
Uh, guys?
Scatter!
Don't you recognize me?
Wait.
Surprised to see me?
No, that's not good…
Thought you were rid of me, didn't you?
That's better.
What was that?
Who's there?