I'll take Gabriel.
Then I've got Petra.
Hold on, this might be a bumpy ride.
Come on, horses!
Whatever you do, don't look back.
Ah!
I looked.
Watch out!
It's gaining on us!
We're not gonna make it!
Just keep it together, Gabriel.
Don't let it come any closer!
I'm trying!
Jesse, look out!
Am I seeing Andermen attack the Wither Storm?
Andermen move blocks. It's what they do.
There! We need to get over there!
Don't be rich.
Guys, come on!
We've got to build a new one, like right now.
Come on, faster!
Yee-haw!
Woo!
Axel, you're screaming in my ear!
Sorry.
We made it!
We actually freaking made it!
Hey, how are you feeling?
I...
I'm afraid I don't feel much like myself at the moment.
Gabriel!
It really is you!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Gabriel, it really is you!
They told us you'd kicked it!
Who are you people?
It's me, Magnus!
Old friend, don't you recognize us?
It's Sorin.
We've known each other for a very long time.
I'm sorry.