Who likes explosions?
That's right, yeah you do.
That's why I'm standing up here today.
Well, you guys ready then?
Oh, yeah! This'll be a way easier target than Magnus.
Wait, what's going on?
Oh, well, that's not good.
Is that your wither storm?
How are we? What do we?
Okay, just a little farther.
Wow, someone really went bonkers with the defenses, huh?
Who goes there?
Oh, Jesse? Is that you?
No, it's not Jesse.
Jesse, you're not going to get away with this.
You're going to get away with this.
Jesse, is that you?
Lukas, did you build all of this?
Well, yeah. I figured I would try and fortify the place,
you know?
Nice!
Quick, come on. You guys are never going to believe who
showed up while you were gone.
Petra!
Hey guys, how's it going?
Petra, you made it!
It's good to see you too, big guy.
And it's really good to see you, Jesse.
Back there in Gabriel's bunker, it got pretty dicey.