Seriously? Fishing?
It could work.
Got it!
Okay, we're all set to go again.
Time to move, buddy. Let's go.
Hitting the power plants.
Yeah.
I never doubted you for a second, but... but that was
incredible.
Maybe we have a chance of getting Dwellegarde after all.
Look! There's the sign! Redstonia! Redstonia, here we come!
We're about to meet the greatest Redstone builders in the
world!
Wow! Who would have thought that someday I'd really get to
visit Redstonia,
Ellegaard's capital city of engineering. Incredible!
Do you think Ellegaard will be willing, you know, to help us?
Redstonia
Have you seen all these inventions? These inventors are all
incredible.
I might know Redstone where we come from, but these people
are the real deal, Jesse.
I mean, I don't even know how they're making some of these
things.
That's rare for me.