Heroes can come from unlikely beginnings.
And broken friendships can lead to dark rivalry.
When the world is in danger, fate calls on the ordinary to
do extraordinary deeds.
But the question remains, will it be enough to save the
world?
This is so cool! The amount of engineering it must have
taken to do this?
Automated train tracks running all through the Nether?
Connecting all the different order members?
This is impressive! Thanks to these rails, we'll be there
in no time.
If we don't get the order back together, the Witherstorm is
going to eat everything.
We're gonna get to Ellegaard, get her to help us, and we're
gonna save the world.
I hope you're right. We definitely stand a better chance
with Ellegaard's help.
Uh... Jesse!
Whoa!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
The minecart!
Wait! More gas!
Grrr!
Do something about the gas!
Okay, think fast, Jesse. What to choose?