It's such a relief to see you. I'm glad you're okay
You pulled me out of that wither storms crutches, and I ran
and ran and ran for the temple
If you hadn't saved me
Well, I owe you everything Jesse Wow did Gabriel get away,
too. Did you see?
It's all a blur, but the wither storm left almost nothing
behind
everything
Everyone was just gone
It even got Gabriel
Wow
Been a while since I've been here
What is she doing here
Call this a hunch, but do you two not like each other?
Right. I forgot to mention
Olivia went on a little
Expedition of her own while you were gone and this
Olivia person
Came back with her
Did you know about this?
Jesse Jesse look I found Ella guard just hang on a sec.
Okay, I'll go figure out what's going on good
Easy now Olivia, let's try and play it cool. Hmm. So who
are you now?
And why did you bring him with you?