I don't understand. How did you escape?
You pulled me out of that wither storm's crutches and I ran
and ran and ran for the temple
If you hadn't saved me
Well
I owe you everything jesse
Wow, did cabriel get away too? Did you see?
It's all a blur, but the wither storm left almost nothing
behind
everything
Everyone was just gone
It even got cabriel
Wow, it's been a while since i've been here. Whoa
What is she doing here
Call this a hunch, but do you two not like each other?
Right. Um, I forgot to mention
Olivia went on a little
Expedition of her own while you were gone and this
Olivia person
Came back with her
Did you know about this?
Jesse jesse look i've found Ellegaard
Just hang on a sec. Okay, i'll go figure out what's going
on. Good. You do that
Easy now olivia, let's try and play it cool. Hmm. So who
are you now? And why did you bring him with you?
um