I couldn't save you. Things were happening so fast and that
thing was powerful.
Well, thank you for trying.
Um, sure.
All that matters is you're with us now.
And that you're still a fighter. The best one I know.
So, what do you say? Will you be part of our group again?
Alright, count me in.
We didn't all make it back though.
Guys, it was my fault.
I'm the one who took Ellegaardd's armor.
But you couldn't have known what was going to happen.
She's right. Don't blame yourself, kid.
I, uh, never blame myself for anything.
Ah! Being emotional is getting us nowhere!
What I want to know is what happened out there today. Why
is that thing still alive?
The Formidabomb just wasn't strong enough.
I mean, it ripped the Witherstorm apart, but it didn't make
a dent in the command block.
So the command block is still out there? Oh, great.
Look, our plan didn't work, so we obviously need a new one.
The question is, what do we do?
Why are you asking me?
Am I expected to know every last thing in the universe?
I need a moment to think.
Is he always like this?
You have no idea.
That jacket, it looks familiar.
Lukas always wears that jacket.
Oh, I saw other people wearing it when I was being thrown
from that dead monster.
Even thinking about it hurts.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
Jesse, if what Petra said is true...
I mean, do you think?
I thought for sure they were gone, but if they were just
trapped in the Witherstorm...