Give. Me. Back. My. Pig.
All right, you little maniac, fine. Take him, he's yours.
C'mon, Reuben.
I'm sorry Reuben. I was so busy trying to find that creepy dude, I didn't notice.
Remember that thing I had to go do with Petra?
Long story short, we met up with this guy.
He cheated me and Petra on a deal, and now we're trying to track him down. You in?
Oh, I'm in, all right.
Any sign of him?
I thought I saw him earlier, but it was just a false alarm.
Wait! There he is!
Looks like he's heading towards the Hall.
We're going to have to get past that usher to follow him.
Let's go!
So, yeah, hey...
What would it take to get us inside tonight?
Uh... tickets... hehehe...
This might sound crazy, but we're actually on an important mission.
I hope your mission came with tickets to the show. 'Cause otherwise...
Chickeeeeennnnnn!!!
Chicken - Chicken - Chicken!
It's gone, you're totally fine, you're a totally cool dude.
We have to do something.
Like what? This show has been sold out for ages!
We need a distraction.
A lot of chickens running around might be a distraction.
Shoo! shoo! Get outta here!
The usher is afraid of chickens...
What would you say if I told you I wanna break this guy's chicken machine to create the mother of all distractions?
But you have to break that pane of glass.
How're you going to reach it?
Let's look around. There has to be something we can do.