Let's see what this sucker does.
A secret passageway.
Why would you build a secret passage in a house that nobody ever visits?
More like why wouldn't you?
Secret passageways are cool.
Good point.
Are you guys okay?
We're fine, but the lever isn't working anymore. Stay there. We'll head down and see what we can find
What is all this?
Incredible. He's gathered them all in one place.
Gathered what exactly?
The treasures of the Order of the Stone.
The stories I could tell about these dusty old things.
You know, I often give up on my family.
You know, I often give Ivor a hard time, but for all his complaining, his time with the Order clearly meant a great deal to him.
Yeah, I guess so. Anyway, let's go get that enchanting book.
By the stars, the Ender Dragon. With replica ender crystals in all.
Wow, I always wondered what it looked like.
Hmm, no way out.
It's obviously some kind of puzzle.
Sorin, what's this thing supposed to be?
It appears to be an homage to our battle with the Ender Dragon.
Despite its name, it's still a treasure.
Despite its anger, Ivor never stopped being fond of us.
He was a big part of our team after all.
He knows his days in the Order were his finest.