Everyone, this could be a really nasty fight.
The rest of you go!
Hold them off!
What? Ivor, no!
There's no time to argue.
Just head for the corner of the glitch wall!
The what wall?
Hey, you witch! You're not the only one who can draw a potion!
Come on!
Guys, I think we lost them for...
Wow!
You lost them for wow?
What is that?
Oh...
Wow...
It's like we're at the edge of the world.
Actually, we seem to be at the corner of it.
Welcome to the Far Lands, my friend.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure if I'm the only one who can draw a potion.
I'd feel a lot better about going into this crazy wall thingy if I wasn't still hungry.
I'd rather be hungry than killed by a witch.
I'd rather be eating dinner.
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Sauron, have you been here before?
Not here specifically, but I have visited the Far Lands.
The Order traveled far and wide during our heyday.
How can Ivor live here? I mean, it's one thing to build a wall world inside the End, but this...
Oh, I doubt he lives here.
He most likely comes here only for his most secretive research.
Whatever Ivor is hiding in here, it will be extremely well guarded.
I'm sure he lives here.
This way, I suspect.
I'd feel better about this if the rest of our group was with us.
Come on!
Is this... a maze?
It would appear so.
A massive one from the looks of it.
If Ivor used the command block to build this, it could hold unspeakable peril.
Why do I sense that entering this so-called maze would be a grave mistake?
Because some part of you still knows Ivor.
Unfortunately, this seems to be the only way forward.
There has to be another way.
A secret door, or... I don't know.
Somewhere around.