Olivia I just stay out of this but your friends right
Olivia. I've got this just fine on my own
People can we please focus on the bigger picture
We have a very hungry wither storm and the process of
turning the whole world into its dinner
Yeah, I'll admit that thing looked real nasty and I've seen
some nasty stuff in my time
Too much for you was it your usual brutish approach didn't
cut it. Hey, you weren't there
All right, you didn't see how this thing just tore
everything up. You've never seen anything like it
Would you two stop fighting whoa
Jesse's right. We need to find some way to stop that thing
I don't know if you've looked around yet
But this place isn't nearly the stronghold it used to be
most of our supplies are gone
It would take a mountain of TNT to kill that thing
Hate to say it but you have a point. Can we start crafting
some men? I don't think we got that kind of time
Only soren were here. He might have something we could use.
Oh Ellie not this again
There's something stronger than TNT
Soren had a kind of super TNT stronger and more explosive
than anything else in the world
the form it a bomb
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I've heard all about the f-bomb before
well the for minibombs sounds perfect we should go get it
now
Well, there's a little problem there
We don't know where soren is
But you found us. Do you know where he is?
Our map could locate him
Unless he's in the nether or the end but it's worth a shot