He's lost control of it!
Oh, no need to be alarmed, my friends.
I have an elixir that will destroy this creature.
That potion, is that?
Uh-oh.
What?
It should work. I took such care.
Axel, you've got to throw the real potion.
But finders keepers.
You thieves, you're ruining everything!
Axel, come on!
Jesse, throw it!
It's protecting itself!
Now the command block exposed, the potion is useless!
It wasn't supposed to happen like this!
Martin! You coward, come back here!
Jesse, help me!
Help, help!
Thank you. I've always read about one thing.
I can't defeat that thing.
Not on my own.
Everyone's running away!
Axel, will you help me?
Will you help me?
Of course!
Follow me!
Out of my way, chickens!
No!
Wait!
Sam, up here!
Somebody help me!
Guys!
Help!
The End