Ivor, what are you doing?
No need to be alarmed, my friends. I have an elixir that will destroy this creature.
That potion -- is that...?
Uh-oh...
Uh, what?
It should have worked -- I took such care!
Axel! You've got to throw the real potion!
But -- finders, keepers!
You thieves! You're ruining everything!
Axel, come on!
Jesse -- throw it!
It's protecting itself!
Without the command block exposed... The potion is useless!
It wasn't supposed to happen like this.
Ivor! You coward, come back here!
Jesse, help me!
Thank you. Ivor was right about one thing...
I can't defeat that thing.
Not on my own. Everyone's running away...
Except for you. Will you help me?
Of course!
Follow me!
Out of my way, chickens!
Wait!
Hey! I'm up here!
Somebody help me!
Guys!