Hey, Soren?
Jesse!
Think I've got almost enough gunpowder now.
Glad to hear it.
And Jesse, I am sorry for not keeping this place as
organized as I should.
It's very embarrassing.
And this is my super TNT.
Let's build us a Formidabomb.
Yes, let's build away.
Uh, how do we build us a Formidabomb, exactly?
Do we just combine this with gunpowder?
Well, the crafting recipe is quite simple, really.
Super TNT in the middle and gunpowder all around.
Got it.
No, no, no, no.
The ingredients are highly unstable, even putting them in
close proximity to each other
is a risk.
Okay, well, we may not have the Formidabomb yet, but at
least we finally have the ingredients
to build one.
Progress.
And now that we have them, we...
We...
I literally don't remember.
You're gonna have to help me out a little, Jesse.
Now we just need to find a way to get it inside the
Witherstorm to blow it up.
Oh, oh dear.
Oh, I was afraid of this.
With the end underwater, the Endermen will try to escape.
The Enderman could lead or end them show up.
Of course.
To the mine carts, everyone!
I've been waiting ages to say that.
To people.
Oh, there you are.
I'm so glad you could make it!
Ha!
Could have used you earlier!
Ha ha.