The name's Jesse. What's it to you?
I'm supposed to meet up with Petra, not whoever you're supposed to be!
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't walk out of here right now!
You're the guy who needed a Wither skull , right?
Not so loud, you idiot!
Too many people know my business already.
Do you have the skull?
Uh... well… Petra has it -- and she'll be back any minute now!
Well. As long as she's bringing it... I suppose it wouldn't kill me to wait a minute longer.
Uh... well…
Ivor!
Ah, here she is!
Sorry I'm late, but -- good things are worth waiting for. I've got what you asked for.
IF you have what you promised us.
You didn't say anything about "us" when we first met.
And I don't like surprises.
If these are the people you associate with…
perhaps we should call the whole thing off
My friend is fine, right, Jesse? There's no problem here