The name's Jesse. What's it to you?
I'm supposed to meet with Petra, not whatever you're
supposed to be.
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't walk out of here
right now!
You're the guy who needed a wither skull, right?
Not so loud, you idiot!
Too many people know my business already.
Do you have the skull?
Uh, well... Petra has it. Should we back any minute now?
Well, as long as she's bringing it. I suppose it wouldn't
kill me to wait a minute longer.
Uh, well...
Ivor!
Ah, here she is.
Sorry I'm late, but good things are worth waiting for. I've
got what you asked for.
If you have what you promised us...
You didn't say anything about an us when we first met?
And I don't like surprises.
If these are the sorts of people you associate with...
Perhaps we should call the whole thing off!
My friend is fine, right Jesse? There's no problem here.
Let's not be too hasty, okay?
This is just a little misunderstanding.