No, who are YOU?
If you belonged here, you would know!
Unless that's all part of the plan…
I'm supposed to meet up with Petra, not whoever you're supposed to be!
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't walk out of here right now!
You're the guy who needed a Wither skull , right?
Not so loud, you idiot!
Too many people know my business already.
Do you have the skull?
Uh... well… Petra has it -- and she'll be back any minute now!
Well. As long as she's bringing it... I suppose it wouldn't kill me to wait a minute longer.
Uh... well…
Ivor!
Ah, here she is!
Sorry I'm late, but -- good things are worth waiting for. I've got what you asked for.
IF you have what you promised us.
You didn't say anything about "us" when we first met.
And I don't like surprises.
If these are the people you associate with…
perhaps we should call the whole thing off
My friend is fine, right, Jesse? There's no problem here