Don't worry, I'm fine
Stay safe, I'll find a way down
Hey show yourself who's there?
You
Trying to interfere with my plans again, I see
What are you doing down here?
Being rudely interrupted by you, clearly
I'm here with the order to find Soren's Super TNT
We're gonna take down your wither storm
The order?
Ha ha ha
I'm not sure
The order?
Believe me
That plan will blow up in their faces in more ways than one
They cannot help you
But me?
I choose not to
Sorry, Ivor
Stop right there, Ivor
Gabriel
You're alive
Against all your best efforts, Ivor
Look at what you've done
I never dreamt that even you could be this twisted
Save your posturing, Gabriel
We both know your words have always been hollow
Just like the order
They're not going anywhere
At least not in one piece
The threats pass harmlessly through me
But this sword will pass through you