I really appreciate you helping Reuben back there, Lukas.
Huh. I guess I did.
You don't have to do it all yourself, you know. I could
help.
Like I said, thanks.
Jesse?
What?
The amulet.
Soren must be close.
Uh, where'd he go?
You have got to be kidding me.
Sounds like the grinder is backed up.
With loot?
Go, go, go, go, go!
Whoa!
Keep moving!
Axel, look out!
Take that, ugly!
Oh, you want some too?
I'm coming, buddy!
I have had enough of this!
Take that!
Look at your face, spider!
There's two things I hate. It's running and monsters.
An ant portal?
That's the way out.
Wait!
What? Look!
Oh, no!
Petra!
Get away from them!
In your face, monsters!
I think I'm starting to get the hang of this.
Here we go!
Jump!
Oh, great!
Just keeps getting better.
Where's Axel?
He was right behind me.
I swear, I'm not trying to do that.
Get off!
Oh, jeez.
Are you hurt?
What?
No, I'm not crying. Just look.
So, what do we call that?
A herd of Endermen?
A flock of Endermen?
A swarm?