Call it whatever you want. As long as we don't look at
them, we'll be fine.
Yeah. Yeah.
We might want to hold off on the grammar lessons until
later.
Which way are we headed, Jesse?
The amulet does not work in the end.
Ha ha! Ah, great!
Whew! Man, so we were trapped, and now we're lost.
At least we're alive, and well.
Yeah.
We just have to keep on trucking till we get to Soren.
Face it, Jesse. We might never find this guy.
There he is.
That has to be Soren. Who else would build a staircase in
the end?
We gotta go.
Everyone, behind me! I'll handle the Intimate.
It's not a good idea.
Jesse's right.
Actually, you know what? I'll just go.
Give me a chance.
Just say the word, and I'll do it.