Hey, speak for yourselves, you fraidy cats. Reuben and I handled ourselves just fine. Isn't that right, Reuben?
Pfffft what? No. YOU screamed... like a piglet… is who did the piglet-like screaming.
Can you throw up... like, inside your body?
Uh-huh. I know because I just did, about five times.
Wow -- look at this place!
All these tracks converge at this point. You could probably get anywhere in the world from here.
There's the portal!
This is what Gabriel was talking about.
That's our way out.
It must lead back to the surface.
The surface is also where that creature is.
He's right. We have no idea what we're walking into. It could be dangerous.
Thanks for being so brave, Axel.
All right. I'm gonna go. I'm going. I'm going right now.