That's easy. I'll take the little tiny little zombies.
A hundred of them, crawling all over you with their tiny
hands.
Uh... All I need is like a shovel. I'm telling you, way too
easy.
So I've got a daylight sensor on the roof, and if I did this
right,
these lamps should turn on once it gets dark.
I didn't want to just leave Reuben here with nothing while
we're at the building competition.
He's coming with us.
Really?
What kind of question is that? Of course he is.
Okay, I'm not saying he shouldn't come. I'm not.
But don't you think it's a little weird that you take him
with you everywhere you go?
Reuben's my best friend.
I thought I was your best friend.
Both of you are.
I didn't mean anything by it. I'm glad he's coming.
I just don't want to give people one more reason to call us
losers.
Who cares what other people think?
I know. I'm just... It wears you down.
You say you're not a loser, Olivia. So win.
Okay. Fine.
Do you hear that?
No.
Oh, man. You guys totally freaked out. That was aweso-
Axel, what's the matter with you?
Great. Now I'm going to smell like a pig in Endercon.
I thought we were buddies.