Nothing built can last forever.
And every legend no matter how great,
fades with time.
With each passing year, more and more
details are lost until all that remains
are myths...
half-truths. To put it simply: lies.
And yet, in all the known universe,
between here and the Far Lands...
The legend of the
ORDER OF THE STONE endures, unabridged,
as self-evident fact.
Indeed, it is only a troubled land that
has need for heroes --
And ours was fortunate to
have, so long ago, four heroes such as these;
Gabriel the Warrior --
Before whose sword all combatants would tremble.
Ellegaard, the redstone engineer --
Whose machines would spark an era of invention.
Magnus the Rogue --
Who would channel his destructive creativity
for the benefit of all.
And Soren the Architect --
Builder of worlds.
And leader of the Order of the Stone.
These FOUR friends together, would give
so much to gain their rightful place as FOUR heroes.
Their greatest quest would take them on
a dangerous journey to fight a
mysterious creature
known as the Ender Dragon.
In the end, the Order of the Stone
emerged victorious and the dragon
was defeated.
Their story complete, they slipped away
into the pages of legend.
But when one story ends,
another one begins.
Would you rather fight
a hundred chicken-sized zombies
or ten zombie-sized chickens?