What are you doing here?
What did you see?
Leave her alone!
Yeah, back off pal.
You two!
Did you follow me here?
You thought you could get away with it, didn't you?
We're here to prove you wrong.
What are you going to do about it?
We know what you're doing down here.
Soul sand and three wither skulls?
You're building a wither!
Smarter than you look.
Hey, nobody talks to my friends like that.
Now shut your mouth or else.
Enough!
You've wasted too much of my time already.
Where'd he go?
If you won't leave of your own volition, I'll happily
remove you myself.
So I'll raise the door, will you?
Oh man, this is so exciting.
And now, for the first time ever here at EnderCon, we are
very proud to present...
The one, the only...
Please, please.
Thank you.
Are you with me?
Yes!
Anybody okay?
Um, guys?
I thought he was right behind me.
Well, if he's not here, the only place he could be is...
He's still down there!
Ivor's got an iron golem and all the ingredients to build a
wither down there.
If he were to unleash it in this crowd of people, we have
to act fast.
It just so happens that the greatest warrior of all time is
in the building.
We should ask Gabriel for help.
This is the smartest way to help Lucas.
He's tough.
I just hope he's tough enough to hold out a little bit
longer.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do this.