Olivia, look out!
What are you doing here?
What did you see?
Leave him alone!
Yeah, back off, pal.
You two! Did you follow me here?
You thought you could get away with it, didn't you?
We're here to prove you wrong.
What are you going to do about it?
We know what you're doing down here.
Soul sand and three wither skulls? You're building a wither!
Hmph. Smarter than you look.
Hey, nobody talks to my friends like that.
Now shut your mouth, or else.
Enough! You've wasted too much of my time already.
Where'd he go?
If you leave of your own volition, I'll happily remove you
myself.
Come on, friends, the tour, will you?
Oh, man, this is so exciting.
It sure is.
And now, for the first time ever here at EnderCon,
we are very proud to present...
The Web.
Please, please.
Thank you.
Are you with me?
To the end!
Anybody okay?
Um, guys?
Where's Lucas?
I thought he was right behind me.
Well, if he's not here, the only place he could be is...
He's still down there!
Ivor's got an iron golem and all the ingredients to build a
wither down there.
If he were to unleash it on this crowd of people, we have
to act fast.
It just so happens that the greatest warrior of all time is
in the building.
We should ask Gabriel for help.
This is the smartest way to help Lucas.
He's tough.
I just hope he's tough enough to hold out a little bit
longer.
...exploits of the Order of the Stalled, and even I do.
But then, it's so easy to doubt ourselves, isn't it?
It's easy to tell ourselves we can't do the things we want
to do.