It's such a relief to see you. I'm glad you're okay
You pulled me out of that wither storms crutches, and I ran
and ran and ran for the temple
If you hadn't saved me
Well, I owe you everything Jesse Wow did Gabriel get away,
too. Did you see?
It's all a blur, but the wither storm left almost nothing
behind
everything
Everyone was just gone
It even got Gabriel
Wouldn't believe that anything could defeat Gabriel if I
hadn't seen it for myself. This is terrible
Boy can't remember the last time I saw this place
Would someone care to explain what he is doing here
Called us a hunch, but do you two not like each other?
Right. I forgot to mention Axel went on a little
Adventure of his own while you were gone an adventure to
get him
Did you know about this?
Look, just wait here a second while I figure out what's
going on
Much appreciated
So who are you then and why'd you bring the queen of the
nerds with you that's Jesse my best friend
Trust me. Jesse's totally cool
I'll be the judge of that, huh?