I'll get the one with the fishing pole, you get the little
blue-haired creep.
Think fast!
Whoa!
Your training is coming along nice and new.
Just give me the amulet.
Jeez, pal. No need to shout.
Here you go.
My turn!
Come on, kid.
Kated, you're coming this way?
Yeah, and she had the amulet again.
Stop right there!
How about no?
These bricks will take forever to punch through.
Luckily, I think I found us a punch-free entrance.
Okay, little amulet. Show me the way.
Of course, not sure what I'll do when I get there, but
that's future Noor's problem.
I bet future Noor is very successful.
Uh-oh!
What's going on?
What did you know?
Uh-oh!
Ha! Nice! What did I tell you about teamwork?
What? But I'm the one who said we should work together.
No, you didn't. Give me that!
Give it back!
Got it! I actually got it!
Quick! Flush it out!
Huh?
Max Old Magnus is somewhere in that building above us. He's
gotta be close!
Then quick! Cross me the amulet!
You're surrounded by briefers, and they're gonna tear you
apart!
Well?
Jesse, we need to move now!