Hey, speak for yourselves, you freaky cats. Ruben and I
handled ourselves just fine. Is that right, Ruben?
What? No! You! Scream! Like a piglet.
Guess who did the piglet-like screaming?
Let's burn them.
Can you throw up, like, inside your body?
Uh-huh. I know, because I just did. About five times.
Wow. Look at this place.
All these tracks converge at this point. You could probably
get anywhere in the world from here.
There's the portal.
This is what Gabriel was talking about.
That's our way out.
It must lead back to the surface.
The surface is also where that creature is.
He's right. We have no idea what we're walking into. It
could be dangerous.
Thanks for being so brave, Axel.
Alright, I'm gonna go. I'm going. I'm going right now.
Like, right right now.
I just need to make sure I have everything I'll need.
I think I put the, uh, thing over in, uh...