It's the most beautiful place I've ever seen.
Ah, so bright.
Ah!
That's my body, Axel. My broken, battered body.
Hang on a second...
What in the-- it's made of wool.
This tree... the grass... it's all... wool.
You're telling me, that we've been resting all our hopes on
this guy,
and the whole time he's been building some... totally
artificial Happyland?
Could it be that he just missed home?
If you miss home, you go and visit.
You don't build an exact replica.
We came here for nothing!
We CAME here for Soren, and for his Formidi-bomb.
That's still the plan.
Just look around, Jesse!
If the greatest builder of all time has spent years working
on this,
what're the chances he's even gonna have that bomb, huh?
I've had enough crazy for one day!
Is he going to be okay?
Just give him some space.
He'll be okay.
So I'm probably looking for...
If I were you, I'd be looking for a secret door,
and the secret mechanism to open said door.