You're not going anywhere. But Jesse, that's enough. We're
all on the same team now. You stay.
Zombie-sized chickens. That's what I would fight.
Why's that?
Because I'm starving.
Thanks for keeping me around, Jesse.
Yeah.
Sorry about all that business last night.
Honestly, I'm just... I'm more embarrassed than anything
else.
See anything?
Hey! There's something over that way!
What is it?
Some kind of building, I think.
Let's get a closer look.
What's that?
What are we waiting for? Let's go!
What is this place?
That's what we're trying to figure out.
What's that?
I don't know.
That's what we're trying to figure out.
It's the Temple of the Order of the Stone.
Lucas, are you sure?
He's right. Look.
Do you think they're in there?
Let's go in and find out.
Let's just all be careful.
Okay.
If you spot anything, call it out. We don't have a lot of
time.
Isn't it weird how dispensers are carved to look like
spooky little faces?
What do you dispense, little guy?
I get the feeling that we don't really want to find out.
Get behind me.
What was that?
That's probably not a good thing.
Oh, come on, dispenser faces.
What about we're friends?
Run!
We're trapped!
We activated the dispensers with that pressure plate.
If we can figure out a way to trigger it again, I bet
that'll shut them off.
There's a crafting table. Maybe we can make something
useful.
What do you mean? We don't have anything.
All of our tools and materials are back home.
Alright, everyone. Empty your pockets.
Let's see what we've got to work with.
I have a few sticks left over from building the shelter
last night.
I've got some flint and...
a piece of string.
All I have are some chicken feathers I picked up after that
chicken machine exploded.
Let's see. We've got some flint and steel.
A sword.
Oh, and some string from a spider that I fought in the
woods around here.
String, sticks, flint, and feathers.