Be careful out there. Always am.
Add up all the times he was a jerk to us and this doesn't
compare.
You're being ridiculous. And if anything happens to him,
I'm blaming you.
I didn't know it would rain.
You feeling good about yourself?
He'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
Hey, guys. I picked some apples.
You are more than welcome with some if you want.
Thanks, Lukas.
You got up early and did all this?
I figured we have to eat.
I thought you left.
Yeah, me too. I got a tower up as fast as I could.
I tried to do some thinking, but it was too cold.
And then it started raining.
No, it's alright. It's just...
It's been a long night.
I'm resourceful, you know? People always say that.
And I am a good friend.
Most of the time, I'm a good friend.
Now yesterday I wasn't at my best for one second and it's
like, none of that matters.
Except for one thing.
Petra still needs us.
I let her down once.
It won't happen again.
We're in this together now.
I'm with you guys.
To the end.
I'm not really used to having to invite myself along.