He wasn't on the map.
Jesse, do you still have the amulet I gave you?
Of course.
Alright, there's your light, my light.
That's new.
There he is.
Warren had his fortress deep inside the mountains.
After the order broke up, that's where he went to keep
doing his experiments.
Look, he invited me there a couple times, but it always
seemed a little...
Weird, right? It always seemed a little weird.
Then let's stop hanging around here and go get us some
super TNT.
Whoa.
Blue?
Blue? That's Ivor!
Ivor is going to Soren's. We need to move.
It's not too far. We could probably make it on foot.
Righteous! We'll get some rest and head out first thing in
the morning,
avoiding all the no time and the monsters and everything.
If you had seen that monster, you wouldn't be saying that.
We need to leave, now!
Hey, I don't want the wither storm catching up with us. We
should go now.
Okay, everyone, let's get moving.
Yo, we haven't really gotten a chance to chat yet.
Oh, hello.
Gabriel over there says you saved him from this wither storm
thing.
You're pretty tough, huh?
I'm just doing my best to keep everyone safe.
Humility. Nice. I can dig it.
What to deal with your buddy Axel?
Can't tell if he's awesome or a little bit of a dork.
He's just a little, uh, doofy, you know?
He's like a little puppy. You don't know whether you want
to hug it or just walk away.
You know what I'm talking about?