I think I must be... seeing things.
It's like another world up here. A brand-new, totally
unspoiled world. So bright...
That's my body, Axel. My broken, battered body.
Hang on a second...
What in the-- it's made of wool. This tree... the grass... it's
all... wool.
You're telling me, that we've been resting all our hopes on
this guy, and the whole time
he's been building some... totally artificial Happyland? Could
it be that he just
missed home?
If you miss home, you go and visit. You don't build an exact
replica. We came here for nothing.
We CAME here for Soren, and for his Formidi-bomb. That's
still the plan.
Just look around, Jesse! If the greatest builder of all time
has spent years working on this,
what're the chances he'll even have that bomb, huh?
I've had enough crazy for one day!
Is he going to be okay? Just give him some space. He'll be okay
So I'm probably looking for...
If I were you, I'd be looking for a secret door and the secret mechanism to open
said door