Our friend is in trouble because of you.
We're trapped in the Nether because of you!
You have much bigger problems to contend with.
Through that tunnel is a network of mine carts built by the Order of the Stone.
It's your only way out.
Much as I hate to admit, he might be right.
Bravo for embracing the truth.
What was that?
I would wish you good luck, but luck won't carry you through the Nether.
You have my sympathies.
Let's get out of here!
RUN!
This must be what Ivor was talking about.
Everybody, hold on!
Wow.
The Nether.
Yeah... That is a LOT of lava.
And fire.
And other things that could burn you to death.
Oh no!
Oh that's a drop. That is very, very much a drop.
What are you talking about, new guy?
What drrrr
Oh! You weren't kidding.