She's going to make it.
You're concerned about your friend.
It's aberable.
You're all going to be dead very soon.
We'll see about that.
You don't even realize you're in danger right now.
So are you.
Through that tunnel is a network of minecarts built by the
Order of the Stone.
It's your only way out.
Much as I hate to admit it, you might be right.
Bravo for embracing the truth.
What was that?
I would wish you good luck, but luck won't carry you
through the nether.
You have my sympathies.
Let's get out of here!
Run!
Aaaaaah!
This must be what Ivor was talking about.
Everybody hold on!
Wow.
The nether.
Yeah, that is a lot of lava.
And fire.
And other things that could burn you to death.
Oh no!
Oh, that's a drop. That is very, very much a drop.
We were talking about it, you guys.
What drop? Oh, you weren't kidding.
Thanks for watching!