Look, even if your friends are out there somewhere, there's nothing you can do for them.
What? No, if they're alive, I have to go after them.
They might need me, Jesse.
You can't just up and leave, Lucas. You're part of our team.
And you saying that just reminds me that I left my team.
Lucas...
Look, you and me, we've made a pretty good team so far.
I'd even call us friends.
So I hope you'll understand why I need to go help my old friends.
I can't believe I'm saying this, but if your heart's telling you to go, then you gotta go.
Otherwise you'd be heartless or something.
Thank you, Jesse. I'll find them. And then I'll find you again, too.
I promise.
Thanks.
Hey, buddy. You doing okay?
Of course you are.
Wish I could say the same for everyone else.
We've lost too many people already.
Thanks for watching!