You're the genius, Eligar. Let's get started.
Fantastic.
Okay, excellent. Good. This is so exciting.
Terribly exciting.
Has it gotten this far before?
No, never!
Is it... destabilizing?
Oh, no!
Eligar, come on!
We need to go! We need to get to the portal!
Over here!
This way!
Captain!
Okay, just a little farther.
Wow, that's certainly impressive.
Wow.
Who goes there?
Oh, Jesse? Is that you?
Lucas, did you build all of this?
Well, yeah.
I figured I would try and fortify the portal.
Yeah, I figured I would try and fortify the place, you know?
Nice!
Quick, come on. You guys are never gonna believe who showed
up while you were gone.
Gabriel!
Hello, everyone.
It is good to see you.
He showed up not too long before you guys.
Eligar, my old friend.
Why are you a sight for sore eyes?
Maybe with you here we actually stand a chance against this
thing.
Oh, how I've missed your optimistic spirit.
Oh, and it's especially good to see you, Jesse.
I fear that you might be the last face I ever saw.
Getting here was... hard.