Hey, Eligard is cool and she's going to help stop this
wither storm.
Ellie? Cool?
Ah! Oh, wait, wait, you're serious?
Oh wow, that's uh, that's uh, woo! Oh boy!
I got tired of waiting around so I decided to go recruit
Magnus myself.
It was kind of a crazy adventure, but it all worked out in
the end.
And now, I'm the king of Boomtown!
Boomtown?
That's the name of Magnus' kingdom. I had to beat him in a
crazy tournament and...
Long story, you had to be there.
Short version, epic battle of explosions and mayhem,
death-defying action, shenanigans, and pyrotechnics.
Bada bing, bada boom!
Your friend here is kind of supreme ruler of my kingdom
now, you know what I mean.
Well, this is unexpected.
I'm not entirely sure what you mean, but I'm definitely
sure that I don't like it.
Yeah, show him some respect.
Oh, you're sticking up for Magnus, that's very... sweet.
Yeah, he's sticking up for me.
It's because I'm really awesome and super cool.
I'll never understand your fans.