This glow, I think I know what it means.
And look, it glows brighter when I move it in certain
directions.
Easy does it. Easy.
Maybe to the left. No, the right. I mean your left.
Right, I mean. Your right. About left.
Axle? You're stressing me out with that.
Whoa. Whoa.
Ding, ding, ding. Looks like that spire is where we'll find
Magnus.
Hey there, new people.
You, uh, you said you know where Magnus is?
Just leave us alone, okay? It's none of your business.
Hmm. I'm afraid to say that you're just making me wonder
even more what the heck is up with that thing.
What's going on?
North bouts of noobs. Who would think they could find
Magnus?
What?
I promise it's to help save the world.
Yeah, sounds complicated. I prefer you just handing over
the thingy.
Get back here with that.
I am North, and I shall use this amulet to find Magnus and
become the new world!
Watching you!
Hey, are they going the same way? They're working together.
This is just how we do it in Boomtown.
Which one took the amulet?