Yeah, well, the green part is...
It's weird.
Yeah...
And look, it glows brighter when I move it in certain
directions.
Eeeasy does it. Easy.
Maybe to the left.
No, the right. I mean, your left.
Right, I mean.
Your right.
About left.
Axle?
You're stressing me out with that.
Whoa.
Whoa!
Yeah.
Ding, ding, ding.
Looks like that spire is where we'll find Magnus.
Hey there, new people.
You, uh...
You said you know where Magnus is?
Just leave us alone, okay? It's none of your business.
Hmm.
I'm afraid to say that you're just making me wonder even
more what the heck is up with that thing.
What's going on?
North-Alice noobs. They think they can find Magnus.
Jessie?
Why don't you help us, huh?
I promise it's to help save the world.
Yeah...
Sounds complicated.
I prefer you just handing over the thingy.
Get back here with that.
I am North, and I shall use this amulet to find Magnus and
become the new world!
Move!
Watching you!
Hey, are they going the same way?
They're working together.
This is just how we do it in Boomtown.
Which one took the amulet?