No!
Do we still have everyone?
We just set off from my fortress. We'd better protect it
then.
Thanks for that, just a minute.
Incoming!
This way.
Hold it! Exide the tower!
The V-R chamber is built entirely of obsidian. We should be
untouchable in there.
Get out of here!
Herb, if you can get through the portal, you'll be safe.
Uh, something's not right here.
It's not red.
Let's get out of here!
Everyone, get in! Now!
Gabriel!
Thank you.
There are so many of them. I can't save them all.
I can't stop this by myself. We need to find the others.
Others?
The swords have been missing for years. But the others? You
must seek them out.
Take this amulet and guard it with your life.
You can do this.
You must.