That was pretty reckless, Lucas. You could have gotten hurt.
Orbit, jump!
I'm going to kill you!
Oh, be quiet! It's just a pointless building! That's all
I'm saying! I mean, look at...
Magnus, if an artist painted the inside of your mind, he'd
end up with the most extraordinary desert-scape paintings.
That's it! I'm going!
Once again, it falls to me to take care of everything. I'll
find this Super TNT myself.
Oh, no, no, no! You do not get to be the one who walks away!
That's it! I'm going!
See? I'm walking away too now! Super TNT, here I come!
It's hard to pick glass half full when they keep kicking
the glass over.
Bickering is kind of their deal. But hopefully they'll work
things out and get on with the important stuff.
What are we going to do now? Where should we go?
Let's figure it out.