Soren, you are so full of it.
Why would you say that?
You made it sound like you were the only one who mattered.
I was the leader. Believe you me.
Whatever.
I wonder if that story will help me solve this puzzle.
Bow and arrow, great weapons.
That's a sword.
So Soren rode the dragon, huh?
Hey, Ruben, give me a boost, will you?
Aha!
Yes, yes, that's it!
And then Gabriel poked it dead with a sword.
Bravo! You did it!
There's the book.
Wait, aren't those the Ender crystals?
Like the real ones?
No, it can't be.
But those things were destroyed in your big heroic battle with the Ender Dragon, right, Soren?
He kept them. The fool actually kept them.
Soren, you said destroying these crystals was the key to defeating the Ender Dragon.
You did kill the Ender Dragon, right?
Jesse, this isn't what it looks like.
Our story, the story, it's mostly true. I swear it.
Soren, I want the truth and I want it now.
I can't. We swore never to speak of it.
I don't care.
I'm afraid I haven't been honest with you, Jesse.
We did defeat the Ender Dragon, but it wasn't exactly like I said.
How not exactly?
We got rid of it, but we didn't kill it per se.
So what did you do to it?
We didn't do anything. We used the command block.
You used the command block to defeat the Ender Dragon?
I'm afraid so.
Understand, when I found that blasted block, we were nobodies.
But with its help, we became stronger, faster. We could do so much more.
The others had no idea what I was doing.
Yet the more I used it, the more we came to depend on it.
I knew it was only so long before someone would find out.
Ha!
So, I concocted a plan.
I would use the command block to blink the Ender Dragon out of existence.
Woo!
Securing our status as legends forever.
We told the world we defeated a dragon.
And the rest is history.