Take it Lukas.
No no I can't do that.
I insist.
Thank you Jesse.
That was for you Jesse not him.
If you had to, which would you rather fight?
A hundred chicken sized zombies or ten zombie sized
chickens?
Choose wisely.
That's a good one.
Let me think.
How can you guys joke at a time like this?
Petra is still out there.
Petra wouldn't mind at all.
She'd want us to keep our spirits up.
Fire her?
I don't know.
It feels wrong.
Fine.
Then we should get some rest.
We gotta start looking for this temple as early as we can.
Now my guess is if we start at the portal and kinda split
up.
Oh what are you doing?
He's just trying to help.
See?
I'm sorry Jesse.
I'm not gonna sit here and listen to this guy telling us
what's what.
I'm just trying to get ready for tomorrow.
You're the only one wearing that stupid jacket.
Don't tell us what to do.
Take that back.
Can't.
Wouldn't.
You know what?
I get to wear this jacket because I know how to build.
But that doesn't mean I don't know how to break things.
Your threats don't scare me now that we know how you really
are.
Jesse, your friend is way out of line.
Let's just drop it.
Don't be like that Jesse.
Just drop it.
Haven't you done enough damage for one day?
Petra might be dead because of you.
You're taking this too far Axel.
I don't have to take this.
Listen, why don't I just leave and let you guys hash this
out.
You can't leave.
It's dangerous out there.
I can take care of myself.
It's what Axel wants right?
Let him leave if he wants to leave.