Lucas, your friends could still be out there!
I know! And that means I... I gotta go after them!
They might need me, Jesse.
Can't just up and leave, Lucas. You're part of our team.
And you saying that just reminds me that I left my team.
Lucas...
Look, you and me, we've made a pretty good team so far.
I even call us friends.
So I hope you'll understand why I need to go help my old friends.
I can't believe I'm saying this, but...
If your heart's telling you to go...
Then you gotta go.
Otherwise, you'd be... heartless, or something.
Thank you, Jesse.
I'll find them.
And then I'll find you again, too.
I promise.
Thanks.
Hey, buddy. You doing okay?
Of course you are.
Wish I could say the same for everyone else.
We've lost too many people already.
Thanks for watching!