Let's build a hut. It won't take as long.
It's not.
That's it, Olivia. Jesse made the call.
We should get started.
All that work? And we're still eye level with monsters that
are trying to kill us.
It's done. It's over. We aren't talking about it anymore.
We could have maybe done like a multi-level thing, but...
That's too late now. I mean, it's... it's cool.
Let's keep it together, guys.
Oh, man!
What?
I'm going to tell you something. You have to promise not to
freak out.
What is it?
I have cookies.
One for me, one for Olivia, one for Jesse.
Thanks, Axel.
And one for Ruben.
Sorry, Lucas. I only have four.
Oh, no. It's... it's all right. I'm not that hungry anyway.
I'll just grab something in the morning or something.