Let's go with the treehouse.
It's functional. It'll keep us out of danger.
It's not a bad idea.
Alright, fine.
Let's get started then.
If I wake up with a spider on my face, I'm gonna expect you
to deal with it.
Lower your expectations, Axel.
Well, maybe if we'd built into the tree a little bit more,
it could've...
Never mind. It's... This is fine. It's good.
Looks good, guys.
Oh, man.
What?
I'm going to tell you something. You have to promise not to
freak out.
What is it?
I have cookies.
One for me...
One for Olivia...
One for Jesse.
Thanks, Axel.
And one for Ruben.
Sorry, Lucas. I only have four.
Oh, no. It's... It's alright.
I'm not that hungry anyway.
I'll just...
Grab something in the morning, or something.