You feeling any better, Gabriel?
Better is relative. The battle with the Witherstorm sapped the last of my strength. Considerable though it was.
You need to rest.
You're right, I do.
Look, Jesse, wherever you guys go next, give him some time to get his strength back.
The problem is we don't have time.
Jesse's right. In fact, it might be best if my journey ends here. This cave is safe, easy to defend.
If that's what you feel is best, then I support it. You've been through too much as it is.
Thank you, Jesse. I'm just sorry that I can't be there for you.
Me too.
Nothing had to turn out like this. If the order had just been different, if we'd made smarter choices, Iver wouldn't have turned into a maniac and, well, maybe Elagard would still be alive.
Come on, let's not talk about the old days.
But how can we not? So many lives torn asunder, the world ripped to pieces.