Petra, how are you doing? Are you remembering things yet?
I... I don't know.
These little flashes keep coming back to me, but then they float away again.
We've been trying to talk to her, but...
It's like she's never met us before.
I know I've met you before.
Before today, I mean...
I just don't remember... how, exactly.
You totally came to my rescue in the forest, remember?
I remember... a spider.
Yes, that's right!
And you needed me to kill it for you, right?
Hey, it took me by surprise.
Yes, it's working! You're remembering Jesse!
Do you remember me, too?
No. And yet, I feel like I know all of you, somehow.
Well, nobody forgets his ugly face.
It's true, they don't.
Wait... didn't we all fight that wither thing together?
Yes! We totally did!
She remembers it!
I remember... running... to a... a temple in the woods, and...
we were gonna be safe there, and...
How did I end up... inside that thing?
Uh... well...
Something bad happened there. I just... I can't remember what.