Don't go getting any ideas Lukas. Gabriel gave that to me,
remember?
Hang on a minute...
He's close!
Soren's close by!
He's gotta be...
this way!
Look how bright it is!
Sounds like the grinder is packed up!
With food?
Go go go go go!
sweeter than 18
this is huge
Wooho
长走
That's the way out.
Wait! What? Look!
Oh no!
Hector!
Get away from them!
In your face, monsters!
I think I'm starting to get the hang of this.
Here we go!
Jump!
Oh, great!
Just keeps getting better.
Where's Axel? He was right behind me.
Ha! See? I told you I'd pay you back.
Get off!
Oh, geez.
Are you hurt?
What? No, I'm not crying. Just look!
Hide.
So, uh, what do we call that?
A herd of Endermen?
A flock of Endermen?
A swarm?
I don't know.