Don't tell them Gabriel, just let them have their legend.
We all owe a great debt to Jesse and his friends.
But I owe a debt to you people as well.
Which is why...
There is something I want to tell you...
About the Order.
We may have defeated the Ender Dragon,
But that is nothing compared to what these heroes did.
They took down a wither storm.
They are a new generation of heroes.
Thank you, thank you everyone.
I know you think I'm up here because I saved the world or something,
But the truth is I didn't do it alone.
Far from it.
You see, I had my friends with me.
It was Olivia, Axel, Petra, Lucas.
They stood by my side right from the start.
Well, and they made fun of me when I deserved it.
That's just how we are.
Dang right we are.
It's crazy to think my friends and I started out in a tree house
And now we've been to some of the weirdest places in the world.
I mean, come on, we went to the Far Lands.
Whoa!
There was this gigantic wall and a huge maze and a model of the Ender Dragon that was just a dream.
Model of the Ender Dragon that, well, you just had to be there.
But when all was said and done, you know what really mattered?