You're right. They do deserve to know.
We all owe a great debt to Jesse and his friends.
But I owe a debt to you people as well.
Which is why there is something I want to tell you about
the Order.
The Order of the Stone is not what you all believed.
We were frauds.
We used the Command Block to falsify our legacy.
We were no heroes.
So it is time for the world to celebrate new heroes.
Real heroes.
Thank you. Thank you everyone.
I know you think I'm up here because I saved the world or
something.
But the truth is I didn't do it alone. Far from it.
You see, I had my friends with me.
It was Olivia, Axel, Petra, Lucas.
They stood by my side right from the start.
Well, and they made fun of me when I deserved it.
But that's just how we are.
Dang right we are.
It's crazy to think my friends and I started out in a tree
house.
Now we've been to some of the weirdest places in the world.
I mean, come on, we went to the Far Lands.
There was this gigantic wall and a huge maze and a model of
the Ender Dragon that...
Well, you just had to be there.
But when all was said and done, you know what really
mattered?
You