Magnus, as the ruler of Boomtown, I command you to shut up.
Is that so?
Uh, people, can we please focus on the bigger picture?
We have a very hungry wither storm
in the process of turning the whole world into its dinner.
Yeah, I'll admit.
That thing looked real nasty.
And I've seen some nasty stuff in my time.
Too much for you, was it?
Your usual brutish approach didn't cut it?
Hey, you weren't there, all right?
You didn't see how this thing just tore everything up.
You've never seen anything like it.
Would you two stop fighting?
Whoa!
Yikes.
Jesse speaks the truth.
We must find a way to defeat that monstrosity.
I don't know if you've looked around yet,
but this place isn't nearly the stronghold it used to be.
Most of our supplies are gone.
It would take a mountain of TNT to kill that thing.
I hate to say it, but you have a point.
Can we start crafting some, then?
I don't think we got that kind of time.
If only Soren were here,
he might have something we could use.
Oh, Ellie.
Not this again.
There's something stronger than TNT?
Soren had a kind of super TNT.
Stronger and more explosive than anything else in the world.
The Formidabomb.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've heard all about the F-bomb before.
Well, the Formidabomb sounds perfect.
We should go get it now.
Well, there's a little problem there.
We don't know where Soren is.
But you found us.
Do you know where he is?
Our map could locate him.
Unless he's in the nether or the end.
But it's worth a shot.
I'm sure he's in the nether.