We need to distract them! Get out of here!
Fine! But how?
The rest of you, go!
I'll hold them off!
What? Ivor, no!
There's no time to argue. Just head for the corner of the
glitch wall!
The what wall?
Hey you, witch! You're not the only one who can draw a
potion!
Come on!
Guys, I think we lost them for...
Wow!
You lost them for wow?
What is that?
Oh...
It's like we're at the edge of the world!
Actually, we seem to be at the corner of it.
Welcome to the Far Lands.
I'd feel a lot better about going into this crazy wall
thingy if I wasn't still hungry.
I'd rather be hungry than boiling in some cauldron.
I'd rather be eating dinner.
Oh, wow.
I'm so hungry.
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Swerne, have you been here before?
Not here specifically, but I have visited the Far Lands.
The Order traveled far and wide during our heyday.
How can Ivor live here?
I mean, it's one thing to build a wall world inside the
End, but this...
Oh, I doubt he lives here.
He most likely comes here only for his most secretive
research.
Whatever Ivor's hiding in here, it will be extremely well
guarded.
This way, I suspect.
I'd feel better about this if Axel and Lukas were here.
Come on.
Ivor's hiding in here.
Is this... a maze?
It would appear so.
A massive one from the looks of it.
If Ivor used the command block to build this, it could hold
unspeakable peril.
Why do I have a bad feeling about this?
Because some part of you still knows Ivor.
Unfortunately, this seems to be the only way forward.
There has to be another way.
A secret door, or... I don't know.
Some way around.