Soren, I looked up to you. The whole world did.
Nobody is more ashamed than me.
So you finally admit it.
Soren, how could you?
Ivor, how long have you guys been standing there?
Long enough that they heard the whole thing.
So we're liars. All of us.
You didn't think you could keep it secret forever, did you, Soren?
Is this why you left the Order? Because Soren lied?
Because they all did.
Soren, Gabriel, Magnus, Eligard. They agreed to keep this a secret.
And you? You agreed to stay quiet too, in exchange for all of our treasures.
I've technically never told anybody.
So this whole thing, the wither you unleashed, it's all been to teach the Order a lesson?
To teach the world a lesson. To show you who the Order really are.
Liars, cowards. And now, they know.
Yes. I suppose they do.