we're so close I can taste it I don't think so Jesse unless
Soren recorded
instructions for how to find the formidable this is the end
of the road
who's to say he didn't maybe there's something useful on
this record
I can figure out what he's talking about
Hmm, hide among them, hide among who?
Uh, Jesse? Do you think Soren is talking about... them?
I guess everybody needs hobbies even if they are really
really really dangerous
you think he's actually training Enderman to build stuff?
I think he thinks he's training Enderman to build stuff
let's look around see what we could find out
Olivia check it out looks like a taller one was hanging
there but it's missing
because Soren must be wearing it this is the disguise he
was talking about
In order to walk amongst the Enderman you have to become an
Enderman
kind of stinky but it fits
more than kind of stinky I'm sorry to say it's so weird I
know it's you in there
but I still don't want to look at you
the missing disguise is the one he had to put on before
going outside
he must be conducting his experiment right now
which means if we want to get to Soren
we have to go out there to do it
I'll just wait here
Thanks for watching!