Let's keep this between us for now.
I was thinking the same thing.
They might get upset or...
...I don't know.
Exactly.
We don't know.
It's just gonna cause panic and...
...we can't afford that right now.
If it becomes more of a thing...
...I'll tell everyone.
But...
...let me do it.
Hey guys...
...I have an idea.
Okay?
Magnus, help!
Well, alright.
But I have another idea.
Is it yelling for Eligard?
Well, not anymore.
Look, they aren't coming back.
They couldn't abandon us if they wanted to.
As long as we have...
...this!
Flint and Steel?
I don't get it.
It's not...
...that's not what I meant to pull out.
Hold on.
Oh, this!
Here, let me see it.
Do you mind?
I just...
...want to see it.
You can see it without touching.
If you can't get it to work...
It's working fine.
Soar it!
This is the spot it has to be.
Maybe.
This is definitely it.
Get ready to dig, people.
Who knows how far down that goes?
Anyone else have a better plan?
Jesse's talking to you, Lucas.
I know.
I just...
...need to...
High-go!
Let's get to it, then.
Are we cool?
It's a hole!
Does that mean we're cool?
I'll find out!
I guess that makes sense.
You dig, you get a hole?
I just...
...want to see it.
You can see it without touching.
I just...
...want to see it.
It's a hole.
I'm not sure why I expected anything else.
That was my point.
No it wasn't.
Jesse's got this, you guys.