I couldn't save you things were happening so fast and that
thing was powerful
Well, thank you for trying
Sure all that matters is you're with us now and that you're
still a fighter the best one I know
So, what do you say? Will you be part of our group again?
All right count me in we didn't all make it back though
Guys it was my fault
I'm the one who took Magnus's armor
But you couldn't have known what was going to happen
She's right. You can't blame yourself. Jesse. I'm surprised
he lasted as long as he did
Being emotional is getting us nowhere. What I want to know
is what happened out there today. Why is that thing still
alive?
The Formidabomb just wasn't strong enough
I mean it ripped the wither storm apart, but it didn't make
a dent in the command block
So the command block is still out there? Oh great
Look our plan didn't work. So we obviously need a new one
Question is what do we do?
Why are you asking me? Am I expected to know every last
thing in the universe?
Well, why are you asking me am I expected to know every
last thing in the universe?
I need a moment to think
Is he always like this you have no idea
Jacket it looks familiar
Lucas always wears that jacket
No, I saw other people wearing it when I was being thrown
from that dead monster
Even thinking about it hurts. Hey, hey, it's okay
Jesse if what Petra said is true. I mean, do you think I?
Thought for sure they were gone. But if they were just
tracked in the wither storm
You