We're the DeadEnders.
Whoa. Sounds like a name for pirates.
It's cool.
Okay, DeadEnders. You guys are in booth five.
Is that a freakin' beacon?
They have a freakin' beacon?
Freakin' beacon?
Again.
You're lucky I'm busy.
Hey, Josie. Guys.
Hey, Petra.
How's the build going?
Only time will tell, but we're optimistic.
Hey, Petra. I forgot to thank you for that Nether Star.
Hey, Lucas. Not a problem.
Can you help these tools?
For the right price, I'll help anyone.
If you need anything, you know where to find me.
None of us know where to find you.
Exactly.
No hard feelings, guys.
If you're cool with Petra, you're cool with us.
So why don't we just forget about all this
and, you know, make this about how cool our builds are?