Wow.
It's absolutely incredible.
How did they build this?
This looks like some sort of tracking system.
It's the Order! It's showing where they are now!
Look, we don't know enough about how this thing works.
Maybe the amulet only tracks them when they're on the surface.
Or maybe it doesn't work when they're in the Nether.
We have to go off of what we DO know.
Petra's relying on us.
That Wither Storm is still out there.
We KNOW that Gabriel was trying to tell us something.
We've got to find the Order of the Stone.
But... There are only two lights?
There are only two members of the Order left?
He said Soren was missing.
That leaves Magnus...
Or Ellegaard.
Let's head out.
I'm not going with you guys, I have to stay here.
If I know Petra, she's probably doing everything she can to find this place.
Just... Stay safe okay?
If there's even a small chance she's alive... I have to stay.
Go. Get help.
I'm going to focus on making this place safe before nightfall.
This temple is pretty big though.
If we're gonna have a chance at fortifying it, I'm going to need some help.
If, uh, maybe one of you guys could hang back with me?
Sounds like Olivia's have you totally covered while me and Jesse are out finding Magnus.
"Finding Magnus"? You really think that's how it's going to go?
We need Ellegaard. She's the world's greatest engineer.
She'll figure out a way to stop that thing.
We're trying to DESTROY it.
And when it comes to "destruction", Magnus is the master.