The Redstone Wrap.
And just like that, I'm nervous again.
Don't talk like that. We can do this.
Just stick to the plan and everything will be fine.
This year, we can't lose.
Let's do it.
Building starts...
Now!
Oh no! A fireworks dispenser! I'm so scared!
You worry about your build, and we'll worry about ours.
And now, the moment of truth.
Here goes nothing.
This looks so cool. We'll win this for sure.
I gotta admit, this enemy is sweet.
Good call, Jesse.
Guys, people are looking at us.
We're gonna win this.
Good build, man.
What? No way.
It's just a bunch of dyed wool.
Oh no! Reuben's on fire!
Reuben, no! Come back!
The lava's getting closer.
Where's the build?
Reuben's going to get lost.
You guys stay and save the build. On it.
We've got to cover, Jesse. Be careful.
We'll meet up with you at Endercon.
Reuben, where are you, buddy?
Just oink if you can hear me.
Okay, so now you get to choose where to go.
Go ahead, select a location.
I'm going to go to the end of the road.