Yeah, he's kind of a jerk sometimes, but he's our jerk, you
know?
Can't help but like him.
Interesting. Very interesting.
Then why didn't you listen to his plan to come get me?
I figured that we needed Brains to fight the Witherstorm.
And Brains means Eligard.
Yeah, I've definitely heard that a lot.
I'll try not to let it hurt my feelings too much.
Well, just keep on your toes.
Uh, guys?
I told you he was gonna catch up with us.
Oh, boy. You really weren't kidding.
No. Not again.
We can hash all that out later.
Come on, we gotta get out of here!
Not again. Not again.
Zords isn't much farther than this.
Zords isn't much farther. We can make it.
I am getting very tired of this Witherstorm.
Agreed.
Soren's place is gone.
I'm gonna go check on the other side.
Okay.
I am getting very tired of this Witherstorm.
Agreed.
Soren's place has gotta be just ahead. Come on!
Soren really lived down here?
It's so far from...
anyone.
Enchanting, isn't it?
Yeah, and I'm really not feeling those columns.
Aw, come on! It's fine! Look! Woohoo!
Just don't fall, okay?
Oh, that is deep. That is very, very deep.
Hang on! I'm coming!
Oh, man. We've got Endermen.
It was, uh...
more of a drop than I was expecting.
Endermen.
There are so many, I didn't think they ever came in groups
that big.
No kidding.
I'm not kidding.
It's like an Endermen party.
I heard your voice and thought I would come down to help.