Axel's one of my best friends. He makes me laugh and he
always sticks up for his friends
Interesting very interesting
Then why didn't you listen to his plan to come get me?
I figured that we needed brains to fight the wither storm
and brains means elegant. Yeah, I've definitely heard that
a lot
I'll try not to let it hurt my feelings too much. Well,
just keep on your toes
I
Guys
I told you we're gonna catch up with this
Really weren't kidding
Again
I
Want we gotta get out of here again, not again so it isn't
much farther we can make it
I
Am getting very tired of this wither storm agreed
Soren really live down here so far from anyone enchanting
isn't it?
Yeah, and I'm really not feeling those columns
Oh
Just don't fall, okay
Oh that is deep that is very very deep
Oh
Was more of a drop than I was expecting
Enderman there are so many I didn't think they ever came in
groups that big
No kidding it's like an enderman party I heard your voice
and thought I would come down to hell