I don't understand. How did you escape?
If you hadn't pulled me out of the Witherstorm's clutches...
Well, let's just not think about that.
I came here to the temple, hoping against hope to find
other survivors.
Wow, did Petra get away too? Did you see?
All that creature left in its wake was bedrock.
All those people...
Your friend Petra...
No one could get away.
We are alive.
That means there's still hope.
Come along. Everyone else is still inside.
Wow! Been a while since I've been here.
What is SHE doing here?
Oh, this isn't going to go well.
Right. I forgot to mention, Olivia went on a little...
expedition of her own while you were gone.
And this Olivia person...
came back with her?
Did you know about this?
Jesse, Jesse! Look! I found Ellegaardd!
Just hang on a sec, okay? I'll go figure out what's going
on.
Good. You do that.
Easy now, Olivia. Let's try and play it cool.
So, who are you now? And why did you bring HIM with you?
You