Let's build an Enderman.
Ah...
a Libius thing?
Are you whining?
No, I was saying, ah...
song.
Yeah.
I think this is the first time we've decided on something
before getting to the competition.
Think we've got everything we need?
It wouldn't hurt to grab a little more.
Let's get to grabbing then.
We're so prepared. We can't lose.
Cannot.
Bring it in.
Dare to prepare on three.
No, no, no.
Preparing is...
Darren.
No, that's the same thing.
Forget it.
Team on three.
One, two, three.
Team prepared.
We know what we're building.
We've got all the stuff for it.
We are so ready.
This year, it's going to be different.
I'm not just ready to build.
I'm ready to win.
Nice pig, losers.
Mmm.
I'm not ready to win.
I'm ready to win.
Mmm.
Oh, great.
There's Lukas and the Ocelots.
The rivalry continues.
Man, they've got matching leather jackets and everything.
So cool.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't the Order of the Losers.
Great. The fail squad's here.
Lukas, get a load of these losers.
Let's go, guys.
Name, please.
Axel.
How do you do?
No, your team name.
Team name?
We are not ready for this.
So much for losing anonymously.