All right, let's build the creeper.
You're going with Axel's idea?
What's wrong with my idea?
Nothing. It could be totally cool.
It is cool.
Yeah. I think this is the first time we've decided on
something before getting to the competition.
Think we've got everything we need?
It wouldn't hurt to grab a little more.
Let's get to grabbing, then.
We're so prepared. We can't lose. Cannot.
Bring it in.
Dare to prepare on three.
No, no, no. Preparing is...
Darren. No, that's the same thing. Forget it.
Team on three. One, two, three.
Team prepared.
Oh, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We know what we're building. We've got all the stuff for
it. We are so ready.
This year, it's going to be different. I'm not just ready
to build. I'm ready to win.
Nice pig, losers.
Oh, great. There's Lukas and the Ocelots. The rivalry
continues.
Man, they've got matching leather jackets and everything.
So cool.
Well, well, well. If it isn't the order of the losers.
Great. The fail squad's here.
Lukas, get a load of these losers. Let's go, guys.
Name, please.
Axel. And how do you do?
No, your team name.
Team name? We are not ready for this.
So much for losing anonymously.