And these are supposed to be the Ender crystals?
Scale models of them. They were the secret to the dragon's demise.
A secret, huh?
Ha, if only you'd been there. It was a fight for the ages.
We'd spent weeks preparing for our greatest battle ever.
But even so, the Ender Dragon was stronger than even I had imagined.
I realized that it was drawing strength from the Ender crystals, and that the crystals had to be destroyed.
I hit the first with a perfectly placed arrow, the second I destroyed by launching myself on the shockwave of Magnus' TNT.
Using only my strength and my wiles, I steered the foul beast toward the third crystal.
I flew the dragon directly toward the final crystal.
Only then did Gabriel deliver his famous final blow.
We became heroes, and eventually, legends.
The greatest the world has ever known.