We're missing something here, Sorin.
And I have a feeling the key might be locked in that head of yours.
I have a key locked in my head?
What I'm saying is, I think you need to tell me about the Ender Dragon battle.
Oh! Ha, if only you'd been there.
It was a fight for the ages.
We'd spent weeks preparing for our greatest battle ever.
But even so, the Ender Dragon was stronger than even I had imagined.
I realized that it was drawing strength from the Ender Crystals, and that the Crystals had to be destroyed.
I hit the first with a perfectly placed arrow, the second I destroyed by launching myself on the shockwave of Magnus' TNT.
Using only my strength and my wiles, I steered the foul beast toward the third crystal.
I flew the dragon directly toward the final crystal.
Only then did Gabriel deliver his famous final blow.
We became heroes, and eventually, legends.
The greatest the world has ever known.