Here we go!
Oh, no.
Watch it!
Okay, so, I'm not the only one seeing that we're running out of track, right?
No!
Good!
Jesse! That switch! Now! Do it!
Ooh, arms don't fail me now...
Haha, wow. I thought something bad was going to happen there, but, heh, I guess everything's going to be...
Whoa!
Whoa! Wait!
Oh man!
Uhhhhhhh, Axel? Olivia? Reuben? Anybody?!
Hang on, Reuben!
Reuben!!
Okay Reuben, remember when I everything was going to be just fine before?
I know I was wrong THEN but...
Whoa!
Stop!
Well, Ghasts are OFFICIALLY crossed off my to-see list.
Done with the Ghasts. Never need to see them...
Are you freaking kidding me with this?
This-is-bad, this-is-bad, this-is-bad.
Is...Ha... Is everyone okay?
I mean I'm not dead. I guess that's pretty good.
Ditto. Ditto with the not dead.
I just can't believe that Petra comes down here all the time... This place is awful.