Everybody hold on!
Oh no!
Fuck!
Watch it!
Okay, so...
We're not the only ones seeing that we're running out of
track, right?
No!
Good!
Jesse! That switch! Now, do it!
Hold on, don't fail me now!
Wow!
I thought something bad was gonna happen there, but I guess
everything's gonna be...
Whoa!
Oh, wait!
Uh, Axel?
Lydia?
Ruben?
Anybody?
Hang on, Ruben!
Ruben?
Okay, Ruben, remember how I said everything was gonna be
just fine before?
I know I was wrong then, but...
Whoa!
Stop!
Well, gasser officially crossed off my to-see list.
Some of the gas, you never need to see them.
Are you freaking kidding me with that?
Spin, spin, spin...
Oh!
Is... huh... is everyone okay?
I mean, I'm not dead. I guess that's pretty good.
Ditto. Ditto with the not dead.
I just can't believe that Petra comes down here all the
time.
This place is awful.
Your throat's gonna be sore later, Axel.
Why?
I'm just saying.
Wasn't that you doing all that screaming before?
Sounded like you were really shredding your larynx.
Oh, yeah! I heard that too.
Really high-pitched, kind of like a squeaky piston.
What? No, shut up.
Never mind. Must've... must've been something else.