Soren come back here dude, what a chicken
Jesse you can handle things out here, right? What I can't let him get himself killed
Just get to the command block and destroy it. Sorry
So much for the mighty order of the stone
Doesn't matter. We have work to do
We need to get those Enderman to attack it
Tractor beam Jesse that's it
Make them chase you into the tractor beam
Oh
Yes
Jesse boiling
Now we just need to find you a way up
Build you a way up. That's it. Everyone empty your pockets. Let's see
I've got redstone and cobblestone from Ivor's armory. I have some TNT from boom town got Pistons repeaters
Look, it gave me some more. I took some slime from the maze. Oh, and they still have that minecart
That's gotta be enough to make something right?
I mean if we use the TNT on say minecart or those piston and we do have all that cobblestone
Maybe we could build a ramp or even go straight up vertically or find a way to use redstone
We're close to an answer. I can feel it