Hey, thanks for grabbing that.
Not a problem.
Hang on a minute.
He's close.
Soren's close by.
He's gotta be... this way.
Look how bright it is.
Sounds like the grinder is packed up.
With loot?
Go, go, go, go, go!
Wee, wee, wee, wee!
Whoa!
Keep moving!
Axel, look out!
Ah!
Keep that, aren't we?
Oh, you want some too?
I'm coming, buddy!
I have had some of this!
Take that!
In your face, spider!
There's two things I hate.
It's running and monsters.
Can you pull it off?
That's the way out.
Wait!
What?
Look!
Oh no!
Gabriel!
Get away from them!
Yah!
In your face, monsters!
I think I'm starting to get the hang of this.
Here we go!
Jump!
Whoa!
Oh, great!
Just keeps getting better.
Where's Axel?
He was right behind me.
Ooh!
Ha!
See?
I told you I'd pay you back.
Get off!
Oh, geez.
Are you hurt?
What?
No, I'm not crying.
Just look!
So, what do we call that?
A herd of Endermen?
A flock of Endermen?
A swarm?