Ivory you're a madman
In all your scheming to expose the order you've nearly
destroyed the known world
My wither plan obviously backfired. Yeah, thank I didn't
know we'd end up with three of those things tearing the
world apart
Which brings us back to why we're here. We need to destroy
that command block like now
Jesse's right
Destroying the command block is all that matters anymore
How
Ironic that the best thing the command block gave us was
the very means to destroy it
So the enchanting book, what do we do with it? You craft a
weapon then put it on an anvil follow me
I'll show you hi, Vore
I'm sorry
About everything. Yes. Well, it doesn't matter now
Grab some ingredients and craft a weapon. I'll show you how
to enchant it sweet
Let's see there's a bunch of crafting stuff and diamond
score
You