That was absolutely amazing!
They didn't call us the Order of the Stone for nothing.
I wonder if that story will help me solve this puzzle.
Bow and arrow, great weapons.
That's a sword. So Soren rode the dragon, huh?
Hey Ruben, give me a boost, will ya?
Aha!
Yes!
Yes, that's it!
And then Gabriel poked it dead with a sword.
Bravo! You did it!
There's the book.
Wait, aren't those the Ender crystals?
Like, the real ones?
No, it can't be.
But those things were destroyed in your big heroic battle
with the Ender dragon, right, Soren?
He kept them. The fool actually kept them.
Soren, you said destroying these crystals was the key to
defeating the Ender dragon.
You did kill the Ender dragon, right?
Jesse, this isn't... this isn't what it looks like. Our
story, the story, it's mostly true. I swear, I swear.
Soren, I want the truth and I want it now.
I can't. We swore never to speak of it.
I don't care.
I'm afraid I haven't been honest with you, Jesse. We did
defeat the Ender dragon, but it... it wasn't exactly like I
said.
How not exactly?
We got rid of it, but we didn't kill it, per se.
So what did you do to it?
We didn't do anything. We used the command block.
You used the command block to defeat the Ender dragon?
I'm afraid so.
Understand, when I found that blasted block, we were
nobodies.
But with its help, we became stronger, faster, we could do
so much more.
The others had no idea what I was doing. Yet the more I
used it, the more we came to depend on it.
I knew it was only so long before someone would find out.
So, I concocted a plan.
I would use the command block to blink the Ender dragon out
of existence.
Securing our status as legends forever.
We told the world we defeated a dragon.
And the rest is history.