I'll go first.
That's not what I was saying.
I'm going.
Well, if you absolutely insist.
Well, see you guys on the other side, I guess.
Be careful.
Thanks, Jesse.
Okay, not what I was expecting.
Oh, man.
That was close.
There was a zombie.
Oh.
Is it dead?
I mean, you know, it's probably dead.
Yeah.
Where are we?
In the dark in the middle of nowhere?
Maybe we should bed down for the night.
It's dangerous to be out when it's this dark.
I thought we were headed toward a temple.
We're looking for a giant building.
It should be pretty obvious.
I've or said...
No, I've or said,
well, then maybe this is the temple.
Take it easy, Axel.
He called me stupid.
No, I'm not.
But you wanted to.
No, I didn't.
Huh?
Did you say something?
We have to build a shelter.
I thought that was what I said, but, uh...
Yep, that's totally...
It's getting dark and stuff.
I say we build a tree house.
That'll take forever and we'll be exposed while we do it.
We just need a quick and dirty hut.
Look, whatever it is, we gotta do it fast.
What?
In a hut, we won't know what's coming until it's knocking
on our door.
A tree house is gonna be spider town.
I hate spiders.