You can do it, Axel.
That's right, I can do it.
Whatever's on the other side has no idea when it's got coming.
Alright, here I go. Thanks, Jesse.
Right behind you.
Be safe up there, Axel.
Ready or not, here I come.
Get off of me!
Oh, man. That was close.
I'm never going first again.
Where are we?
In the dark; in the middle of nowhere.
Maybe we should bed down for the night.
It's dangerous to be out when it's this dark
I thought we were headed toward the temple.
We're looking for a giant building. It should be pretty obvious.
Ivor said...
Ohhh. "Ivor said". Well, then maybe this is the temple.
Take it easy, Axel.
He called me stupid.
No, I didn't.
But you wanted to.
Huh? Did you say something?
We have to build a shelter.
I thought that was what I said, but… uh...
Yup. That's totally... It's getting dark and stuff.
I say we build a treehouse.
That'll take forever. And we'll be exposed while we do it.
We just need a quick and dirty hut.
Look, whatever it is? We gotta do it fast.