Gabriel, are you okay?
I know it's not the best time and I don't want to worry
you, but there's something I'd like to discuss with you in
private, Jesse.
But let's split up.
I'm aware that letting them head off alone was risky, but I
need to talk to you about a private matter.
Hey, whatever it is, I trust you. You can tell me.
Thank you for being so understanding.
I'm so glad to see my old friends together again. I don't
want to ruin it with this.
What?
You may have succeeded in getting me away from the Wither
Storm, but I fear it was already too late.
What is that? What's wrong with your arm?
Tell me. Do you know what Wither is?
The Wither? Of course, we've been-
No, just Wither. Or Wither's sickness, to be more
descriptive.
It is something I've contracted before in my travels, but
it always wears off.
It seems that Ivar's monster exudes a Wither sickness that
is decidedly more fatal.
Well, we're going to go back and tell the others we can get
help.
No, Jesse. You can't tell anyone about this.
What? Creeper, look out!
Take my hand. I'll pull you up.
My strength is compromised! I couldn't maintain my hold!
I'm so sorry!
Jesse, are you alright?
Are you hurt, Jesse?