The order failed. Part of me was still holding out hope that they could fix things, but...
I guess I should have known better.
You're really not making me feel better, Reuben.
Oh, you want help, do you?
That's what I said, isn't it? Just as you once helped us before.
This isn't about the past, it's about the future. There are three of those things now.
You say that like it's my fault!
It is your fault!
Take responsibility for once, Soren!
Soren, you need to listen to me!
Hush! I vore for once!
I told you, I wouldn't have followed you here without good reason.
What you don't understand is, you are all in very grave danger.
Oh, oh, oh, obviously!
No, I mean specifically this group.
The Weather Storm isn't acting randomly, it's following Gabriel.
You see, I may have programmed it to follow his amulet.
I have the amulet, Ivor, I have all along.
What?
Ivor, you fool! You've created a monster that's following Jesse!
I... I didn't know.
And it's only getting stronger!
You don't think I realize that? Nothing can stop those things! Nothing even hurts them!
Well, except Enderman.
We actually just saw a bunch of Endermen pull blocks off a Weather Storm.
So, enough of them working together might be able to destroy a Weather Storm entirely.
The question is, how to bring the storms and the Endermen together?
Endermen aren't pets, they don't follow orders.
At least, not from mere mortals.
I mean, they're just animals.
They're just animals.