This might explain why Ivor had such a grudge against Gabriel.
They lied to us. They lied to the whole world.
Why would they do this?
This is so... crazy.
The Order might not be what we thought they were, but Petra is still out there.
The monster is still out there.
Jesse's right. We need to focus on what we came here to do.
Where do these stairs go?
Only one way to find out.
Now this is cool.
Wow.
What happened to the walls?
More like, what happened to this whole place?
This must have been where they met.
So where are they then?
Gabriel said that once we find the temple, the amulet would lead us to the Order of the Stone.
Well, what are you waiting for? Pull it out then.
Is... something supposed to happen?
Well, that was a let down.
There's got to be something we're missing.
Look around and see if you can find anything.