Awesome! I've never owned a diamond weapon!
Just wait till you enchant it!
Behold my enchanted diamond hoe!
Yes, that should do the job nicely.
But if you're fighting those wither monsters head on,
you'll want better armor too.
I enchanted these for the Order. They're about as strong as
it comes.
Even able to withstand TNT!
Any preference?
Well, I kinda want to keep the armor I'm already wearing.
Really?
I mean, Eligar died so I could have it, you know?
Come to think of it, she would have liked that. Very well.
Nice weapon, Jesse!
Thanks!
But at least take some for your friends.
Sounds good to me.
Let's get back to Soren's fortress and see how the wither
storms are doing against those Endermen.
I'm sure they'll be here soon.
Oh, my poor fortress!
I see Endermen, so this means the plan's working, right?
Shouldn't the Endermen have dismantled those things by now?
Or am I just confused?
It's not just you. Something's wrong.
Jesse, over here!
Axle!
You guys made it! Nice freakin' armor, by the way.
Do you still have the amulet?
Safe and sound. That's not the problem.
Then what is?
The Endermen. They're not angry enough.
I mean, some of them are, but a lot of them are just
standing around moving blocks.
You know, being Endermen.
Ugh! Blast!
They kept the main wither storm busy, but one of the
smaller ones started attacking us.
And Magnus ran off to fight that thing all by himself.
He's fighting a wither storm? Alone?
Yep. Kept saying something about paying for the mistakes of
the past. Whatever that means.
If a fellow member of the Order of the... of the, uh...
Order of the Stone?
Is out there fighting, then I belong out there, too.
Gabriel, no, no! I told you, you're not who you think you
are!
My name is Gabriel the Warrior!
Raaaaaah!
Man, he's running the wrong way.
Without the command block, none of them stands a chance.
Say what now?
I'll explain later.
Fine.
Hey, uh, you guys didn't check on Petra, did you?
No, we came straight here.
All alone in that cave? I hope she's all right.
She will be as long as we destroy the command block.
So what's the plan?
I mean, I know we gotta go in there, but...
Do we just go for it, or what?