Okay, I can do this.
Redstone repeater, redstone repeater, redstone repeater.
Done. Pretty nice.
If I make up one of myself.
Okay, that's a step in the right direction.
Bam! Door open.
Switch is on.
Okay, good, good.
Wow, here it is.
Ellegaardd's redstone laboratory.
Seems more like an entrance or a foyer or something.
Don't worry, pal, we'll find her.
I just hope she can actually help us.
That might be the most redstone stuff I've ever seen in my
life.
You can say that again.
She's moving a lot of different ingredients around here.
Man, look at all this, huh?
Whatever she's working on, if it requires all of these
ingredients,
it must be something really, really big.