Not gonna lie, but we've dealt with worse, right?
Have we?
How's it going?
Tell me, Jesse, who is this person?
She keeps insulting me.
That right there is Eligard. Ellie to you.
Eligard, hmm?
And how do I know her exactly?
You guys defeated the Ender Dragon together, the most
fearsome creature this land has ever seen.
Really?
Yeah, really! You're kind of a big deal.
It isn't working. He doesn't remember anything.
Talk to him about your past, something only you would know
about.
Hmm... like what?
Talk about fighting the Ender Dragon.
I don't think so. I've told that story way too many times.
Which is why it might help.
Ah, okay, fine.
Ender Dragon. Scariest thing alive, right?
Well, for most of the battle, it looked like we were goners.
But you know who finally slayed that beast?
Um, was it Jesse?
What? No! It was you, Gabriel. You slayed it!
Oh... thank you for sharing that with me.
And Jesse, thank you too. You've been a big help here.
I, uh... I need to repay your kindness.
I'm not sure how exactly.
But I want to express my gratitude.