I'll go first.
That's not what I was saying.
I'm going.
Well, if you absolutely insist.
Well -- see you guys on the other side, I guess.
Be careful.
Thanks Jesse.
Okay... Not what I was expecting.
Oh man. That was close.
There was a zombie.
Oh... Is it dead? I mean, you know, dead-dead?
Yeah.
Where are we?
In the dark; in the middle of nowhere.
Maybe we should bed down for the night.
It's dangerous to be out when it's this dark
I thought we were headed toward the temple.
We're looking for a giant building. It should be pretty obvious.
Ivor said...
Ohhh. "Ivor said". Well, then maybe this is the temple.
Take it easy, Axel.
He called me stupid.
No, I didn't.
But you wanted to.
Huh? Did you say something?
We have to build a shelter.
I thought that was what I said, but… uh...
Yup. That's totally... It's getting dark and stuff.
I say we build a treehouse.
That'll take forever. And we'll be exposed while we do it.
We just need a quick and dirty hut.
Look, whatever it is? We gotta do it fast.