Awesome! I've never owned a diamond weapon!
Just wait till you enchant it!
Behold! My enchanted diamond pickaxe!
Yes, that should do the job nicely.
But if you're fighting those wither monsters head on, you'll want better armor too.
I enchanted these for the Order. They're about as strong as it comes.
Even able to withstand TNT!
Any preference?
Oh, I kinda wanna keep the armor I'm already wearing.
Really?
I mean, Eligar died so I could have it, you know?
Come to think of it, she would have liked that. Very well.
Nice weapon, Jesse!
Thanks!
But at least take some for your friends.
Sounds good to me.
Let's get back to Soren's fortress and see how the wither storms are doing against those Endermen.
Oh, my poor fortress!
I see Endermen, so this means the plan's working, right?
Shouldn't the Endermen have dismantled those things already? Or am I just confused?
It's not just you. Something's wrong.
Jesse, over here!
What?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's not just you. Something's wrong.
Jesse, over here!
Axle!
You guys made it!
Nice freakin' armor, by the way.
Do you still have the amulet?
Safe and sound. That's not the problem.
Then what is?
The Endermen. They're not angry enough.
I mean, some of them are, but a lot of them are just standing around moving blocks.
You know, being Endermen.
Blast!
Well, it's nothing we can't handle, right?
I'm not so sure about that.
Now is not the time for cold feet, Soren!
So what's the plan?
I mean, I know we gotta go in there, but...
Do we just go for it, or what?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.