I'll take Gabriel.
Then I've got Petra.
Hold on, this might be a bumpy ride.
Come on, horses!
Whatever you do, don't look back.
Ah!
I looked.
Watch out!
It's gaining on us!
We're not gonna make it!
Just keep it together, Gabriel.
Don't let it come any closer!
I'm trying!
Jesse, look out!
I'm gonna get you!
Am I seeing Andermen attack a wither storm?
Andermen move blocks, it's what they do.
There, we need to head over there.
The bridge.
Guys, come on!
We gotta build a new one, like right now.
Come on, faster!
Yee-haw!
Woo!
Axel, you're screaming in my ear!
Sorry.
We made it!
We actually freaking made it!
Hey, how are you feeling?
I...
I'm afraid I don't feel much like myself at the moment.
Gabriel!
It really is you!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It really is you!
Oh, I knew if anybody could outrun death it would be you!
Who are you people?
It's me, Ellegaardd, come on!
Old friend, don't you recognize us?
It's Sorin.
We've known each other for a very long time.
I'm sorry.