I've got Petra!
Then I'll take Gabriel!
Hold on, this might be a bumpy ride.
Come on, horses!
Whatever you do, don't look back.
I won't.
Watch it!
It's gaining on us!
No offense, but you can use a little practice.
First time on a horse here!
I turn around to see if it's gaining,
but it's all I can do to hold on.
Jesse, look out!
I'm going to get you!
Am I seeing Enderman attack a weather storm?
Enderman move blocks, it's what they do!
There, we need to get over that!
Courage!
Guys, come on!
We gotta build a new one, like right now.
Come on, faster!
I saw you screaming in my ear!
Sorry.
We made it!
We actually freaking made it!
Hey, how are you feeling?
I...
I'm afraid I don't feel much like myself at the moment.
Gabriel!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Gabriel!
It really is you!
Oh, I knew if anybody could outrun death it would be you!
Who are you people?
It's me, Elegard, come on!
Old friend, don't you recognize us?
It's Sorin.
We've known each other for a very long time.