What part of throwing the fight was that what say you noob
I am king and those who challenge me will be
Annihilated Jesse. I think he just lost it Magnus crowds a
cannon
Yeah, finish it with a cannon if it's a cannon you want
It's a cannon you get
Yep, he's completely lost it. Dude's going for the kill.
Jesse, you better craft the I don't know greatest thing in
your life
Like right now. Well, there's still some material in the
chest
That's it Jesse go
Max, check it out
Yeah, it might do but Jesse look
Jesse look
Supposed to throw the fight
Jesse look out
Get back
Stop, I got you
I got you a bow and some arrows
A bow and a cannon fight
Max, there are all sorts of cliched lines about this
Yeah, but the TNT
Inside the cannon
TNT plus arrow
Oh yeah
Time to see how well you fly
Calvin
I got you, I got you
Man, you smell delicious right now
Hey Magnus
Yeah, short stub
Flying pig jokes are totally played out
Ha ha ha ha ha
No
We have a winner
The MUA Holder
Can I say something there champ?
It's just the winner sometimes I don't know gives a speech
Quantificates
More rates, say something