Right on, Jesse!
Uh, by the power vested in me, yadda-da-yadda-da-da,
the Order of the Stone!
What?
Jesse, you're going to have to set down a crafting table
out there
and make that for Midabob.
Everyone else, grab a buddy and split up.
We need to keep that wither storm on track, so build,
build, build!
Jesse, don't forget, super TNT in the middle
and gunpowder all around!
I hope this works!
Go, go, go!
Not yet!
Got it.
Please don't blow up.
Watch out!
No!
Magnus!
There.
Eat this!
Yeah!
Is that it?
Is it over?
I can't believe it's actually dead.
You did it, Jesse! You actually did it!
Not that I'm saying I doubted you, but I did a little.
But now I don't, and I never will again.
Look, I know it wasn't easy, but...
About time we got a real wed.