We're the Nether Maniacs.
You just thought of that right now?
Yep.
We've never even been to the Nether.
Who the Nether cares?
Okay, Nether Maniacs, you guys are in booth five.
Is that a freakin' beacon?
They have a freakin' beacon?
Freakin' beacon?
That's stained glass.
They aren't just building a beacon.
They're building a rainbow beacon.
Our design is way cooler.
A gigantic Enderman is better than a fancy light.
Their difficulty score is going to be higher than our total
score.
We've got something they don't.
Fireworks.
We should probably stop staring at them.
Look, it's the Order of the Losers again.
Good one, Gil.
We're just looking.
There'll be plenty of time for you all to look at it after
it wins and gets shown at Endercon.
You're being unpleasant.
Maybe not all of you.
Endercon doesn't allow outside food or drink.
Shut up.
What's that?
Jesse said shut up.
Do you need to hear it again?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Stop wasting your time, Aiden.
We've got work to do.
You're lucky I'm busy.
Hey, Jesse.
Guys.
Hey, Petra.
How's the build going?
Only time will tell, but we're optimistic.
Hey, Petra.
I forgot to thank you for that Nether Star.
Hey, Lukas.
Not a problem.
You help these tools?
For the right price, I'll help anyone.
If you need anything, you know where to find me.
None of us know where to find you.
Exactly.
No hard feelings, guys.
If you're cool with Petra, you're cool with us.
So why don't we just forget about all this and, you know,
make this about how cool our builds are?
Thanks.