Call it whatever you want. As long as we don't look at
them, we'll be fine. Yeah
Yeah, we might want to hold off on the grammar lessons
until later. Which way are we headed Jesse?
Stuff like that doesn't work in the nether probably not the
end either
Great
Man, so we were trapped and now we're lost at least we're
alive
well
Yeah
We just have to keep on trucking till we get to soren
Face it Jesse
We might never find this guy. There is
That has to be soren who else would build a staircase in
the end
We gotta go everyone follow me I'll get us to the other side
It's not a good idea
Jesse's right
Actually, you know what I'll just go
Give me a chance just say the word and I'll do it