The Witherstorms are already chasing us. If we just get them to chase us to your fortress again...
They'll be caught between a rock and a hard place!
Just one problem. You're forgetting about the command block!
Ugh, yes. It's clear now that no weapon can destroy it. Not even a Formita bomb.
Yes, well, I created a failsafe.
What kind of failsafe, exactly?
An enchanting book. One that contains the power of the command block itself.
Use it to enchant a weapon, and you'll be able to smash the command block to bits. Forever!
Yes. Yes, that's it!
What?
Ivor!
It is you!
Good to see you too, Magnus.
It just keeps coming for us.
Guys, there's a reason it's been following us. Ivor says it's because of the amulet that Gabriel...
We aren't safe. Not as long as we have that amulet.
I'll take it. I'll keep the Witherstorms busy. You guys do what you gotta do.
Axel, thank you.
You just go make that super weapon. I'll meet you back at Soren's fortress.
Well, Axel shouldn't have to do this alone. I'm coming with you, man.
Nice.
Well, I'm going with Jesse. I pledge to help, and that's what I must do.
Everyone, take good care of yourselves.
Hey, Jesse. Let's try our handshake again, just once for the road.