We know for a fact that wither storm will follow the ambulance.
So if we take the amulet back to your fortress where the endermen are...
We'll lead them straight into a massive trap!
Just one problem. You're forgetting about the command block.
Ugh, yes. It's clear now that no weapon can destroy it. Not even a formidable.
Yes, well, I created a failsafe.
What kind of failsafe exactly?
An enchanting book. One that contains the power of the command block itself.
Use it to enchant a weapon, and you'll be able to smash the command block to bits. Forever!
Yes. Yes, that's it!
What?
Ivor! It is you!
Good to see you too, Magnus.
It just keeps coming for us.
Guys, there's a reason it's been following us. Ivor says it's because of the amulet that Gabriel...
The point is we need to get moving. We aren't safe. Not as long as we have that amulet.
I'll take it. I'll keep the wither storms busy. You guys do what you gotta do.
Axel, thank you.
You just go make that super weapon. I'll meet you back at Soren's fortress.
Well, Axel shouldn't have to do this alone. I'm coming with you, man.
Nice.
Well, I'm going with Jesse. I pledge to help, and that's what I must do.
Everyone take good care of yourselves.
Hey, Jesse. Let's try our handshake again, just once for the road.