Guys, check it out. We use the pistons and some redstone to build a flying machine.
Then when I'm high enough, I ignite the TNT and blast myself into the wither storm.
Heck yeah! I love that idea.
So what are we waiting for? Let's hurry up and...
Look out!
Axle!
No!
I can't hold on!
I got you!
Lucas! You're here!
Ocelots, distract that wither storm!
Hey you! Get a load of this!
Lucas, thank you.
Anything for us, right?
Now let's hurry up and build this thing.
Okay, it's finished.
Quick, climb on!
And Jesse, I know you can do this.
We all do.
Thanks guys. It means a lot.
Now go to walls that command block.
Ruben, this is no place for a...
Wow!
No!
There it is.
We meet again, command block.
Now it's time to destroy you.
Ruben, I think we made it angry.
It's doing everything it can to protect the command block.
I'm going to get you, Ruben.
Awesome weapon, don't fail me now.
Holy moly!
At least they won't die!
Ruben, whatever happens, we have to destroy that command block.
Wait a second, I know exactly how to get up there.
The tractor beams!
Hey, you!