Guys, check it out. We build a cobblestone ramp, lay down
some track,
attach the TNT to the minecart, and launch it off the ramp
like a rocket!
Heck yeah! I love that idea!
So what are we waiting for? Let's hurry up and...
Oh, look out!
Petra!
Axel!
I can't... hold on!
I got you!
Lucas! You're here!
Ocelots, distract that wither storm!
Hey you! Get a load of this!
Lucas, thank you.
Anything for a friend.
Now let's hurry up and build this thing!
Okay, it's finished.
Quick, climb on!
Jesse, you can do this. I know you can.
We all do.
Thanks, guys. It means a lot.
Now go to walls that command block.
Okay, let's go.
Ruben, this is no place for a...
Big...
Aaaaaah!
No!
Wow.
There it is.
We meet again, command block.
Now it's time to destroy you.
Ruben, I think we made it angry.
It's doing everything it can to protect the command block.
We're gonna have to be careful.
I'm gonna go get the others.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Alright.
It's doing everything it can to protect the command block.
Awesome weapon, don't fail me now.
Holy moly!
At least they won't die!
Ah!
Ruben, whatever happens, we have to destroy that command
block.
Wait a second, I know exactly how to get up there.
The tractor beam!
Hey, you!
I'm sorry.