Guys, check it out. We build a cobblestone ramp, lay down some track, attach the TNT to the minecart, and launch it off the ramp like a rocket!
Heck yeah! I love that idea!
So what are we waiting for? Let's hurry up and...
Oh, look out!
Axle!
I can't hold on!
I got you!
Lucas! You're here!
Ocelots, distract that wither storm!
Hey you! Get a load of this!
Lucas, thank you!
Anything for a friend.
Now let's hurry up and build this thing!
Okay, it's finished!
Quick, climb on!
And Jesse, I know you can do this.
We all do.
Thanks guys.
It's a lot.
Now go demolish that command block.
Ruben, there's no place for ruben.
Wow.
No!
There it is.
We meet again, command block.
Now it's time to destroy you.
Ruben, I think we made it angry.
It's doing everything it can to protect the command block.
Awesome weapon, don't fail me now.
I'll finish you off.
Holy moly!
Still time!
Ruben, whatever happens, we have to destroy that command block.
Wait a second, I know exactly how to get up there.
The tractor beam!
Hey you!