Guys, check it out. Use the Pistons, the Redstone, and the TNT to build a TNT launcher.
Then I climb on and you guys blast me all the way into the Witherstorm.
Heck yeah! I love that idea.
So what are we waiting for? Let's hurry up and...
Oh, look out!
Axle!
No!
I can't hold on!
I got you!
Lucas! You're here!
Ocelots, distract that Witherstorm!
Hey you! Get a load of this!
Lucas, thank you. Anything for a friend.
Okay. Now let's hurry up and build this thing.
Okay, it's finished.
Quick, climb on!
And Jesse, I know you can do this.
We all do.
Thanks guys. It means a lot.
Now go demolish that command block.
Ruben, this is no place for a...
Please!
Wow.
There it is.
We meet again, command block.
Now it's time to destroy you.
Ruben, I think we made it angry.
It's doing everything it can to protect the command block.
Awesome weapon. Don't fail me now.
Ruben, whatever happens, we have to destroy that command block.
Wait a second, I know exactly how to get up there.
The tractor beams!
Hey you!