We need Gabriel to get Lukas back.
And to deal with everything else we saw down there.
We're doing the right thing, Jesse.
I just hope Lukas can hold out against that golem for long enough for us to get help.
Come on, then.
Let's crash this party.
With the right training, and guidance, anyone... and I mean anyone can become a hero.
You just have to believe it.
I want you to look me in the eyes.
We've just gotta push through this crowd to get to Gabriel.
Start. Believing. It.
And then...
Now I'd like to open up the floor for a few questions.
Keep it orderly, folks.
Aaaaand -- you, right there in the front row.
You know when uh... Ellegaard... and the dragon... umm... like what was her favorite food?
Bread. Next question.
What question do you have for the mighty Gabriel?
Every person here is in danger!
Now, hold on just a minute. If this is a joke, it isn't funny.
I'm not joking -- somebody's been building a monster in the basement.
Hmm. Perhaps we should have this checked out...
I have a question for you.
Excuse me, sir -- you'll have to wait your turn!
Just tell me first: do you really believe anyone can be great?
With enough hard work -- yes!
Was that where I went wrong? I simply didn't WORK hard enough?
Ivor?
That's the guy who attacked us in the basement!
I wish I could say I was surprised.
If it's surprises you want, you're in for a treat.
Why don't you tell them the real story, Gabriel?
I see time has made you bitter.
And it's made YOU an even bigger fool.
Now, these people were promised greatness -- and I'm ready to deliver.
I'm sorry this is how they had to learn the truth...