Go and find the others. Hopefully you can find a way to get
down to me or something.
Time to be a hero again.
Stay safe. I'll find a way down to you.
Hey, show yourself. Who's there?
You. Trying to interfere with my plans again, I see.
What are you doing down here?
Being rudely interrupted by you, clearly.
I'm here with the order to find Soren's super TNT.
We're going to take down your wither storm.
I'm going to take down your wither storm.
Super TNT, we're going to take down your wither storm.
The order? Believe me, that plan will blow up in their
faces in more ways than one.
They cannot help you. But me? I choose not to.
Sorry, Ivor. I'm...
Stop right there, Ivor!
Gabriel! You're alive!
Against all your best efforts, Ivor. Look at what you've
done.
I never dreamt that even you could be this twisted.
Save your posturing, Gabriel.
We both know that words have always been hollow, just like
the order.
They're not going anywhere, Ivor. At least not in one piece.
Your threats pass harmlessly through me, but this sword
will pass through you.