That is like the perfect warmup for when we get to Boomtown.
Boomtown?
Yeah! Boomtown!
This is it.
I, uh, I think I'm gonna hold off on the whole going first
thing for a while, Jesse.
How about you take this one?
Yeah.
Careful, okay? We're on the step.
Whoa! You see that? Utter chaos, man.
Your loot is mine, friggin'!
You'll have to catch me first, Mammoth.
Whoa! Um, I hope they're okay.
And if they're not, at least they died doing what they
loved.
Well, here you have it, Jesse.
Boomtown in all its glory. What do you think?
Wow, Boomtown sure does keep you on your toes. Exciting
stuff, huh?
Yeah, yeah, now you're getting it.
Dude, it's freaking glowing.
Dude, I think you're on fire.
Dude, I think you're on to something there.