Meeting Gabriel would be a dream and an honor!
Totally, he’s awesome!
It’d be amazing to meet him!
Reuben better be careful in that costume.
Last time Gabriel saw a dragon, it didn’t end well.
Sooo… Does this “source” of yours make posters for a living?
Huh?
Yeah… my source… doesn’t exist.
You guys are my only friends.
Guys let’s stay focused, we have a competition to win.
We never win, and this year we’ve got Reuben with us.
We're going to win. Because...
What are you talking about?
Because up to now we've hated losing.
But today, today my friends, we're going to start learning how to love winning...
That didn't sound as good as it did in my head.
No, no. I'm with that.
All right.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute! We’re thinking about this all WRONG!
The point of the building competition isn’t just to BUILD something!
We have to DO something to get noticed by the judges!
Okay, then. So how do we do this?
We don’t just build something functional.
We build something FUN!
After we finish the fireworks machine like we planned, we then build something cool on top of it!
You might be onto something!
If you wanna get a reaction out of the judges, you need to build something scary.
So I say we build a creeper!
Wouldn’t an enderman be better?
I’m more scared of endermen than creepers.