It's not that big of a deal. Endercon will be fun either
way.
What? Hold on. Let me try that again.
What?
He's right, Jesse. Incredibly. This is a huge deal.
So, does this source of yours make posters for a living?
Huh?
Yeah, my source doesn't exist. You guys are my only friends.
Guys, let's stay focused. We have a competition to win.
We never win. And this year we've got Reuben with us.
We're going to win because...
What are you talking about?
Because up to now, we've hated losing. But today, today, my
friends,
we're going to start learning how to love winning.
That didn't sound as good as it did in my head.
No, no. I'm with that.
All right.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. We're thinking about this all
wrong.
The point of the building competition isn't just to build
something.
We have to do something to get noticed by the judges.
Okay then. So how do we do this?
We don't just build something functional. We build
something fun.
After we finish the fireworks machine like we planned,
then we build something cool on top of it.
You might be on to something.
If we want to get a reaction out of the judges, you build
something scary.
So I say we build a creeper.
Wouldn't an Enderman be better?
I'm more scared of Endermen than creepers.
They both have their moments. They're both pretty scary.
You