He wasn't on the map.
I'm very curious to see it.
I've never actually seen it work before.
Alright, there's your light, my light.
That's new.
There he is.
Sorin had his fortress deep inside the mountains.
After the order broke up, that's where he went to keep
doing his experiments.
Look, he invited me there a couple times, but it always
seemed a little...
Weird, right? It always seemed a little weird.
Then let's stop hanging around here and go get us some
super TNT.
Whoa.
Blue?
Blue? That's Ivor!
Ivor is going to Sorin's. We need to move.
It's not too far. We could probably make it on foot.
Righteous! We'll get some rest and head out first thing in
the morning,
avoiding all the no time and monsters and everything.
If you had seen that monster, you wouldn't be saying that.
We need to leave, now!
Yeah, I don't want the Witherstorm catching up with us. We
should go now.
I'm sorry.
Okay, everyone, let's get moving.
Yo, we haven't really gotten a chance to chat yet.
Oh, hello.
I heard you saved your friend back there from this
Witherstorm thing.
Pretty tough, huh?
I'm just doing my best to keep everyone safe.
Humility? Nice. I can dig it.
What's the deal with your buddy Axel?
Can't tell if he's awesome or a little bit of a dork.
He's just a little, uh, doofy, you know?
He's like a little puppy.
You don't know whether you want to hug it or just walk away.
You know what I'm talking about?