I bet we can find him. I'm very curious to see it. I've
never actually seen it work before
All right, there's your light my light
That's new
There he is
Sorin had his fortress deep inside the mountains after the
order broke up. That's where he went to keep doing his
experiments
Look, he invited me there a couple times, but it always
seemed a little weird, right? It always seemed a little
weird
Then let's stop hanging around here and go get us some
super TNT
I
Bore is going to soren's we need to move
It's not too far we could probably make it on foot
righteous get some rest and head out first thing in the
morning avoiding all the
Monsters
If you had seen that monster, you wouldn't be saying that
we need to leave now
Yeah, I don't want the weather storm catching up with us.
We should go now
Okay
Everyone let's get moving
Yo, we haven't really gotten a chance to chat yet. Oh
Hello, I heard you saved your friend back there from this
wither storm thing. You're pretty tough, huh?
I'm just doing my best to keep everyone safe
Humility nice. I can dig it
What's the deal with your buddy Axel?
Can't tell if he's awesome or a little bit of a dork
He's just a little
Doofy, you know
Little puppy you don't know whether you want to hug it or
just walk away
You know what I'm talking about