Just don't lose it this time, okay?
Hey, don't worry about me. I got this.
You just keep them distracted.
At the top!
Love a good table turning. Excellent.
So you just keep right here!
I'm not losing!
Well, hello opportunity.
Jesse, we made it!
You don't need to sound so surprised.
Do you have the amulet?
Of course. Me and the pig, we totally rocked it.
Good boy, Ruben. Magnus, here we come.
You are completely surrounded by hundreds of hidden death
traps.
One step closer, and...
It's Magnus! We totally got caught by Magnus!
I think we're gonna die now.
Did you really think you could sneak up on me?
You're two of the worst grievers I've ever met.
And a pig?
Really? Hardly, Stoathe.
Oh yeah? Well, I'm going going to you, poor chop.
I'm going to you.