Actually, no offense, but I'm not letting this thing out of
my sight or my hand ever again.
Don't worry, man, I got this.
Okay, well hurry. I'll try and cover you.
Guys! Hey, guys, I've got the ambulance.
Hey! I hate all the things that guy's saying! It makes me
so mad!
Come on!
Oh, boy!
Jesse, you made it!
You don't need to sound so surprised.
Everything go okay?
Long story. Lots of throwing eggs at griefers.
Well, sounds exciting.
Totally was. You still got the amulet?
Yep, let's go. Look out for booby traps, okay?
Oh!
You were completely surrounded by hundreds of hidden death
traps.
One step closer, and...
It's madness! We totally got caught by madness!
Ah, oh. I think we're gonna die now.
Did you really think you could sneak up on me?
Ha! You're two of the worst griefers I've ever met.
And a pig? Really? Hardly stealthy.
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm going going to you, pork chop!