This isn't your fault. It's Ivor's who wouldn't do
something stupid for a diamond
But without my help Ivor wouldn't have wouldn't have wanted
revenge on Gabriel
Believe me. He would have found another way. I'm gonna do
everything I can to make this right
Petra I know this isn't easy to hear but you're too sick to
be going anywhere. I'm not that sick
Maybe you should rest in this cave for a while. I mean it's
safe
Defensible I say I'm fine then I'm
Fine
You staying here is the right move
You'll never get better if we keep pushing you but I want
to be there for you guys. I know you do and you will
Maybe you're right. It's the right call Jesse. I hope so.
We didn't all make it back though
Guys it was my fault
I'm the one who took Magnus's armor, but you couldn't have
known what was going to happen
She's right. You can't blame yourself. Jesse. I'm surprised
he lasted as long as he did
Being emotional is getting us nowhere
What I want to know is what happened out there today? Why
is that thing still alive?
The formidable just wasn't strong enough. I mean it ripped
the wither storm apart, but it didn't make a dent in the
command block
So the command block is still out there. Oh
Great
Look our plan didn't work. So we obviously need a new one
Question is what do we do?
Why are you asking me am I expected to know every last
thing in the universe?
Huh? I need a moment to think
Is he always like this you have no idea?
That jacket I recognize it
Lucas always wears that jacket. No, there were other people
wearing that very same jacket when I was thrown from the
monster
It hurts just to think about just put it out of your mind
Jesse if what Gabriel said is true, I
Mean do you think I thought for sure they were gone, but if
they were just trapped in the wither storm
You