There's no way you could have known what would happen. No one's ever seen anything like this.
Still, I'm gonna do everything I can to make this right.
Petra, I know this isn't easy to hear, but you're too sick to be going anywhere.
I'm not that sick.
Maybe you should rest in this cave for a while. I mean, it's safe, defensible.
If you say I'm fine, then I'm... fine.
You staying here is the right move. You'll never get better if we keep pushing you.
But I want to be there for you guys.
I know you do, and you will.
Maybe you're right. It's the right call, Jesse.
I hope so.
We didn't all make it back, though.
Guys, it was my fault.
I'm the one who took Magnus's armor.
But you couldn't have known what was going to happen.
She's right. You can't blame yourself, Jesse.
I'm surprised he lasted as long as he did.
Being emotional is getting us nowhere!
What I want to know is what happened out there today. Why is that thing still alive?
The Formidabomb just wasn't strong enough.
I mean, it ripped the witherstorm apart, but it didn't make a dent in the command block.
So the command block is still out there?
Oh, great.
Look, our plan didn't work, so we obviously need a new one.
The question is, what do we do?
Why are you asking me?
Am I expected to know every last thing in the universe?
I need a moment to think.
Is he always like this?
You have no idea.
That jacket! I recognize it!
Lucas always wears that jacket.
No. There were other people wearing that very same jacket when I was thrown from the monster.
It hurts just to think about it.
Just put it out of your mind.
Jesse, if what Gabriel said is true...
I mean, do you think?
I thought for sure they were gone, but if they were just trapped in the witherstorm...