I don't know, he disappeared outside the witch's hut!
Curse that fool of a man.
Come on!
Guys, I think we lost them for...
Wow!
You lost them for wow?
What is that?
Oh... wow.
It's like we're at the edge of the world.
Actually, we seem to be at the corner of it.
Welcome to the Far Lands, my friend.
I'm glad Jesse snagged this cake.
Makes the whole wall of insanity thing a lot easier to face.
Say what you like about witches.
They sure know how to make a cake.
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Sworn, have you been here before?
Not here specifically, but I have visited the Far Lands.
The Order traveled far and wide during our heyday.
How can Ivor live here?
I mean, it's one thing to build a wall world inside the End,
but this...
Oh, I doubt he lives here.
He most likely comes here only for his most secretive research.
Whatever Ivor is hiding in here, it will be extremely well guarded.
This way, I suspect.
I'd feel better about this if the rest of our group was with us.
Come on!
Is this... a maze?
It would appear so.
A massive one from the looks of it.
If Ivor used the command block to build this, it could hold unspeakable peril.
Why do I sense that entering this maze is a good idea?
I'm not sure.