Eligard, I can't. This armor belongs to you.
You earned it, Jesse.
Well, Zoran, at least I finally got to be a real hero,
right?
All those people, they're alive. The Witherstorm didn't
kill them.
Jesse, those people, you have to help them. All of them.
Of course I'll save them. Every one of them.
We're the good guys, right? That's what we do.
Come on, Ruben. We've got a job to do.
You guys help the survivors.
I need to make sure we find the people who might be trapped.
Don't worry. It's all over now. My friends are gonna help
you.
Thank you. Thank you.
You're gonna be okay, I promise.
I... thank you.
No! The command block, that's impossible!
I don't understand. Zoran said the Formidabomb would
destroy it, but it... it looks fine.
What the...
Guys, over here!
No! No!
Somebody, help!
But... I thought you were dead, I saw you!
What happened here?
I'll explain everything, just not right now.
Come on, we've gotta get out of here!
Gabriel, let's go!
Who's Gabriel?