If we stick together we can do anything even something that
feels impossible
It just feels extra impossible now, then we stick together
extra hard
Okay, I kind of wish Gabriel would tell everybody it would
just make things easier
I kind of need to get at that lever you're blocking
I think I found the way out
Thanks, yep
That's weird
Hey everyone, I think I found soren's way out
Oh
No, I'm fine if I wasn't fine could I do this
We'll see what we can find in the rest of the house
Just hope we don't discover soren as he's getting ready for
bed
He's wore the most
revealing bathrobes
Let's see what's going on behind this door
Oh
It's just a recording
After all that he's not even here
We came all this way and for what
We're no closer to soren than before