It just means you gotta step up more than you have already,
okay?
Okay.
I kinda wish Gabriel would tell everybody.
It would just make things... easier.
I kinda need to get at that lever you're blocking.
Really?
Thanks. Yep.
That's... weird.
Hey everyone, I think I found Soren's way out!
Oh no, I'm fine. If I wasn't fine, could I do this?
We'll see what we can find in the rest of the house.
I just hope we don't discover Soren as he's getting ready
for bed.
He always wore the most... revealing bathrobes.
Let's see what's going on behind this door.
And I call that one Symphony in E.
A new composition to celebrate my newest discovery.
To celebrate my newest discovery!
That's him!
In time, I observed one other block on top of another block.
What the?
It's just a recording.
A time of undeniable intelligence.
I hope I'm not imagining things.
After all that, he's not even here?
I better eat something.
We came all this way and for what?
We're no closer to Soren than before.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.