You know, that stunt your friend pulled really hurt my pig.
Okay, maybe, but I had nothing to do with that.
Hey, you didn't happen to see a creepy guy with a long hair and a beard roaming around, did you?
I don't think so... why?
He kinda scammed Petra out of a diamond earlier.
Whoa -- everyone knows, you don't mess with Petra.
Not if you know what's good for you.
I'll keep a eye out, okay?
Thanks, I appreciate it
So, uh, we're cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
Cool, cool.
Ha! See you later, Lukas.
Yeah. See ya.
Thought you could just wiggle right out of that trap, didn't you?
Well -- Wiggle as much as you want -- you're not goin' anywhere
Axel, listen up -- any chance you've seen a creepy-looking beard-y guy anywhere?
No, but Petra told me what happened -- I'm keeping an eye out for him.
Okay, so I got a little distracted.
It's just this machine presses all my buttons -- unnecessarily complicated, and mean to birds for no reason.
Stop messing around -- we need your help
I was looking, I swear -- I've just got a short attention span.
Have you seen Reuben? I was hoping he might've made it to town while I was distracted.
Haven't seen hide nor hair. But I'm sure he's fine. He's a tough little ham.
Axel?
All right, all right. I'll look.
After I watch one more chicken get owned.
Ha! I see you now, weirdo...
Well, if it isn't Team Trashbag! How's your stupid pig?
I'm busy right now, man.
What? Busy trying to get a life? Busy trying to find some friends?
Hey!
Hey! Where do you think you're --
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Get away from me!
I said I was sorry.
Reuben? Is that you?!
Nothing sticks to your ribs quite like a juicy pork chop!
Reuben!
What's the big idea? I'm trying to run a business here.
That's my pig! You kidnapped my pig!
Well, I don't know what you're talking about, Chief. I found this pig wandering alone in the streets.
Please. He's my friend.
To me, he's inventory.
I might be amenable to some kind of trade...
Not that you look like you've got much of value. I gotta get some kind of return on my investment.