Try not to touch anything until we know what it does, okay?
I wasn't gonna touch anything. I was just going to look
really carefully
Come on. Let's keep moving
Seems like this place is really blowing you away. You're
not kidding. This is like everything I've ever dreamed of
This is just like I dreamt it entering Ella guards
laboratory seeing her right there
She'll ask me to be her apprentice and the next thing you
know, we'll be changing the world together
Let's just try to save the world first. Whoa. Hi. Hey
didn't see you sneaking up on me. Guess that's the point
Don't touch anything in here. Okay, it's all supremely
fragile and genius
Didn't Calvin send you you my new assistance?
New assistance with a stupidly adorable pig that is
Jesse she thinks we're her new assistance
This is so exciting