This isn't your fault. It's Ivor's who wouldn't do something stupid for a diamond
But without my help Ivor wouldn't have wouldn't have wanted revenge on Gabriel
Believe me. He would have found another way. I'm gonna do everything I can to make this right
Petra I know this isn't easy to hear but you're too sick to be going anywhere. I'm not that sick
Maybe you should rest in this cave for a while. I mean it's safe
Defensible if I say I'm fine, then I'm
Fine
You staying here is the right move
You'll never get better if we keep pushing you but I want to be there for you guys. I know you do and you will
Maybe you're right. It's the right call Jesse. I hope so. We didn't all make it back though
Guys it was my fault
I'm the one who took elegant armor
But you couldn't have known what was going to happen
She's right. Don't blame yourself kid. Hi. Yeah, never blame myself for anything
Being emotional is getting us nowhere
What I want to know is what happened out there today? Why is that thing still alive?
The formidable just wasn't strong enough. I mean it ripped the wither storm apart, but it didn't make a dent in the command block
So the command block is still out there. Oh
Great
Look our plan didn't work. So we obviously need a new one
Question is what do we do?
Why are you asking me am I expected to know every last thing in the universe?
Huh? I need a moment to think
Is he always like this? Do you have no idea?
That jacket I recognize it
Lucas always wears that jacket. No, there were other people wearing that very same jacket when I was thrown from the monster
It hurts just to think about hey, it's okay
Hey
Jesse if what Gabriel said is true, I
Mean do you think I thought for sure they were gone, but if they were just tracked in the wither storm