Go and find the others. Hopefully you can find a way to get
down to me or something.
Okay, I got this. Stay safe. I'll find a way down to you.
Hey, show yourself. Who's there?
You. Trying to interfere with my plans again, I see.
What are you doing down here?
Being rudely interrupted by you, clearly.
I'm here with the order to find Soren's super TNT. We're
going to take down your wither storm.
The order? Believe me, that plan will blow up in their
faces in more ways than one.
They cannot help you. But me? I choose not to.
Sorry, Ivor.
You're not going anywhere.
Petra, you escaped?
I'm not going anywhere.
Foolish girl!
Shut up! I don't care what you have to say. I'm just going
to take you down.