Hey, thanks for grabbing that.
Not a problem.
Hang on a minute.
He's close.
Soren's close by.
He's gotta be...
this way.
Look how bright it is!
Sounds like the grinder is packed up.
With loot?
Go, go, go, go, go!
Ah!
Whoa!
Keep moving!
Have to look out!
Keep down,ounty!
I'm coming, buddy!
I have had enough of this!
Take that!
Get your face fired!
There's two things I hate.
It's running and monsters.
A key portal?
That's the way out.
Wait!
What?
Look!
Oh no!
Petra!
Get away from them!
Yah!
Get in your face, monsters!
I think I'm starting to get the hang of this.
Here we go!
Jump!
I'm coming!
Oh, great.
Just keeps getting better.
Where's Axel?
He was right behind me.
Boo!
See?
I told you I'd pay you back.
Get off!
Oh, jeez.
Are you hurt?
What?
No, I'm not crying, just look!
So, uh...
What do we call that?
A herd of Endermen?
A flock of Endermen?
A swarm?