Hello boomtown, how we all doing, huh?
Hey, that's awesome
So proud standing in front of you all today. Well you guys
ready then
Wait, what's going on? Oh, well, that's not good
Help me!
What are we?
Go, red messing boomtown, go!
Okay, just a little farther
Wow, someone really went bonkers with the defenses, huh?
Who goes there? Oh, Jesse?
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Who goes there? Oh, Jesse? Is that you?
Lucas, did you build all of this?
Well, yeah, I figured I would try and fortify the place,
you know?
Nice!
Quick, come on, you guys are never gonna believe who showed
up while you were gone
Petra!
Hey guys, how's it going?
What? What? What? What?
Petra, you made it!
It's good to see you too, big guy
And it's really good to see you, Jesse
Back there in Gabriel's bunker, it got pretty dicey
You