I'm not gonna lie man, but we've pulled through worse, right?
Have we?
How's it going?
Tell me Jesse who is this person?
He keeps insulting me
That right there is Magnus. Everyone knows Magnus
Magnus
How do I know him exactly you guys defeated the Ender dragon together the most fearsome creature this land has ever seen
Really?
Really? You're kind of a big deal. It isn't working
He doesn't remember talk to him about your past something only you would know about
Like what talk about fighting the Ender dragon. No, no, no, no anything but that. Come on. It's what you're famous for
Well, all right then
the Ender dragon you see it was huge and dangerous and
And for a while there it looked like we were goners, but you know who stepped in and killed that thing
Was it Jesse? Huh? No, it was you man. You killed it. Oh
Thank you for sharing that with me and Jesse. Thank you, too. You've been a big help here
I need to repay your kindness
I'm not sure how exactly
But I want to express my gratitude