I've got Petra!
Then I'll take Gabriel!
Hold on, this might be a bumpy ride.
Come on, horses!
Whatever you do, don't look back!
Ah! I look!
Watch out!
It's gaining on us!
It's coming after us!
Kick-locker!
Make it stop, please!
Doing the best I can.
Jesse, look out!
I'm going to get you!
Have I seen Enderman attack a weatherstorm?
Enderman move blocks. It's what they do.
There! We can hide over there!
Guys, come on!
We've got to build a new one, like right now.
Come on, faster!
I saw your screaming in my ear!
Sorry.
We made it! We actually freaking made it!
Hey, how are you feeling?
I don't really feel like myself.
I still can't believe you're even alive.
Do you not recognize us?
I'm Axel. This is Olivia.
We've been friends for a really long time.