Everything in the universe starts out as just a block.
What comes of those blocks is up to those who wield them.
Our friends have traveled far and wide in search of the Order of the Stone
and a way to stop the wither storm for good.
But even well-laid plans can go awry.
The threat to this world, to its very existence, is far from over.
Go!
Where... where am I? What's happening?
Come on, I'm gonna get you out of here.
Do I... know you?
Jassby, Jassby, where are you?
We're coming!
No way, no way!
Get up, Petra.
Who is Petra?
I'm gonna get you out of here.
This way!
Jassby, you made it!
Petra?
You're missing friend.
Look out!
Those Endermen are running the wrong way! They'll be killed!
Soren, what do you think you're doing?
These Endermen are running directly into danger.
You're putting us in danger every second you just stand there.
Now!
Jassby! They're falling behind!
Axel, you gotta move faster!
He's too sick. That's the best we can do.
They're not gonna be able to outrun him. Not on foot!
We just need to get them moving faster.
Bingo!
Everybody, get on!
Go!
Wait, what about us?
Come on, Jassby, we got this!
We'll take the reins, and they can just hang on.