Everyone, just hold on to me. I'll guide us through them.
I guess if this is the only way we're gonna make it back to
the trap door...
Maybe we should, uh, turn around... or not.
This guy's right in my base.
Oh, when I constructed this place, I worried about how
flammable my building material was.
So I installed a fire suppression system to prevent the
whole thing from going up in flames.
So there's more water?
Much more. If we activate it, it could disperse all these
endermen while we swim to safety.
Can we reach the controls from here?
The lever! It's right up there!
Yeesh.
I don't know how much water this thing is gonna kick out,
so everybody...
It's working!
Well done, Jesse! Now, time to swim to that trap door!
We made it!
Making it is relative.
Oh, come on!
Not that this isn't a ton of fun, but grab that permitted
bomb and get out of here!
One small problem. Tiny. Really?
I haven't actually built it yet.
That's a small problem?
You seem like a person who appreciates cool stuff that's
cool for no reason.
Thanks?
Go ahead and throw that lever behind you!
Hold on to your socks, because they're about to get blown
off!
Go to work, boys!
Ouch! Yikes!