Petra can take care of herself you just worry about you
you're hiding something
and by not telling me the truth you are putting all of us
in danger why don't you
go back to looking for soren I know you're sick of talking
to me
I kind of need to get at that lever you're blocking fine
that wasn't too hard wasn't walking one foot to the left
nope I think I got that
covered that's weird
hey everyone I think I found soren's way out
nope don't want it don't need it thanks we'll check out the
rest of the house
see if we can find soren before he finds us
let's see what's going on behind this door
so
And I call that one Symphony in E. A new composition to
celebrate my newest discovery.
That's him!
In time, I observe one place of block on top of another
block.
What the?
It's just a recording.
After all that, he's not even here?
We came all this way and for what?
We're no closer to Soren than before.