Just...run.
Run where? You don't think I tried that already?
Now Lukas! Run!
Nice one, Rueben!
Okay Jesse, come on! Let's go!
Thanks for coming for me! I didn't know if anybody was going to…
No man left behind. That's my motto.
Guess I owe you one.
Where are the others?
Dude, I dunno how can I be any clearer!
Weird guy! Doing weird stuff! Freaky with a side of strange!
Why won't you listen to me? What do you want me to do? Tell you charades-style?
I promise you, that's the last thing I want you to do.
Four words; six syllabes; sounds like... Schmonster in the schmasement".
Next.
Wait, just --
I have a question for you.
Excuse me, sir -- you'll have to wait your turn!
Just tell me first: do you really believe anyone can be great?
With enough hard work -- yes!
Was that where I went wrong? I simply didn't WORK hard enough?
Ivor?
That's the guy who attacked us in the basement!
I wish I could say I was surprised.
If it's surprises you want, you're in for a treat.
Why don't you tell them the real story, Gabriel?
I see time has made you bitter.
And it's made YOU an even bigger fool.
Now, these people were promised greatness -- and I'm ready to deliver.
I'm sorry this is how they had to learn the truth...