You know that stunt your friend pulled really hurt my pig.
Okay, maybe, but I had nothing to do with that.
Hey, you didn't happen to see a creepy guy with long hair
and a beard roaming around, did you?
I don't think so. Why?
He kinda scammed Petra out of a diamond earlier.
Whoa, everyone knows you don't mess with Petra.
I don't know what's good for you.
I'll keep an eye out, okay?
Thanks, I appreciate it.
So, uh, we're cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
Cool, cool.
See you later, Lukas.
Yeah, see ya.
I thought you could just wiggle right out of that trap,
didn't you?
Well, wiggle as much as you want.
You're not going anywhere.
Axel, listen up. Any chance you've seen a creepy-looking,
beardy guy anywhere?
No. Petra told me what happened.
I'm keeping an eye out for him.
Okay, so I got a little distracted.
It's just this machine presses all my buttons.
Unnecessarily complicated, mean to birds for no reason.
Stop messing around. We need your help.
I was looking, I swear.
I've just got a short attention span.
Alright, alright, I'll look.
After I watch one more chicken ghetto.
I see you now, weirdo.
Wow, if it isn't Team Trashback.
How's your stupid pig?
I'm busy right now, man.
What, busy trying to get a life?
Busy trying to find some friends?
Hey.
Hey, what do you think you're...
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Get away from me.
I said I was sorry.
Reuben, is that you?
Nothing sticks to your ribs quite like a juicy pork chop.
Reuben!
What's the big idea? I'm trying to run a business here.
That's my pig, you kidnapped my pig.
Well, I don't know what you're talking about, Chief.
I found this pig wandering alone in the streets.
Please, he's my friend.
To me, he's inventory.
I might be amenable to some kind of trade.
Not that you look like you got much of value.
I gotta get some kind of return on my investment.
Otherwise, it's straight to the slaughterhouse for this one.