We need to find a way for me to use this.
Whoa, that is, without question, the coolest thing I have ever, ever seen.
Oh, then I brought you some armor, Axel.
Here.
Nice! I was feeling a little left out.
Guys, let's go kick some command block butt.
Does anyone see the command block?
I don't think it's exposed.
We need to get out of here.
Command block? I don't think it's exposed.
We need to get more Endermen focused on the Winter Store.
How do you make Endermen focus? I can't even make myself focus.
We shouldn't be here. Not if this is going according to plan.
Soren, what are you doing?
I, uh, you know, I really enjoy meeting you all, but...
Soren!
Did Soren just run away?