We need to find a way for me to use this.
Whoa, that is, without question, the coolest thing I have
ever, ever seen.
Oh, and I brought you some armor, Axel.
Here.
Nice! I was feeling a little left out.
Guys, let's go kick some command block butt.
Woohoo!
Does anyone see the command block?
I don't think it's exposed!
We need to get out of here!
I'm not going to let you get away with this!
I'm going to get out of here!
Command block?
I don't think it's exposed!
We need to get more Endermen focused on the Winter Store!
How do you make Endermen focus? I can't even make myself
focus.
We shouldn't be here. None of this is going according to
plan.
Zorin? What are you doing?
I, uh, you know, I really enjoy meeting you all, but...
Zorin!
Did Zorin just run away?