Just keep your distance.
Jesse, come on. He was here all night.
No, it's okay. I'll take that.
All right, then. Let's head out.
Look at that thing.
What is it?
Let's get a closer look.
What?
What are we waiting for? Let's go.
What is this place?
That's what we're trying to figure out.
It's the Temple of the Order of the Stone.
Lukas, are you sure?
He's right, look.
Do you think they're in there?
Let's go in and find out.
Let's just all be careful.
Okay.
If you spot anything, call it out. We don't have a lot of
time.
Isn't it weird how dispensers are carved to look like
spooky little faces?
What do you dispense little guy?
I get the feeling that we don't really want to find out.
Get behind me.
What was that?
That's probably not a good thing.
Oh come on dispenser faces.
I thought we were friends.
Run!
We're trapped!
We activated the dispensers with that pressure plate.
If we can figure out a way to trigger it again, I bet
that'll shut them off.
There's a crafting table, maybe we can make something
useful.
Out of what? We don't have anything.
All of our tools and materials are back home.
Alright everyone, empty your pockets.
Let's see who we've got to work with.
I have a good idea.
Let's go.
Everyone empty your pockets.
Let's see who we've got to work with.
I have a few sticks left over from building the shelter
last night.
I've got some flint and a piece of string.
All I have are some chicken feathers I picked up after that
chicken machine exploded.
Let's see, I've got some flint, steel, sword.
Oh and some string from a spider that I fought in Windsor.
String, sticks, flint and feathers.
Let's go.