That's easy. I'll take the little tiny... little zombies.
A hundred of them... crawling all over you, with their tiny hands.
All I need is, like, a shovel. I'm telling you, way too easy.
Soo... I’ve got a daylight sensor on the roof... And if I did this right, these lamps should turn on once it gets dark.
I didn't want to just leave Reuben here with nothing while we're at the building competition.
He's coming with us.
Really?
What kind of question is that? Of course he is.
Okay. I'm not saying he shouldn't come. I'm not... but don't you think it's a little weird that you take him with you everywhere you go?
Reuben’s my best friend.
I thought I was your best friend.
Both of you are!
I didn’t mean anything by it. I’m glad he’s coming.
I just don’t wanna give people one more reason to call us “losers”.
Who CARES what other people think?!
I know, I just… it wears your down.
You say you’re not a loser, Olivia! So WIN!
Okay. Fine.
Do you hear that?
Oh, no.
Hahaha! Oh, man you guys totally freaked out! That was awe-
Axel! What’s the matter with you?!
Great. Now I’m gonna smell like a pig at Endercon.
I thought we were buddies!