I've got Petra!
Then I'll take Gabriel!
Hold on, this might be a bumpy ride.
Come on, horses!
Whatever you do, don't look back.
Ah! I look.
Watch it!
It's gaining on us!
No offense, but you can use a little practice.
First time on a horse here!
I'll turn around and see if it's gaining,
but it's all I can do to hold on.
Jesse, look out!
I'm going to get you!
Am I seeing Enderman attack a weatherstorm?
Enderman move floppies, it's what they do!
There! We need to get over there!
Guys, come on!
We've got to build a new one.
Right now.
Come on, faster!
I saw you screaming in my ear!
Sorry.
We made it!
We actually freaking made it!
Hey, how are you feeling?
I... I'm afraid I don't feel much like myself at the moment.
Gabriel!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Gabriel!
It really is you!
They told us you'd kicked it!
Who are you people?
It's me, Magnus!
Old friend, don't you recognize us?
It's Sorin.
We've known each other for a very long time.