You'll get your chance Gabriel, this fight isn't over yet.
Very well.
It was dark and foul, and I was sure I was a goner.
Well, you aren't. You made it back alive. Which is more
than I can say for some of us.
Magnus, for a second there, I almost managed to forget.
You guys talking about Magnus?
I still can't believe he's gone.
Guys, it was my fault.
I'm the one who took Magnus' armor.
But you couldn't have known what was going to happen.
She's right. You can't blame yourself, Jesse.
I'm surprised he lasted as long as he did.
Being emotional is getting us nowhere!
What I want to know is, what happened out there today? Why
is that thing still alive?
The Formidabomb just wasn't strong enough.
I mean, it ripped the Witherstorm apart, but it didn't make
a dent in the command block.
So the command block is still out there?
Oh, great.
Look, our plan didn't work, so we obviously need a new one.
The question is, what do we do?
Why are you asking me? Am I expected to know every last
thing in the universe?
I need a moment to think.
Is he always like this?
You have no idea.
That jacket! I recognize it!
Lucas always wears that jacket.
No. There were other people wearing that very same jacket
when I was thrown from the monster!
It hurts just to think about.
Just put it out of your mind.
Jesse, if what Gabriel said is true...
I mean, do you think?
I thought for sure they were gone, but if they were just
trapped in the Witherstorm...
I'm sure they're still there.