Doesn't matter how this started or who started it.
We just have to end it.
You're right. I know you're right.
I only wish I could continue to help.
It was dark and foul, and I was sure I was a goner.
Well, you aren't.
You made it back alive.
Which is more than I can say for some of us.
Oh, Magnus. For a second there, I almost managed to forget.
You guys talking about Magnus?
I still can't believe he's gone.
Guys, it was my fault.
I'm the one who took Magnus's armor.
But you couldn't have known what was going to happen.
She's right. You can't blame yourself, Jesse.
I'm surprised he lasted as long as he did.
Being emotional is getting us nowhere.
What I want to know is what happened out there today.
Why is that thing still alive?
The Formidabomb just wasn't strong enough.
I mean, it ripped the Witherstorm apart, but it didn't make
a dent in the command block.
So the command block is still out there?
Oh, great.
Look, our plan didn't work, so we obviously need a new one.
Question is, what do we do?
Why are you asking me?
Am I expected to know every last thing in the universe?
I need a moment to think.
Is he always like this?
You have no idea.
That jacket, it looks familiar.
Lucas always wears that jacket.
No, I saw other people wearing it when I was being thrown
from that dead monster.
Even thinking about it hurts.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
Jesse, if what Petra said is true...
I mean, do you think?
I thought for sure they were gone, but if they were just
trapped in the Witherstorm...