Well, at least we're back together.
Yes! The dream team reunited!
Now the dream team's just got to find a way across this gaping bottomless pit.
What about this thing? Could it get us across?
It's some kind of flying barge. It would probably get us to the other side.
But it's in really bad shape. And it's really complicated.
You can fix it though, right?
I don't know. I think it's out of my league.
Come on, you'll figure it out. You know you always do.
This layout doesn't even make any sense. What was I ever thinking?
Or maybe it's just me. I mean, Ellegard herself said I don't have what it takes to be a great engineer.
So prove her wrong. Show the world what you're made of.
Prove her wrong? Jesse, she was the greatest redstone engineer ever.
She was in the Order of the Stone.
Sure, but the Order are still people, just like us.
Right. Just like us. I mean, how are we the ones saving the world when even they don't have what it takes?
Soren and Ivor are always at each other's throats. All I ever see Magnus do is argue.
And we both know what happened to Ellegard.
If the Order can't do this, how are we supposed to?
All I know is the world is depending on us.
Then maybe the world is in trouble. I mean, they defeated an Ender Dragon.
Can you name even one thing we've done right?
And I don't mean managing to stay alive.
Something that actually matters.
I mean, it's not something that really matters.
It's something that really matters.