Well, this record didn't turn on by itself.
Oh, good point. I guess he really likes the sound of his
own voice then.
Maybe there's something useful on this record. If I can
figure out what he's talking about.
I've worked up a simple set of building instructions to
inspire them.
I will disguise myself and hide among them in order to
observe them more closely.
Hmm. Hide among them. Hide among who?
Uh... Jesse? Do you think Soran is talking about... them?
I guess everybody needs hobbies. Even if they are really,
really, really dangerous.
You think he's actually training Enderman to build stuff?
I think he thinks he's training Enderman to build stuff.
Let's look around, see what we can find out.
Olivia, check it out. Looks like a taller one was hanging
there, but it's missing.
Because Soran must be wearing it. This is the disguise he
was talking about.
You mean...
In order to walk amongst the Enderman, you have to become
an Enderman.
Kind of stinky, but it fits.
Ugh, more than kind of stinky, I'm sorry to say.
It's so weird. I know it's you in there, but I still don't
want to look at you.
The missing disguise is the one he had to put on before
going outside.
He must be conducting a training.
I don't know. I don't know.
The missing disguise is the one he had to put on before
going outside.
He must be conducting his experiment right now.
Which means if we want to get to Soran...
We have to go out there to do it.
I'll just wait here.