We need to find a way for me to use this.
Whoa, that is, without question, the coolest thing I have ever, ever seen.
Oh, me too! Nice, Jesse!
Petra, you saw that back at the Far Lands.
It's still cool.
Oh, and I brought you some armor, Axel.
Here.
Nice! I was feeling a little left out.
Grrr!
Guys, let's go kick some command block butt.
Woohoo!
I'm going to get you!
Does anyone see the command block?
I don't think it's exposed!
We need to get more Endermen focused on the Winter Storm!
How do you make Endermen focus? I can't even make myself focus.
We shouldn't be here! None of this is going according to plan!
Soren? What are you doing?
I, uh, you know, I've really enjoyed meeting you all, but...
Soren!
Did Soren just run away?