You feeling any better, Gabriel?
Better is relative. The battle with the Witherstorm sapped
the last of my strength. Considerable though it was.
You need to rest.
You're right, I do.
Look, Jesse, wherever you decide to go after this cave,
give him some time to get his strength back.
Problem is we don't have time.
Jesse's right. In fact, it might be best if my journey ends
here. This cave is safe, easy to defend.
If that's what you feel is best, then I support it. You've
been through too much as it is.
Thank you, Jesse. I'm just sorry that I can't be there for
you.
Me too.
Nothing had to turn out like this. If the order had just
been different, if we'd made smarter choices, Iver wouldn't
have turned into a maniac and...
Well, maybe Magnus would still be alive.
Let's just let bygones be bygones.
But how can we not? So many lives torn asunder. The world
ripped to pieces.