Look, Lukas, Gabriel's sick.
How long have you known?
A while, but he asked me not to say anything.
The wither infected him with something.
So everything I was worried about is true?
This is my fault, Jesse.
Gabriel's wither sickness, it's because of me.
There's no way this is because of you.
If I hadn't choked, you would have been able to pull
Gabriel out of that tractor beam
sooner.
For all we know, Gabriel didn't get sick until way after
that.
Maybe you're right.
If one of our best fighters is sick, do we even stand a
chance anymore?
Not like we haven't dealt with some grade A problems
before, but I just can't help feeling
kind of hopeless.