Gabriel can take care of himself. You just worry about you.
You're hiding something. And by not telling me the truth,
you are putting all of us in danger.
Why don't you go back to looking for Soren? I know you're
sick of talking to me.
I kinda need to get at that lever you're blocking.
Fine.
That wasn't too hard, was it?
Walking one foot to the left? Nope. I think I got that
covered.
That's... weird.
Hey everyone, I think I found Soren's way out!
Oh no, I'm fine. If I wasn't fine, could I do this?
We'll see what we can find in the rest of the house.
I just hope we don't discover Soren as he's getting ready
for bed.
He always wore the most revealing bathrobes.
Let's see what's going on behind this door.
And I call that one Symphony in E.
A new composition to celebrate my newest discovery!
I'm so excited!
Discovery! That's him!
Soren!
What the... It's just a recording.
...undeniable intelligence. I hope I'm not imagining things.
After all that, he's not even here?
I better eat something.
We came all this way and for what?
We're no closer to Soren than before.
I'm so excited!