We politely ask for what's ours.
Short, sweet, and to the point.
Not bad.
You ready?
Ready.
You see anything?
He must have gone out another way.
What is all this?
Looks like it used to be the basement.
A place to have a hideout.
I bet you anything I'll find my wither skull here.
And if we find anything else cool to steal along the way,
so be it, right?
Axel, that's not what we're here to do.
I said we should ask politely, Axel.
Yeah, but if the guy's not here, we can't ask.
So I say, we take.
Let's focus on finding the skull, not stealing.
Nobody ever lets me have any fun.
We let you hang out with us.
The faster we find what we're looking for, the faster we
can get the heck out of here.
Oh, hello.
Too heavy, and too soft.
But super flashy.
You're keeping it?
But I thought it was too soft, too heavy.
Eh, it still might come in handy.
And it is super flashy.
Hey, you still have that one stone sword, right?
Nah, I had to give it to some jerk Wad Butcher to save
Reuben's life.
Geez. Oh well. I guess that was a pretty good cause.
Here.
Thanks. Again.
You're welcome. Don't lose that one.
Find anything?
I wanna steal that, and that.
I just wanna touch that.
Boo, take a look at this.
You're not gonna believe me, but I swear I had a dream
about this.
Okay, potion. I know this is a big step, but...
I would be honored if you'd come home with me.