I wouldn't mind a little payback. He deserves it for
crossing Petra. You ready? Ready
You see anything? He must have gone out another way
What is all this? Looks like it used to be the basement, a
weird place to have a hideout
I bet you anything I'll find my wither skull here. And if
we find anything else cool to steal along the way, so be
it, right?
Axel, that's not what we're here to do. I
Did say we wanted payback. No better paybacks than thieving
from a thief, right?
Let's focus on finding the skull not stealing. Nobody ever
lets me have any fun
We let you hang out with us. The faster we find what we're
looking for the faster we can get the heck out of here
Oh
Hello
Too heavy and too soft but super flashy
You're keeping it but I thought it was too soft too heavy
It still might come in handy and it is super flashy
Hey, you still have that one stone sword, right? Now I had
to give it to some jerk Watt butcher to save Ruben's life
Geez. Oh, well, I guess that was a pretty good cause here
Thanks again, you're welcome. Don't lose that one
Find anything I want to steal that and that I just want to
touch that
Boo take a look at this you're not gonna believe me, but I
swear I had a dream about this
Okay potion. I know this is a big step but I
Would be honored if you'd come home with me