You can be anywhere, stay in your guard!
Vanish all you want, slimeball! You're still not going
anywhere!
End of the rail, Ivor. We're not letting you get away with
this.
This one's on you, you puffed up fool!
There's no time for this.
Jesse! Petra! Even more of you?
Will this parade of useless babblers never cease?
What's going on?
We found Ivor. He stopped him.
Jesse did, anyway.
False. You have stopped nothing.
Aquarian, have you ever seen the effects of a splash potion
of slowness?
What?
What are you talking about?
You bitch!
Magnus and Ellegaard may think they can stop me, that they can
destroy the Witherstorm,
but they are mistaken, and it will cost them their lives.