It's one of his invisibility potions, he could be anywhere!
Vanish all you want, slimeball. You're still not going
anywhere.
End of the rail, Ivor. We're not letting you get away with
this.
This one's on you, you beautiful!
There's no time for this.
Jesse! Petra! Even more of you?
Will this parade of useless babblers never cease?
What's going on?
We found Ivor. We stopped him.
Jesse did, anyway.
False! You have stopped nothing.
Aquarian, have you ever seen the effects of a splash potion
of slowness?
What?
All around...
You, Petra...
Get out!
Magnus and Ellegaard may think they can stop me, that they
can destroy the Witherstorm,
but they are mistaken, and it will cost them their lives.