Everything in the universe starts out as just a block.
What comes of those blocks is up to those who wield them.
Our friends have traveled far and wide in search of the
Order of the Stone
and a way to stop the wither storm for good.
But even well-laid plans can go awry.
The threat to this world, to its very existence, is far
from over.
No!
Where am I? What's going on?
Come on, I'm going to get you out of here.
What? Who are you?
Jesse, Jesse, where are you?
We're coming!
No way, no way!
Get down Gabriel!
It's Gabriel!
Get out of here!
Jesse, you made it!
Then, Gabriel?
Did you say Gabriel?
Look out!
Those Endermen are running the wrong way! They'll be killed!
Shoren, what do you think you're doing?
These Endermen are running directly into danger!
You're putting us in danger every second you just stand
there!
Whoa!
Jesse, they're falling behind!
Axel, you gotta move faster!
She's too sick, and that's the best we can do!
They're not going to be able to outrun it, not on foot!
We just need to get them moving faster.
Bingo!
Everybody, get on!
Get on!
Hey, what about us?
Come on Jesse, we got this!
We'll take the reins, and they can just hang on.