If we stick together we can do anything even something that
feels impossible it just feels extra impossible now
Then we stick together extra hard
Okay, I just kind of wish Petra would tell everybody just
make things easier I
Kind of need to get at that lever you're blocking
Thanks
Yep
That's weird
Hey everyone, I think I found soren's way out
Nope don't want it don't need it. Thanks
We'll check out the rest of the house see if we can find
soren before he finds us
Let's see what's going on behind this door
That's him soren
It's just recording
After all that
We came all this way and for what we're no closer to soren
than before
You