it's the most beautiful place I've ever seen
so bright
second
what it's made of wool this tree the grass it's it's all
wool you're telling
me that we've been resting all our hopes on this guy and
the whole time he's been
building some totally artificial happy land could it be
that he just missed
home if you miss home you go and visit you don't build an
exact replica we came
here for nothing we came here for Sorin and for his
formidable that's still the plan just look around Jesse if
the greatest builder
of all time has spent years working on this what are the
chances he's even gonna
have that bomb huh I got enough crazy for one day
what's his problem just give him some space he'll be okay
so I'm probably looking for well to open a secret door you
need a secret mechanism
you